<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Visual Novel on Game Vibe</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/tags/visual-novel/</link><description>Recent content in Visual Novel on Game Vibe</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://game-vibe.github.io/tags/visual-novel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Joker's Game</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-jokers-game/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-jokers-game/</guid><description>Game Description The Jokers Game is an FMV crime game where every decision has fatal consequences for the character. The process of overcoming challenges requires maximum intellectual and strategic concentration from the gamer. Competitors will face challenges such as drawing complex shapes using chocolate icing or navigating a maze filled with optical illusions. A significant part of the competition is devoted to exerting psychological pressure and eliminating opponents through a special voting system.</description></item><item><title>Anxiety Puppy</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/anxiety-puppy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/anxiety-puppy/</guid><description>Game Description Anxiety Puppy is an interactive story that focuses on coming to terms with your inner state. At the center of the plot is an unusual metaphor, where anxiety takes on a physical embodiment in the form of a small puppy. This approach turns a complex psychological topic into a touching fairy tale for adults. The project is made in the original style of an illustrated book, and the entire visual range is made by hand.</description></item><item><title>UNBEATABLE</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/unbeatable/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/unbeatable/</guid><description>Game Description UNBEATABLE is about a band on the run from the law in a world where music is a crime. The plot follows a girl named Beat and her companions as they navigate a repressive society where live concerts are an act of defiance. Clashes with law enforcement occupy a central place in the story, often escalating into direct skirmishes that force the heroes to flee. The situation is complicated by encounters with mysterious monsters and alliances with other individuals wanted by the authorities.</description></item><item><title>No, I'm not a Voenkom</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/no-im-not-a-voenkom/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/no-im-not-a-voenkom/</guid><description>Game Description No, I&amp;rsquo;m not a Voenkom is a psychological thriller whose plot revolves around a sudden invasion of personal space. A sharp knock on the door becomes a catalyst for a whole series of tense events that test the protagonist&amp;rsquo;s endurance. Every interaction with the outside world becomes a difficult choice between trying to remain safe and risking succumbing to destructive curiosity. The oppressive atmosphere of an old apartment, where the air is saturated with the smell of dust and paint, increases the feeling of isolation.</description></item><item><title>Alice's World</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/alices-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/alices-world/</guid><description>Game Description Alices World is a story-driven 2D adventure in which the gamer plays an unusual role. There is no place for role-playing here, because the player acts as himself - the voice that the main character hears from behind the screen. A girl named Alice, waking up in a world filled with death, is completely dependent on instructions from the outside. You can be an honest guide or a deceiver, help or deliberately lead to death.</description></item><item><title>Dreaming Blue</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dreaming-blue/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dreaming-blue/</guid><description>Game Description Dreaming Blue is a romantic visual novel in which the main goal is to get rid of an ancient curse. Fate brings the main character, a young woman, with two powerful deities who can help her in this difficult task. The first of these is Zenith, the patron of good fortune, who has a playful disposition and is associated with cats. His complete opposite is Sirius, a mysterious ancient deity whose symbol is the wolf.</description></item><item><title>Galaxy Princess Zorana</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/galaxy-princess-zorana/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/galaxy-princess-zorana/</guid><description>Game Description Galaxy Princess Zorana is a strategic life simulator, the main task of which is to conquer the throne of the Heavenly Empire after the sudden death of your father. The previously carefree life of the second heir to the throne, known for her love of beautiful shoes and pets, is changing dramatically. After the death of his mother and the betrayal of his brother, who was considered a prince, the emperor disappears under mysterious circumstances.</description></item><item><title>Dictator Simulator: Gradnar</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dictator-simulator-gradnar/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dictator-simulator-gradnar/</guid><description>Game Description Dictator Simulator: Gradnar is a political simulator where the government of the fictional Eastern European state of Gradnar is associated with the constant threat of a coup. In the role of dictator Vyslan Gatskolki will have to determine the fate of an entire nation, maneuvering between the democratic vector of development and harsh autocracy. Each decision directly affects key indicators, including the economy, army loyalty and party support. Neglect of these systems inevitably leads to the overthrow of the regime.</description></item><item><title>Home</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/home/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/home/</guid><description>Game Description Home is a pixel adventure, the plot of which reveals a short but eventful segment in the life of a boy who left his home. This narrative, based on real events, offers to follow the fate of the protagonist, whose new refuge becomes the space under the bridge. His main occupation is street musical performances, during which he encounters unexpected acquaintances. The whole story is presented in a restrained and honest manner, reminiscent in style of a short musical film.</description></item><item><title>Demonschool</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/demonschool/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/demonschool/</guid><description>Game Description Demonschool brings a new twist to tactical RPGs by making movement the core of your strategy. You lead Faye and her team through trials that blur the lines between the human and demon worlds. All this happens on a mysterious island where school life takes a demonic turn. A key mechanic allows you to rewind actions while planning, creating complex combos to defeat pesky enemies. This rewind feature adds a layer of challenge, forcing you to strategize like a chess grandmaster to outsmart your enemies.</description></item><item><title>Chill with You: Lo-Fi Story</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/chill-with-you-lo-fi-story/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/chill-with-you-lo-fi-story/</guid><description>Game Description Chill with You: Lo-Fi Story immerses you in a world where the main goal is to establish a deep emotional connection with Satone, a gifted and imaginative girl who devotes herself to writing stories. Progress in relationships directly depends on the time spent working together at the same table. Each break turns into a valuable opportunity for communication, allowing you to get to know the young writer better and strengthen the budding friendship.</description></item><item><title>Beyond R: Rule Ripper</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/beyond-r-rule-ripper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/beyond-r-rule-ripper/</guid><description>Game Description Beyond R: Rule Ripper is a visual novel that places ten strangers in a ruthless game of survival. Finding themselves locked in the mysterious Golden Jack bar, they learn from the mysterious Boss that they have been poisoned. The only chance of salvation lies in following the rules or breaking them completely, setting the stage for a tense psychological thriller.
The ultimate goal for each of the captives is to survive until there are three or fewer people left alive.</description></item><item><title>Hymer 2000</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/hymer-2000/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/hymer-2000/</guid><description>Game Description Hymer 2000 plunges into a melancholy and philosophical story, where a mundane task of disposing of an outdated artificial intelligence module turns into a deep investigation for technician Frank. He is sent to a mysterious residential complex called Hope Residence with the goal of carrying out a complete shutdown of the system named Hymer. However, upon arrival, he is confronted with digital fragments of other people&amp;rsquo;s memories, mysterious images and long-buried secrets.</description></item><item><title>Rue Valley</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rue-valley/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rue-valley/</guid><description>Game Description Rue Valley plunges into the depths of human consciousness, allowing you to live countless lives in the body of one person. Each new cycle of a temporary anomaly becomes a chance to radically change the protagonist’s personality. Yesterday&amp;rsquo;s cold-blooded loner, inclined to analyze everything, the next day can turn into an expressive melancholic, trusting only instincts. These constant metamorphoses are not just an experiment, but the only tool for unraveling the mystery that holds the hero in an endless day and forces him to fight the shadows of his own mind.</description></item><item><title>Yes, My Queen</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/yes-my-queen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/yes-my-queen/</guid><description>Game Description Yes, My Queen is a tactical strategy game where magic and absurd tricks break the canonical rules of chess. To break free from captivity, you will have to defeat a chain of opponents in a series of fights, whose power is constantly increasing, which will require both a sharp mind and a willingness to disregard the foundations. There are over forty different cards at your disposal, the use of which can radically change the situation on the board.</description></item><item><title>Choice of Life: Samosbor</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/choice-of-life-samosbor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/choice-of-life-samosbor/</guid><description>Game Description Choice of Life: Samosbor is a visual novel that immerses you in the gloomy reality of the endless Gigakhrushchevka. The usual way of life of its inhabitants collapses at one moment, when one of the blocks becomes isolated from the rest of the world. The reason for the cordon is the search for a mysterious secret object, turning gray everyday life into an intense struggle for survival. The mournful wail of a siren and the hermetically sealed doors of residential cells now foreshadow not just another shift, but an unknown filled with total control and suspicion.</description></item><item><title>Service with a Shotgun</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/service-with-a-shotgun/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/service-with-a-shotgun/</guid><description>Game Description Service with a Shotgun plunges you into an absurd reality where retail rules apply even during a zombie apocalypse. The main task becomes not only survival among the hordes of the undead, but also high-quality service to the eccentric customers lining up at the half-empty shelves. While the living dead are wandering outside the window, a real drama is unfolding inside the store: you need to speak quickly, shoot accurately and build defensive structures in order to survive the next work shift.</description></item><item><title>Snowfall's Mystery</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/snowfalls-mystery/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/snowfalls-mystery/</guid><description>Game Description Snowfall&amp;rsquo;s Mystery plunges into the mind of a student computer programmer named Elliot, who encounters a mysterious program during the cold winter of 1999. An ordinary floppy disk received from a friend becomes the source of inexplicable events when the Snowfall messenger contained on it begins a dialogue. The program demonstrates a frightening awareness of the hero&amp;rsquo;s inner world, and the mysterious Administrator gets in touch, pursuing unknown goals.</description></item><item><title>Syrup 2: Candy Alchemy RPG</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/syrup-2-candy-alchemy-rpg/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/syrup-2-candy-alchemy-rpg/</guid><description>Game Description Syrup 2: Candy Alchemy RPG is a role-playing adventure where the alchemical synthesis of sweets is a central element of the gameplay. The main task for the protagonist named Syrup is to significantly enrich the assortment of her confectionery shop Atelier Sweets. To do this, you need to travel, collecting rare components from all over the world. Defeating magical opponents provides access to unique ingredients needed to create new treats.</description></item><item><title>Truth Universally Acknowledged</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/truth-universally-acknowledged/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/truth-universally-acknowledged/</guid><description>Game Description Truth Universally Acknowledged is a short dating sim where players experience a few days in the life of a typical high school student. The main character is a young man named Talai, whose daily life is filled with study and communication with friends. The narrative revolves around non-linear choices that determine which of four potential partners the protagonist will become romantically involved with. The key feature of the project is the decision-making mechanics: instead of standard text lines, you need to choose Talai’s facial expressions and emotions.</description></item><item><title>Love Craft</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/love-craft/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/love-craft/</guid><description>Game Description Love Craft is a dating simulator where the search for a soulmate is based on the principle of selection within a creative circle. Events take place within the walls of Cubiversity University, where the protagonist arrives as a new student. The central element of the story is joining the prestigious Handicraft Club. Here you will have to form a working group of 5 candidates, choosing them from 15 available classmates.</description></item><item><title>UltraGirl Alters</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ultragirl-alters/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ultragirl-alters/</guid><description>Game Description UltraGirl Alters is a tactical project in which the gamer controls a group of virtual idols, Alters, fighting the creations of corporate algorithms. Five girls, dressed in tokusatsu-style battle suits, confront monsters on live-streamed battlefields. The outcome of each clash is determined not only by the competent use of the heroines’ unique abilities, but also by the reaction of the audience to the actions of the commander. Accumulating SP points gives you access to ultimate attacks that can destroy entire squads of enemies or deal devastating damage to bosses.</description></item><item><title>GHOST TRAVELER: Adventures in Edo</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ghost-traveler-adventures-in-edo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ghost-traveler-adventures-in-edo/</guid><description>Game Description GHOST TRAVELER: Adventures in Edo is a mystical visual novel that follows the investigation into a series of brutal murders set against the backdrop of Japan&amp;rsquo;s Yoshiwara entertainment district. The main character is a 17-year-old boy named Kotaro, whose soul, after a supernatural incident in modern Shibuya, is transported to the 19th century. Having learned from a certain deity about the death of his physical body, the protagonist finds himself locked in the past with no clear path to returning home or moving on to the afterlife.</description></item><item><title>Undusted: Letters from the Past</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/undusted-letters-from-the-past/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/undusted-letters-from-the-past/</guid><description>Game Description Undusted Letters from the Past is a touching story about a girl named Jane who, after moving into her late grandmother&amp;rsquo;s house, discovers an abandoned workshop full of dusty and broken objects. Every item, be it an old camera or a music box, requires careful restoration. The process of dusting and repairing the mechanisms reveals hidden letters and memories, gradually revealing a secret love story from her family&amp;rsquo;s past.</description></item><item><title>Yomegami: My Sweet Goddess</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/yomegami-my-sweet-goddess/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/yomegami-my-sweet-goddess/</guid><description>Game Description Yomegami My Sweet Goddess is a story about the difficult fate of Hayato Narukawa, whose new life suddenly turns into a series of comical and awkward situations. A sudden kiss with Ichijiku Mikoto, the daughter of the head of a local crime syndicate, jeopardizes his deepest mission. Now the protagonist will have to find a common language not only with the mafia heiress, but also with the clumsy class leader, as well as with a naive girl with dog ears.</description></item><item><title>Ascend From Nine Mountains</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ascend-from-nine-mountains/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ascend-from-nine-mountains/</guid><description>Game Description Ascend From Nine Mountains is a story about the metamorphosis of a mortal into a deity, where fate is determined through the mastery of six deadly combat schools and the creation of powerful artifacts. The world of this project lives by its own laws: the change of seasons directly affects the environment, and autumn auctions become a place where the strongest adepts fight for legendary items. Survival requires exploring ancient rock-cut fortresses and trading in bustling cultivator cities, where valuable pills and treasures are exchanged for spiritual stones.</description></item><item><title>Murder Is Game Over: Murder Otaku</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/murder-is-game-over-murder-otaku/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/murder-is-game-over-murder-otaku/</guid><description>Game Description Murder Is Game Over Murder Otaku is a mysterious incident at the pop culture convention YokaiKon, where a detective duo must unravel a mysterious crime. The main characters, Detective Guy and his faithful dog Cleo, arrive at the historic 1920s hotel that serves as the venue for the event. Their mission begins after the tragic death of a famous J-pop singer, whose death shrouds the noisy event in an ominous mystery.</description></item><item><title>Syrup and the Ultimate Sweet</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/syrup-and-the-ultimate-sweet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/syrup-and-the-ultimate-sweet/</guid><description>Game Description Syrup and the Ultimate Sweet is a visual novel where failure to create a magical dessert sets off a chain of unpredictable events. The conflict flares up when the main character Syrup, who fundamentally does not use magic in confectionery, rejects the idea of ​​​​creating the so-called Ideal Sweetness. This decision prompts a living candy golem named Gumdrop to escape from the workshop. In her search for the necessary magical ingredients, she joins forces with Butterscotch, Syrup&amp;rsquo;s longtime rival, complicating an already difficult situation for all parties involved.</description></item><item><title>Forsaker: Dingding and Blade</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/forsaker-dingding-and-blade/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/forsaker-dingding-and-blade/</guid><description>Game Description Forsaker: Dingding and Blade begins with a regular mission for two young men, which develops into a Cannibal Odyssey on the Hel continent. The local world is divided into three fractions: people, the Church of the Divine Body and the devouring flesh of the outcasts. Players explore this society, constantly faced with the main choice: to eat another or become prey. The plot reveals deep conspiracies and casts doubt on the established order and the very nature of survival.</description></item><item><title>Wander Stars</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/wander-stars/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/wander-stars/</guid><description>Game Description In Wander Stars, martial artist Ringo and a scoundrel named Wolf work together to search for pieces of a legendary map across the universe. Their alliance becomes the basis for the search for Ringo&amp;rsquo;s brother and the discovery of the secrets of Wolfe&amp;rsquo;s past - a story told in 10 separate episodes. This space adventure involves forming alliances with a variety of characters, gradually creating a real family. The plot touches on themes of mystery, betrayal and redemption as the duo travels between worlds.</description></item><item><title>Sora no Kiseki the 1st</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sora-no-kiseki-the-1st/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sora-no-kiseki-the-1st/</guid><description>Game Description Sora no Kiseki the 1st follows Estelle and Joshua on their first journey through the Kingdom of Liberl. As junior Bracers, defenders of peace in the region, they travel between cities, carrying out assignments and resolving local conflicts. This activity serves as training for them, but their wanderings are also prompted by the disappearance of their father, Cassius. Along their journey, the heroes meet new allies and experience important partings, while a great destiny gradually unfolds before them.</description></item><item><title>I Hate My Waifu Streamer</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/i-hate-my-waifu-streamer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/i-hate-my-waifu-streamer/</guid><description>Game Description In I Hate My Waifu Streamer, the gamer will have to capture the attention of the streamer before other viewers. The main goal is to interact with a girl named Mio during her live broadcasts. Communication is based on writing chat messages and sending donations to stand out among other subscribers. This competition for recognition forms the basis of the gameplay, and financial support becomes a key way to develop relationships and attract Mio&amp;rsquo;s interest.</description></item><item><title>Type-NOISE: Shonen Shojo</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/type-noise-shonen-shojo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/type-noise-shonen-shojo/</guid><description>Game Description Type-NOISE: Shonen Shojo takes place in a familiar but altered version of Tokyo, where six teenagers who have lost their memories gather. Locked in the city, they are forced to wander through bizarre labyrinths in search of a way out. The only way forward lies through the restoration of lost memories, revealing the sealed pages of the past. The main goal is not just an escape from physical captivity, but a meeting with the real you, forgotten for a good reason.</description></item><item><title>Misty Judgment</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/misty-judgment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/misty-judgment/</guid><description>Game Description Misty Judgment begins with the awakening of the protagonist, qi and, from a nightmare in a strange reality without clear memories. Unable to confirm his own personality, he investigates a series of murders filed in the video format with real actors. The main task is the search and analysis of evidence, the comparison of facts and the calculation of the criminal. Any solution affects further events, and the future of the protagonist depends on the deductive abilities of the player.</description></item><item><title>Dead Reset</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dead-reset/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dead-reset/</guid><description>Game Description In Dead Reset, surgeon Cole Mason is forced to operate on a patient to remove a parasitic organism while isolated in an underwater station. After being kidnapped and taken to this facility, the protagonist becomes trapped in a brutal and repeating cycle of death. Each failure and the terrible death that follows is not the end, but a way to look at the situation from a different angle. This series of deaths becomes the main method of gathering information, uncovering the truth and finding a way to escape from the bloody trap.</description></item><item><title>SHUTEN ORDER</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/shuten-order/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/shuten-order/</guid><description>Game Description SHUTEN ORDER immerses gamers in the story of the resurrected founder of a religious nation, awakening without memories after being dismembered. He is given only 4 days to complete the divine test: to find and eliminate his own killer among 5 ministers. Events unfold in a world that has 168 days left to exist, against the backdrop of the rapid emergence of the Shuten Order as a new state.</description></item><item><title>Kemono Teatime</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/kemono-teatime/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/kemono-teatime/</guid><description>Game Description Kemono Teatime invites the player to lead a cafe in the world of Melodius, which has become a refuge for visitors with animal ears. The main task is to prepare signature tea blends for a diverse clientele, where each guest has their own history and preferences. Communication with these characters is central to the narrative, as their visits are temporary and serve as a prelude to their eventual fate.</description></item><item><title>Death end re;Quest: Code Z</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/death-end-request-code-z/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/death-end-request-code-z/</guid><description>Game Description Death end re;Quest: Code Z sends Sayaka Hiwatari into the Voltage Area, a parallel universe made up of deadly dungeons. These locations contain randomly generated monsters and traps that react to her actions. For every movement of the player character, hostile creatures respond with their own move to move or attack. The gameplay involves navigating the dungeon floors to find items and try to go deeper. In this reality, people who were once allies may now turn out to be enemies.</description></item><item><title>The Dark Queen of Mortholme</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-dark-queen-of-mortholme/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-dark-queen-of-mortholme/</guid><description>Game Description The Dark Queen of Mortholme starts from the victory of the Land overlord over the invading hero. The conflict, it would seem, is exhausted, but the applicant is inexplicably returning, meeting the right death over and over again. This violence cycle takes place in a two -dimensional world with a fixed screen, where the player uses the queen&amp;rsquo;s arsenal to multiply pacify the insolent. The plot reveals the secret of the stubbornness of the antagonist, offering a short adventure combining action with a rich history.</description></item><item><title>Static Dread: The Lighthouse</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/static-dread-the-lighthouse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/static-dread-the-lighthouse/</guid><description>Game Description Static Dread: The Lighthouse begins after the global cataclysm, placing the player on the island far from the coast. The port authorities re -activate the lighthouse again, sending the only caretaker to control him. He uses radio equipment to send ships to the harbor - a task that has consequences for the city and vessels at sea. On the mainland, a wife and daughter are waiting for him, a fact that affects his work and spiritual state.</description></item><item><title>Flower in Us</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/flower-in-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/flower-in-us/</guid><description>Game Description Flower in Us features a narrative where the protagonist wakes up in a basement after a brutal attack that erases all personal memory. Nearby is a tied up young woman, in whose gaze one can read a familiar feeling that is unrequited for the player character. She recognizes the main character, but this recognition is not mutual, which immediately creates tension in a closed space. The first goal is to navigate this harsh environment and assess the current situation.</description></item><item><title>Yume Kakigori</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/yume-kakigori/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/yume-kakigori/</guid><description>Game Description Yume Kakigori is the story of a visitor from different times and places who finds solace in a secluded establishment located among the clouds. Each ice-cold dessert served determines the further development of the plot, opening new branches of dialogue and relationships. Objects and scattered notes left by guests serve as fragments of a large mosaic, by collecting which one can understand their past. Gradually, these details not only form a closer connection with each client, but also reveal the truth about this unusual world and its inhabitants.</description></item><item><title>and Roger</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/and-roger/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/and-roger/</guid><description>Game Description and Roger is an interactive novel that begins in the morning, deviating from the usual routine for the main character. Waking up, she discovers her father missing from their home. Instead, a man previously unknown to her is sleeping on the sofa in the living room. When he comes to, the stranger speaks in broken sentences and tells the girl to take medicine, showing sadness in his voice and ignoring her confusion.</description></item><item><title>Magical Girl Witch Trials</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/magical-girl-witch-trials/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/magical-girl-witch-trials/</guid><description>Game Description Magical Girl Witch Trials opens with high school student Emma awakening in a gloomy prison cell. She turns out to be one of 13 girls forcibly brought to a complex on a remote island. An owl appears and declares that a witch is hiding among them and must be found. The captives are told that they will spend the rest of their lives here if they fail to expose the culprit in a formal trial.</description></item><item><title>DRAPLINE</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/drapline/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/drapline/</guid><description>Game Description DRAPLINE is a roguelike simulation that tasks the player with raising a dragon girl in one in-game year to prevent a global catastrophe. The main mechanic of nurturing involves feeding the character a variety of items to develop her special abilities. Her diet is unlimited, allowing her to consume materials ranging from common foods like meat and fish to unconventional matter such as rocks, iron, lava, and even other people&amp;rsquo;s houses.</description></item><item><title>Longstory 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/longstory-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/longstory-2/</guid><description>Game Description Longstory 2 continues the established narrative with a large number of dates, developing friendly relations and difficult situations. The action takes place in the summer in front of a high school, immediately after the events of the previous part. During the party, in honor of Marseille&amp;rsquo;s return, a personality, known as Turkeyhawk, disappears home. This event gives the start of the main riddle, offering the player to find this character.</description></item><item><title>Kill the Clock</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/kill-the-clock/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/kill-the-clock/</guid><description>Game Description Kill the Clock immerses players in the role of the vengeful protagonist, moving along the gloomy European streets of the mid-1900s and finding that his sworn enemy is already killed by an unknown attacker. Accused of this atrocity, the player must reveal the riddle of the death of his enemy. The investigation occurs inside the repeating temporary cycle, forcing the protagonist to live the same seven -day to live again, while each round offers another option for a deprivation of life, which must be unraveled before the time is overturned, in the intricacies of insidious deception.</description></item><item><title>CraftCraft: Fantasy Merchant Simulator</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/craftcraft-fantasy-merchant-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/craftcraft-fantasy-merchant-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description CraftCraft: Fantasy Merchant Simulator sends gamers on a trip to the world of Windspell, a port city filled with potential and adventures. Users stand in place of a merchant, ready to create unique items that can change the fate of the city. This game is not just about the trade in goods, it is about how to pave your way through creativity. Whether you create intricate necklaces for royal mermaids or a weapon from the blood of dragons - each item has its own charm.</description></item><item><title>Mystery Island: Missing Amy</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mystery-islandmissing-amy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mystery-islandmissing-amy/</guid><description>Game Description Mystery Island: Missing Amy tells about the hell, the researcher, looking for sister, mysteriously missing months ago. The plot unfolds when hell receives a selfie from a loved one; The picture captures the missing girl on a remote island, where sea water has a bloody red color. This frame encourages hell to take a sea trip to search for a relative and study the location from a mysterious message.</description></item><item><title>Best Served Cold</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/best-served-cold/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/best-served-cold/</guid><description>Game Description The Best Served Cold puts a gamer at the Knightsp Rack, an underground bar, working during the dry law in the alternative European city of Bukovia. You take on the role of a bartender responsible for the preparation of cocktails for visitors to the institution. Intections go beyond the maintenance, including direct clashes with persons identified as criminals and the need to navigate in dangerous situations.
The main actions include the investigation of the murders taking place in this environment while maintaining the work of the bar.</description></item><item><title>Obscured Stories: The Resentment</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/obscured-stories-the-resentment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/obscured-stories-the-resentment/</guid><description>Game Description Obscured Stories: The Resentment is a psychological horror, the narrative of which is based on the interrogation of the main character by the police. During an interview with investigators, Lisa Parker relives the events of a fateful night that happened while she was in Japan in the early 2000s. Reconstructing a complete picture of the incident is complicated by the fragmentation of memories, presented in the form of fragments of audio recordings and video materials.</description></item><item><title>All in Abyss: Judge the Fake</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/all-in-abyss-judge-the-fake/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/all-in-abyss-judge-the-fake/</guid><description>Game Description All in Abyss: Judge the Fake introduces us to Asuha Senahara, a self-proclaimed gambling genius who seeks dominance in a special area where gambling rules. After challenging the ruling Witch of the gambling district, Asuha suffers her first defeat due to a mysterious power and falls into despair. Determined to take revenge, she begins an adventure of high-stakes poker, uncovering fraud, and amassing wealth. Her journey involves challenging her opponents to duels to the death, where either she or the Witches will die.</description></item><item><title>Disney Villains Cursed Cafe</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/disney-villains-cursed-cafe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/disney-villains-cursed-cafe/</guid><description>Game Description Disney Villains Cursed Cafe begins in a mysterious cafe where every drink has a hidden meaning. The player takes on the role of a new potion maker, working with regular clients whose requests seem simple only at first glance. In this space, characters from a familiar universe place orders without revealing their true intentions. Here, each interaction changes the balance of power and affects the further development of events.</description></item><item><title>Falling for yaoguais</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/falling-for-yaoguais/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/falling-for-yaoguais/</guid><description>Game Description In Falling for Yaoguais, the main character enters the entertainment park, which is controlled by supernatural creatures from Taiwanese folklore. Having settled in appearance to ordinary work, she finds out that this is a trap to attract people as food. The protagonist will have to be disguised as Yaoguay for a secret investigation of the conspiracy underlying the activities of the institution. The girl maneuverates in a brewing conflict between people and inhuman staff, trying to preserve her cover.</description></item><item><title>Immortal Hunters</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/immortal-hunters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/immortal-hunters/</guid><description>Game Description The Immortal Hunters action begins in a world that has forever changed as a result of one fateful act. The church, which once served as a lighthouse of light and leadership, went to a radical step, killing God. That is how - God is dead, and behind this is the church. This is not an ordinary story about faith and devotion; This is a story about power, manipulations and survival.</description></item><item><title>Deadly Heart Gambit</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/deadly-heart-gambit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/deadly-heart-gambit/</guid><description>Game Description Deadly Heart Gambit is an intense card competition, where each card drawn can either extend the allotted time or bring the fatal ending closer. Participants in this fight will have to rely on memory and strategic thinking to avoid a fatal meeting with the Joker, which means an instant loss in the round. Defeat is awarded to the one who draws this single card. To win, you must carefully monitor the cards already played and wisely use the opportunity to skip your turn.</description></item><item><title>PASSIONERS</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/passioners/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/passioners/</guid><description>Game Description PASSIONERS is a visual novel, the action of which takes place on board a spaceship setting off to colonize a distant planet. Having woken up prematurely from cryosleep, the main character finds himself isolated on a ship where women are kept in numerous cryopods. The mission has gone off course, and now the main character must decide which women to awaken and how to interact with them. The dynamics of the emerging relationship and the direction of plot development will depend on the choice made.</description></item><item><title>Recall: Empty Wishes</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/recall-empty-wishes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/recall-empty-wishes/</guid><description>Game Description Recall: Empty Wishes immerses you in a dark atmosphere of exploration, where you have to wander as different characters through frightening locations and understand mystical events. A group of friends one day encounters the disappearance of Tommy Lin, a smart and attentive boy. The guys decide to go in search of the young man in order to save him from possible troubles. The game is made in the horror genre, drawn in an anime style.</description></item><item><title>Star Knightess aura</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/star-knightess-aura/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/star-knightess-aura/</guid><description>Game Description Star Knightess aura - Anime -Nella, the main character of which is a girl with an unusual name of the aura. She falls into a fantastic world called Roya. The heroine is cursed by the king of demons. Its task is to deal with otherworldly monsters every night. At the same time, it is very important not to lose yourself. The girl has insanity and she begins to consider herself a completely different person.</description></item><item><title>Winter Hubris</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/winter-hubris/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/winter-hubris/</guid><description>Game Description Winter Hubris is about confronting not only external threats, but also internal decay. The inexorable spread of a terrible disease, the need to control hunger indicators and maintain the remnants of sanity become central elements of the narrative. The main character named Richard finds himself in complete isolation within the walls of an abandoned scientific complex in the mountains. His main task is to wait for the return of his team, which left him during the mission to retrieve the bodies.</description></item><item><title>Threefold Recital</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/threefold-recital/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/threefold-recital/</guid><description>Game Description Threefold Recital invites gamers to move to bright eastern fantasy, where the overgrown city of Bluscles stands on the threshold of a new era. Once the city was warmed in the rays of the Golden Age, and now it is mired in political instability and tension. Title draws a picture of the world where ancient magic and modern technologies are intertwined, creating a unique mixture that drives the narrative forward.</description></item><item><title>The Haunting of Joni Evers</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-haunting-of-joni-evers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-haunting-of-joni-evers/</guid><description>Game Description The Haunting of Joni Evers takes gamers into the isolated world of Joni, a woman living in a mansion in Harvest, Oklahoma. The plot tells a complex tale of family, loss and the unsettling presence of something dark in an old house. Joni&amp;rsquo;s life, once marked by distance from her family, begins to unravel after a tense argument with her only friend. Subsequent events in The Haunting of Joni Evers draw the user deeper into the secrets of the house, revealing fragments of the past, painful and mysterious.</description></item><item><title>Anime City</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/anime-city/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/anime-city/</guid><description>Game Description Anime City transfers gamers to a bright 3D virtual Tokyo, inspired by anime culture. Title combines the mechanics of the visual novel and sandbox, creating an interactive environment, focused on everyday life, social interactions and school experience. Users stand in the place of a high school student, moving along a dynamic, fictitious city landscape, interacting with the characters, exploring key places and participating in various events.
Title offers many ways to plunge into this detailed city - from clubs after lessons to public events and part -time work.</description></item><item><title>Midori no Kaori</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/midori-no-kaori/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/midori-no-kaori/</guid><description>Game Description Midori no Kaori is an adventure game based on the art of peaceful store management. In this relaxed environment, gamers will create and manage their own establishment, drawing on elements of Japanese culture to shape their vision. The title doesn&amp;rsquo;t focus on fast-paced action or intense competition, but rather encourages players to create a space that reflects their personal taste. There are no strict goals or deadlines, making it a refreshing alternative to many other games that prioritize speed or performance.</description></item><item><title>Touch Type Tale - Strategic Typing</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/touch-type-tale-strategic-typing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/touch-type-tale-strategic-typing/</guid><description>Game Description Touch Type Tale - Strategic Typing immerses users in battles between armies that take place during the Dark Middle Ages. The game is made in the genre of real-time strategy, where you have to deal with printing and solving multi-task missions. The protagonist is a guy named Paul who wants to prevail over the evil forces. Gameplay mechanics allow you to test the typing speed of users, where the ability to type the necessary keys blindly is useful in order to keep control over the events that are happening.</description></item><item><title>YS X: Nordics</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ys-x-nordics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ys-x-nordics/</guid><description>Game Description YS X: Nordics invites gamers to a bright world filled with adventures and research. The action is unfolding in the northern seas of the Opel Gulf, and the main character, Adol Christin, acts as a young adventurer. The narrative unfolds on a variety of archipelago, where normann norman normann inhabit various islands. Each island offers a unique environment that captivates gamers and makes them explore every corner. Thanks to the rich historical background, Advencura creates the basis for exciting quests and interaction with the characters.</description></item><item><title>The Dawn: Sniper's Way</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-dawn-snipers-way/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-dawn-snipers-way/</guid><description>Game Description The Dawn: Sniper&amp;rsquo;s Way crosses a post-apocalyptic setting with a post-Soviet atmosphere. The game invites you to wander around Seversk. This is the name of a fictional industrial city. Previously, research laboratories and a nuclear power plant operated on its territory. In 1981, a disaster occurred there due to floods. After this, all residents were evacuated, and the settlement was abandoned. The video game itself takes place many years later, in 2025.</description></item><item><title>Whimel Academy</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/whimel-academy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/whimel-academy/</guid><description>Game Description Whimel Academy immerses gamers in the everyday life of a magic school student. This time management simulation game offers a fun environment where users juggle classes, extracurricular activities, and social interactions. Every day is a combination of learning and personal growth as gamers navigate the complexities of school and relationships. By taking on the role of a student, users will experience the ups and downs of managing schedules and developing skills in various magical disciplines.</description></item><item><title>The Nameless: Slay Dragon</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-nameless-slay-dragon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-nameless-slay-dragon/</guid><description>Game Description The Nameless: Slay Dragon is a turn-based role-playing adventure game that immerses gamers in a world of strategic combat and deep storytelling. In the center is a young protagonist who must take revenge on a powerful dragon. Users will have to go through a series of battles and clashes, each of which requires careful planning and tactical execution. The title emphasizes the importance of choice; every decision can change the course of the plot.</description></item><item><title>Class of '09: The Flip Side</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/class-of-09-the-flip-side/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/class-of-09-the-flip-side/</guid><description>Game Description Class of &amp;lsquo;09: The Flip Side is the final chapter of the visual novel series that follows the characters&amp;rsquo; lives as they navigate their post-high school struggles. This installment puts the spotlight on Jack, a character who was previously seen in a supporting role. The adventure focuses on her experiences and the emotional difficulties she faces, which contrasts with the more light-hearted approach of the previous protagonist, Nicole. The narrative structure of Class of &amp;lsquo;09: The Flip Side allows gamers to make choices that affect the storyline and offers multiple endings depending on the decisions made.</description></item><item><title>Ace Attorney Investigations Collection</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ace-attorney-investigations-collection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ace-attorney-investigations-collection/</guid><description>Game Description Ace Attorney Investigations Collection, a collection of two games featuring the famous prosecutor Miles Edgeworth, invites users to step into his shoes and go on an exciting investigation. Unlike the courtroom drama of the original series, this collection focuses on the detective work that precedes the trial. Gamers will have to collect evidence, interview witnesses and solve intricate mysteries using logical deduction. The collection includes various quality of life improvements to make gameplay more enjoyable.</description></item><item><title>Kamikaze Lasplanes</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/kamikaze-lassplanes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/kamikaze-lassplanes/</guid><description>Game Description Kamikaze Lassplanes is a visual novel that combines the plot of a novel with the action of a shoot-&amp;lsquo;em-up game. Set in a steampunk world, the dramatic storyline involves two powerful weapons, Lassplanes, and two girls who become them. Gamers navigate a war-torn kingdom and make choices that affect not only the fate of the kingdom, but also their own hearts.
The project introduces Alba Trosset and Hannah Brandenburg, two girls who transform into deadly warplanes.</description></item><item><title>LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild-</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</guid><description>Game Description LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild- is a narrative-driven adventure game that explores the intersection of virtual reality and human connection. The story centers on T-BIT, a high school student and exceptional gamer who finds himself in a mysterious virtual space known as the Moon World. Here he encounters an AI avatar named LUNAR-Q, who is the mascot of the lunar exploration project. The adventure focuses on the developing relationship between T-BIT and LUNAR-Q as they overcome the difficulties of the Lunar World.</description></item><item><title>Everlasting Flowers - Where there is a will, there is a way</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/everlasting-flowers-where-there-is-a-will-there-is-a-way/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/everlasting-flowers-where-there-is-a-will-there-is-a-way/</guid><description>Game Description Everlasting Flowers - Where there is a will, there is a way is a story about two young women. Studio SPRITE created this cinematic romance. Mina, a loner, withdraws from the world. School becomes a battlefield for her. Her hideout? A room filled with dried flowers. Captive of her thoughts, she wanders through endless days. Meanwhile, Ran, born into wealth, discovers the emptiness beneath the gilded cage. Her perfect life is falling apart.</description></item><item><title>Wild West Dynasty</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/wild-west-dynasty/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/wild-west-dynasty/</guid><description>Game Description Wild West Dynasty takes place in 1800s America. The player&amp;rsquo;s task is to build his own ranch, providing himself with wealth and food. Over time, other settlers, workers and friends will join the main character. Each minor character has their own qualities, characteristics and mannerisms. Many of them will turn out to be bandits, and only the gamer can decide who is sent to the gallows.
Having become determined, the central character set out to build a Wild West dynasty, moving further across the Pacific region of America.</description></item><item><title>Sunset Hills</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sunset-hills/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sunset-hills/</guid><description>Game Description Sunset Hills plays out like a hand-drawn narrative puzzle game in the style of a novel. Nico, a writer, travels by rail through the post-war world. Here users play the role of Niko, visiting former comrades in different cities. Users encounter a variety of characters and events as they unravel Niko&amp;rsquo;s life story through clever puzzles. The world is a serene Victorian landscape. Tall buildings contrast with vast open spaces.</description></item><item><title>Who is Abby</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/who-is-abby/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/who-is-abby/</guid><description>Game Description Who is Abby begins with Tom, a man determined to find his missing sister. The title immerses users in an intense psychological thriller where mystery and exploration go hand in hand. With every step, Tom plunges deeper into the mystery of Abby&amp;rsquo;s disappearance, revealing a story shrouded in mystery and darkness. As you take on the role of Tom, the journey becomes personal, with each discovery adding another piece to the puzzle of Abby&amp;rsquo;s life.</description></item><item><title>Harmless Lies</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/harmless-lies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/harmless-lies/</guid><description>Game Description Harmless Lies invites you to immerse yourself in an intense story where the consequences of one careless word become irreversible. The story revolves around the idea of ​​how a small lie, told with the best intentions, sets off a chain of devastating events. The protagonist finds himself trapped by circumstance, forced to weave an increasingly complex web of deception to hide the original untruth. The atmosphere of constant psychological pressure forces you to carefully weigh every decision, because it can lead to a completely unpredictable ending and radically change relationships with other characters.</description></item><item><title>The Rainman</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-rainman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-rainman/</guid><description>Game Description The Rainman takes place in the small town of Crystalpine Grove, where tranquility once reigned. However, the city has recently been gripped by a series of chilling murders, all of which point to a mysterious killer known only as Rain Man. He attacks when it rains, hiding in the shadows and leaving a trail of violence and fear. Local authorities are baffled, and residents are left wondering who the next victim will be.</description></item><item><title>Chains of Judgment</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/chains-of-judgment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/chains-of-judgment/</guid><description>Game Description Chains of Judgment is a dark detective story set against the backdrop of a series of brutal crimes. The city is rocked by the so-called Chain Murders, where each victim is found shackled with a mysterious symbol carved into their skin. The investigation becomes more complicated for homicide veteran Ralph when, at the epicenter of these events, his best friend and partner Nathan, with whom he worked for 5 years, disappears without a trace.</description></item><item><title>1000xRESIST</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/1000xresist/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/1000xresist/</guid><description>Game Description 1000xRESIST is a unique interactive adventure that will take you on a journey through time and space. You will be able to explore different eras and places, meet personalities and learn their stories, look at the past and future through the eyes of the game&amp;rsquo;s heroes. However, do not forget that this world is not a place for weaklings. You will have to make difficult decisions that will affect the fate of not only your heroine, but also future generations.</description></item><item><title>The Hungry Lamb: Traveling in the Late Ming Dynasty</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-hungry-lamb-traveling-in-the-late-ming-dynasty/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-hungry-lamb-traveling-in-the-late-ming-dynasty/</guid><description>Game Description The Hungry Lamb: Traveling in the Late Ming Dynasty is a visual novel set in China during the turbulent reign of the Chongzhen Emperor. Players take on the role of Liang, a former merchant turned bandit tasked with escorting four girls to the prosperous city of Luoyang. The journey is fraught with danger and moral problems. Liang struggles with the truth behind his mission when one of the girls, Sui, reveals a terrifying secret: their goal is not a luxurious life, but an encounter with a monstrous pig demon.</description></item><item><title>Altushka for skufa</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/altushka-dlja-skufa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/altushka-dlja-skufa/</guid><description>Game Description In the gameAltushka for skufa the state provides a tart for skufa through a special service using personal data. For men who have reached forty years of age, do not have a wife and have a stable outlook on life, the project provides the opportunity to receive a legal altushka through the online service Skufuslugi, using the password from your account.
The game is an immersive first-person scoof simulator created by comic artist Vitaly Terletsky and the author of viral anime videos RIKANI in a short time.</description></item><item><title>OUTMINER</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/outminer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/outminer/</guid><description>Game Description OUTMINER is a survival story where, after a spaceship crashes on a hostile and uncharted planet, all responsibility for the fate of the crew falls on the shoulders of the captain. In a harsh and ruthless environment, the protagonist will have to lead his team, fighting for each new day. The fate of all crew members rests entirely with his decisions and ability to adapt to the deadly threats of this lost world.</description></item><item><title>Gensokyo Odyssey</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/gensokyo-odyssey/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/gensokyo-odyssey/</guid><description>Game Description In Gensokyo Odyssey, after a typical school trip takes a detour, you find yourself in the mystical land of Gensokyo, armed only with an air hockey stick. You&amp;rsquo;re immediately thrown into a world filled with strange creatures and quirky characters like Reimu and Marisa who might need your help - although they&amp;rsquo;re not entirely sure why you&amp;rsquo;re here in the first place. The humor never leaves you indifferent as you find yourself in unpredictable situations, trying to figure out what to do next.</description></item><item><title>Knowledge, or know Lady</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/knowledge-or-know-lady/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/knowledge-or-know-lady/</guid><description>Game Description Knowledge, or know Lady throws you into the heart of a unique dating simulator. As the only guy at an all-girl university, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself caught up in a whirlwind of romance and college life. Will you succumb to the charms of the beauties around you or forge your own path to become a campus legend? Ladies School Prince unfolds through your eyes, offering a first-person perspective. Your</description></item><item><title>Touhou Danmaku Kagura Phantasia Lost</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/touhou-danmaku-kagura-phantasia-lost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/touhou-danmaku-kagura-phantasia-lost/</guid><description>Game Description Touhou Danmaku Kagura Phantasia Lost is a rhythm -game built on the foundation of his predecessor. Two different rhythm games have to be passed: traditional and innovative. In Kagura, players check their skills in repulsing the fingers of notes, sequentially hitting six paths. Combinations accumulate with each successful press, which leads to high points. This mode presents more than 160 popular arrangements at four levels of complexity, which will allow you to cope with the task of both beginners and experienced rhythm veterans.</description></item><item><title>Sovereign Syndicate</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sovereign-syndicate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sovereign-syndicate/</guid><description>Game Description The steampunk setting of Sovereign Syndicate features a story set in the alleys of Victorian London. Gamers will have to immerse themselves in a role-playing adventure game where they need to control a character while moving along an isometric map with a top-down view. At the start, players will choose one character to play through the story campaign. You have to pump up and improve the hero, gaining experience for completing quests or destroying opponents in combat situations.</description></item><item><title>KinitoPET</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/kinitopet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/kinitopet/</guid><description>Game Description KinitoPET promises a world of endless fun and communication with your virtual assistant Kinito. This early 2000s wonder can walk, talk, browse, adapt, and play games, making him a friend like no other. But beneath the surface of this seemingly perfect companion lies a disturbing truth. Step into &amp;ldquo;Eternal Fun!&amp;rdquo;, and Kinito will become your personal assistant, ready to fulfill your every request. Its cutting-edge technology promises a &amp;ldquo;truly unique experience&amp;rdquo; designed just for you.</description></item><item><title>Winter Memories</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/winter-memories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/winter-memories/</guid><description>Game Description Winter Memories invites players to once again join Yui, Rio and Miyuki, the trio who created unforgettable summer moments just six months ago. As the seasons change and the snow melts, a new chapter opens in your story. Rediscover a serene coastal village and reconnect with loved ones during this cold season. The past gives rise to the present, but what new experiences await you this winter?
Winter Memories is the sequel to the 2020 game Summer Memories, developed by Dojin Otome.</description></item><item><title>Higurashi whether They Cry Hou+</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/higurashi-when-they-cry-hou/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/higurashi-when-they-cry-hou/</guid><description>Game Description Higurashi When They Cry Hou+ is the final part of its franchise, representing 4 new chapters for playing players. The people who were in the grip of Hinamidzava are now exempted from fate, which riveted them to the repeating events of June 1983. Despite this permission, the story of the region is not completed, and this project proposes to explore many previously hidden worlds.
The narrative Higurashi When They Cry Hou+ departs from the established secret, representing alternative scenarios full of both psychological stress and unexpected humor.</description></item><item><title>Black Lily's Tale</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/black-lilys-tale/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/black-lilys-tale/</guid><description>Game Description Black Lily&amp;rsquo;s Tale is a story about feelings torn apart by the noose of tragedy. The story revolves around a girl whose love for another student on the eve of graduation turns into a series of bitter events. The early black lily&amp;rsquo;s curse forces her to experience misfortunes over and over again, testing her pure intentions. The only way to break this vicious circle is to directly intervene in the narrative fabric, changing the intended course of things.</description></item><item><title>Slay the Princess</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/slay-the-princess/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/slay-the-princess/</guid><description>Game Description Slay the Princess is a dark and daring adventure that will put your skills to the ultimate test, combining the genres of psychological horror and dating simulator. Your mission is simple: kill the princess and save the world from destruction. But don&amp;rsquo;t be fooled by her charms and promises. She will stop at nothing to stop you from completing your task. Make your way through the dense forest and find the hut at the end of the path.</description></item><item><title>VIDEOVERSE</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/videoverse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/videoverse/</guid><description>Game Description VIDEOVERSE invites gamers into a nostalgic digital realm that echoes the early days of online social networking. Set in the fictional online community Videoverse, it follows Emmett, a young gamer and aspiring artist. Gamers navigate a landscape rich with interactions, choices, and character development that are central to the unfolding narrative. Emmett&amp;rsquo;s journey isn&amp;rsquo;t just a game; it explores the intricacies of friendship and the weight of decisions. Each choice can lead to different consequences, allowing users to shape the story in different ways.</description></item><item><title>Stonks-9800: Stock Market Simulator</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/stonks-9800-stock-market-simulator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/stonks-9800-stock-market-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Stonks-9800: Stock Market Simulator immerses gamers into the dynamic landscape of the Japanese stock market of the 1980-1990s. This era, marked by quick economic changes, serves as a background for the game in which strategy and financial management are mixed. Users are in place of a businessman, where each decision made can lead to potential wealth or destructive losses. The Title is a complex web of opportunities, encouraging users to buy and sell shares, carefully monitoring the constantly changing market prices.</description></item><item><title>The Bookwalker: Thief of Tales</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-bookwalker-thief-of-tales/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-bookwalker-thief-of-tales/</guid><description>Game Description The Bookwalker: Thief of Tales invites players to take on the persona of a book traveler. He is a thief whose special ability is to immerse himself in the worlds of books. In his interpretation, they look like dreams, but at the same time they are completely material. Due to this, the hero can take things directly from dreams and drag them into the real world, which is his main task.</description></item><item><title>Staffer Case: A Supernatural Mystery Adventure</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/staffer-case-a-supernatural-mystery-adventure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/staffer-case-a-supernatural-mystery-adventure/</guid><description>Game Description Staffer Case: A Supernatural Mystery Adventure is a supernatural mystery adventure set in a fictional London in the 1960s, where people with unique skills, known as staffers, find themselves at the center of increasingly strange incidents. The user will have to take the place of Notrik, a detective from the Mana affairs department, who is tasked with unraveling a series of crimes. Unlike ordinary criminal investigations, this title requires a different approach.</description></item><item><title>Volcano Princess</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/volcano-princess/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/volcano-princess/</guid><description>Game Description Volcano Princess is a charming RPG that puts you in the role of a single parent raising a daughter in a kingdom blessed by a powerful goddess. But your daughter&amp;rsquo;s fate is in your hands, and you must make the right choices to prepare her for her future role as the country&amp;rsquo;s next monarch. After your wife left, you became the sole guardian of your child. Now you need to provide her with everything she needs to be happy and successful in school and everyday life.</description></item><item><title>The Wreck</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-wreck/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-wreck/</guid><description>Game Description The adventures in The Wreck follow the life of a failed screenwriter named Junon as she tries to cope with the challenges of adulthood. Players will follow a 36-year-old woman who experiences a turning point that derails her aspirations, career, and personal life. The game is a 3D visual novel that will showcase a melancholy story about sisterhood, motherhood, grief and survival in a cruel world.
The storyline in The Wreck will develop gradually through episodes that immerse the protagonist in the past.</description></item><item><title>Mato Anomalies</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mato-anomalies/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mato-anomalies/</guid><description>Game Description Mato Anomalies takes players to Mato. This is the name of the ancient neo-futuristic city. According to the plot, strange incidents began to occur in this metropolis. Several factions are involved in them. And the settlement began to be threatened by demonic creatures. The story follows the adventures of private detective Doe and an exorcist named Graham. They investigate unusual incidents, battle demons in the rifts between worlds, and try to save a populated area from destruction.</description></item><item><title>Looking Up I See Only A Ceiling</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/looking-up-i-see-only-a-ceiling/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/looking-up-i-see-only-a-ceiling/</guid><description>Game Description Looking Up I See Only A Ceiling is a short but thought-provoking psychological visual novel that explores the difficult life of a student. The action takes place in hand-recreated locations, and unique characters immerse you in the seemingly measured world of textbooks and routine study. As they progress, players will have to make difficult choices that can change the fate of the main character forever. The plot revolves around the concept of reaching the &amp;ldquo;point of no return&amp;rdquo;, a critical moment that can make or break the protagonist&amp;rsquo;s life.</description></item><item><title>SAMURAI MAIDEN</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/samurai-maiden/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/samurai-maiden/</guid><description>Game Description SAMURAI MAIDEN may be of interest to fans of isekai and yuri anime. This game takes place in Japan. The plot takes Tsumugi, who is passionate about fencing, from the modern 21st century to the Sengoku era. She must destroy the Demon Lord, who was sealed by her ancestor many centuries ago. Someone came into the distant past to unseal this creature and seize its power. Also, 3 ninja girls from different worlds went there.</description></item><item><title>Monochrome Mobius: Rights and Wrongs Forgotten</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/monochrome-mobius-rights-and-wrongs-forgotten/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/monochrome-mobius-rights-and-wrongs-forgotten/</guid><description>Game Description Monochrome Mobius: Rights and Wrongs Forgotten is an opportunity to immerse yourself in rich fantasy adventures, where gamers get to enjoy the gameplay mechanics of classic JRPGs. Players will travel through the small province of Ennakamuy, which is located on the border with the Yamato Empire. The protagonist lives an ordinary life until he becomes forced to investigate a mysterious violation. The guy eventually meets the girl and learns more details about the events taking place in the world.</description></item><item><title>The Exorcist's Story</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-exorcists-story/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-exorcists-story/</guid><description>Game Description The Exorcist&amp;rsquo;s Story is an atmospheric 2D adventure game in which you will find yourself in the shoes of a young priest, Antonio, who had experience in performing exorcism rituals. But one day everything went wrong and a girl died during the ceremony. You escaped prison, but you promised yourself never to perform such rituals again. But a few years later, strange things begin to happen in your small town and Asmodeus, the demon you once encountered, challenges you again.</description></item><item><title>Persona 5 Royal</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/persona-5-royal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/persona-5-royal/</guid><description>Game Description Persona 5 Royal is the official expansion for the fifth part of the Japanese role-playing video game of the same name, which contains even more unique personas, as well as a lot of interesting quests and items. The plot centers on a seemingly ordinary high school student who goes with his family to Tokyo, where he enrolls in a new school. Soon the main character begins to see inexplicable dreams, in which someone tells the guy that a monstrous catastrophe will befall him in the near future.</description></item><item><title>Mirror 2: Project X</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mirror-2-project-x/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mirror-2-project-x/</guid><description>Game Description Mirror 2: Project X follows the adventures of Dinkudin Naoto, who collaborates with the FBI (Federal Bureau of Research and Conservation). The hero searches for mystical manifestations and otherworldly creatures that sometimes appear in the world. The plot begins with a story with a Demon that infects the body of one of the victims. During the proceedings and investigation of the case, the protagonist will find out the motivations and goals of the creatures in order to make a choice to support or destroy the monster.</description></item><item><title>Milk outside a bag of milk outside a bag of milk</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/milk-outside-a-bag-of-milk-outside-a-bag-of-milk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/milk-outside-a-bag-of-milk-outside-a-bag-of-milk/</guid><description>Game Description The narrative adventureMilk outside a bag of milk outside a bag of mil continues the story of the previous part. The player finds himself in a crazy and mysterious world filled with different combinations of unusual colors and surreal events. On a new journey, you will again have to help the young girl become a little happier. Initially she will be terrified, but as she progresses she will meet new people and realize her own dreams.</description></item><item><title>Kathy Rain: Director's Cut</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/kathy-rain-directors-cut/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/kathy-rain-directors-cut/</guid><description>Game Description Kathy Rain: Director&amp;rsquo;s Cut is an expanded version of the original project, in the center of which Kathy Rain finds herself on a deadly and interesting adventure. The gameplay has undergone many changes, and innovations have also appeared. The story has been expanded, many locations and new puzzles with previously non-existent mechanics and objects for interaction have been added.
The event takes place in the 1990s. The game is a rethinking of a standard project released back in 2016.</description></item><item><title>Ancient Life</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ancient-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ancient-life/</guid><description>Game Description Ancient Life is a simulator in which the main goal is to live an eventful life in the vastness of ancient China, where the ending of one generation serves as the starting point for a new one. The project invites you to immerse yourself in a detailed reconstruction of the era, offering a wide range of activities from farming and handicrafts to hunting or a career as a government official.</description></item><item><title>Doki Doki Literature Club Plus!</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/doki-doki-literature-club-plus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/doki-doki-literature-club-plus/</guid><description>Game Description Doki Doki Literature Club Plus! is a visual novel, the plot tells the story of a student who joins a literature club. Most of the passage is focused on interactions with the girls who are part of the team. The gameplay is similar to other projects in this genre. The player gets few interactive moments. Only occasionally do elections appear that significantly affect the further passage.
The scenes in Doki Doki consist of static 2D images with drawn anime characters.</description></item><item><title>MAMIYA A Shared Illusion of the World's End</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mamiya-a-shared-illusion-of-the-worlds-end/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mamiya-a-shared-illusion-of-the-worlds-end/</guid><description>Game Description MAMIYA A Shared Illusion of the World&amp;rsquo;s End takes you to a post-apocalyptic world in which a small group of surviving guys find themselves. The universe is dying due to a strange and unexplored anomaly that is affecting humanity on the surface of the planet. The guys have to survive and look for ways to cope with problems that are caused by existential fears about the future and their demise.</description></item><item><title>Tiny Bunny</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tiny-bunny/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tiny-bunny/</guid><description>Game Description Tiny Bunny is a black and white visual novel containing a considerable amount of horror and sappress. Get lost in the forest, in no case can you hear his voice, otherwise death will follow. The events of the game occur in winter. Something follows you and constantly walks between the trees. There are rumors about constant screams from the forest, and the board with the losses of children is replenished each time.</description></item><item><title>Asdivine Cross</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/asdivine-cross/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/asdivine-cross/</guid><description>Game Description Asdivine Cross is a Japanese role-playing game with 2D anime-style pixel graphics. The project was ported to computers from smartphones. In the PC version, the developers adapted the controls for a keyboard and mouse and added an achievement system. The title emulates an old school JRPG. In keeping with the tradition of the genre, this video game features random encounters and turn-based combat. The order of moves of all participants in the battle is displayed on the screen, and you can influence it.</description></item><item><title>Firework</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/firework/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/firework/</guid><description>Game Description The dark journey of the boy inFirework allows gamers to find themselves in dangerous environments where they must survive and solve difficult puzzles. The game presents the opportunity to go investigate a mysterious fire that killed many people. The main character, named Lin Lixun, goes to explore the territory where the disaster occurred. In the process of clarifying the circumstances, the young policeman is forced to deal with mysterious phenomena and confusing facts that overlap with each other.</description></item><item><title>Monster Prom 2: Monster Camp</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/monster-prom-2-monster-camp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/monster-prom-2-monster-camp/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Prom 2: Monster Camp is a multi -user dite simulator, the actions of which take place in the monsters camp. The game is replete with charismatic characters and black humor. The events of the game are transferred to the summer camp, where teenagers rest before the start of the new school year. Among the characters, both old heroes and many new ones are represented: Damien, Calcelter, Milo, Dalia, Joy and Arab.</description></item><item><title>Matsuro Palette</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/matsuro-palette/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/matsuro-palette/</guid><description>Game Description Matsuro Palette is based on survival and mystery, in which gamers find themselves locked in a studio with a cursed painting. The story unfolds over seven days, during which the protagonist must navigate the complex and disturbing world created by the girl&amp;rsquo;s painting. To survive, the user must carefully paint her portrait, using notes left by previous victims as clues. However, there is a constant threat: if you anger the girl depicted in the painting, it can lead to fatal consequences.</description></item><item><title>Milk inside a bag of milk inside a bag of milk</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/milk-inside-a-bag-of-milk-inside-a-bag-of-milk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/milk-inside-a-bag-of-milk-inside-a-bag-of-milk/</guid><description>Game Description Milk inside a bag of milk inside a bag of milk is a short visual novel with a deep message and unusual execution, made by the efforts of one developer, one of the indie creators. The visual design of the single-player campaign, which is the only game mode, is made using only two colors - purple and black. For completing a short story, which will take about 15 minutes, the developer has prepared three rewards, implementing a small list of achievements.</description></item><item><title>ATRI -My Dear Moments-</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/atri-my-dear-moments/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/atri-my-dear-moments/</guid><description>Game Description ATRI -My Dear Moments- is a visual novel with a well-developed plot that leaves food for thought after completing the single-player campaign. Casual control is carried out using the keys on the mouse, allowing you to enjoy reading a work with anime-style slides even for people who are not familiar with games. Recognized masters of this genre worked on the story, which allowed the project to receive many prestigious awards and the love of an audience that loves visual novels.</description></item><item><title>Persona 4 Golden</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/persona-4-golden/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/persona-4-golden/</guid><description>Game Description Persona 4 Golden is a role-playing game about a group of friends who are able to summon demons from the other world. To do this, it is enough to shoot yourself in the temple. The events take place in the small Japanese town of Inaba. The children in Persona 4 are teenagers going through puberty. The heroes are investigating a mysterious series of murders.
The gameplay of Persona 4 Golden contains elements of a visual novel.</description></item><item><title>The Test</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-test/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-test/</guid><description>Game Description The Test is a psychological horror with elements of a visual novel, role-playing adventure, and immersive sim with a lot of text monologues inside the protagonist&amp;rsquo;s head. The player gets the opportunity to directly influence what is happening using a decision-making system of varying degrees of importance. The isometric camera allows you to get the best view of the two-dimensional space where all the action of the single-player campaign takes place with a well-developed plot about mental suffering.</description></item><item><title>Senren＊Banka</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/senrenbanka/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/senrenbanka/</guid><description>Game Description Senren＊Banka is primarily aimed at anime fans. The project uses the appropriate style (including chibi art) and Japanese voice acting. The plot combines romantic, tragic, mystical and humorous elements. The story revolves around supernatural incidents. A group of young people are trying to hide them from ordinary people.
The premise in Senren＊Banka: A Thousand Colors of Love is as follows. A guy named Arichi Masaomi comes to the provincial town of Hoori in the summer.</description></item><item><title>some convenience store</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/some-some-convenience-store/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/some-some-convenience-store/</guid><description>Game Description some some convenience store is a visual novel with a lot of sexual content related to naked female bodies, which quite often flash on the monitor screen. The user finds himself in a kind of dating simulator in an alternative reality, playing the role of a simple guy working as a half-time senior salesman in a small grocery store. The goal of the project from indie developers is to establish a relationship with a representative of the fair sex, choosing a companion to your liking from the proposed options and achieving her favor.</description></item><item><title>Disco Elysium: The Final Cut</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/disco-elysium-the-final-cut/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/disco-elysium-the-final-cut/</guid><description>Game Description Disco Elysium is an RPG in which a detective must use his skills to conduct a unique investigation. The player will have to interrogate well-developed characters, investigate murders, and, if desired, take bribes. You can become either the savior of the city or the worst disaster for all humanity. Game Features: Unique branched dialogue system. Wide freedom of choice both in the story narrative and in additional tasks. Well-developed characters with their own stories and personalities.</description></item><item><title>Trinoline All Ages Version</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/trinoline-all-ages-version/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/trinoline-all-ages-version/</guid><description>Game Description Trinoline tells the story of a world where humans and androids live together. The main character&amp;rsquo;s name is Shun Nanami. He lost his sister named Shirone under tragic circumstances and now suffers for years due to the accident. One day he comes home and meets a girl in his home who is exactly like his deceased relative. It soon turns out that her memories and appearance were transferred to the robot.</description></item><item><title>Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney Trilogy</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/phoenix-wright-ace-attorney-trilogy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/phoenix-wright-ace-attorney-trilogy/</guid><description>Game Description Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney Trilogy is a re-release of three parts of lawyer simulators combined with adventure. Here the player will not only defend a person in court, but will also begin to investigate the circumstances of the crime, exploring the place, finding evidence, interrogating witnesses. At the trial, the user will listen to both sides, question, look for contradictions in their words, using found objects. The lawyer will be able to defend himself, even if there is only one piece of evidence proving the innocence of the accused, and will also delay time to collect more information.</description></item><item><title>ISLAND</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/island/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/island/</guid><description>Game Description ISLAND is an intricate adventure story, made in the visual novel genre with elements of a role-playing game, expressed in the non-linearity of the passage due to the choice of lines in dialogues and the possibility of playing a protagonist with different characters. The project has a huge number of endings and routes along which you can get to them. The gamer receives a sufficient number of hints on the way to completing the passage so as not to get confused in the intricacies of the storylines.</description></item><item><title>Monster Prom</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/monster-prom/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/monster-prom/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Prom is a humorous date simulator that includes mature topics, abusive words and obscene scenarios. The plot tells the gamer that he has 3 weeks left before the graduation evening, that the hero is a monster and still has not found a couple. But this is in the order of things, as many of the school have similar problems.
Take part in a single game or cooperative mode up to 4 participants.</description></item><item><title>Mirror</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mirror/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mirror/</guid><description>Game Description Mirror is a visual novel that perfectly combines erotic content, an RPG component, an interactive plot and battles in which you take a direct part. The whole game is built on the “three in a row” principle. In the casual combination of characters, you will only take part in the battle on the Match 3 battlefield. That is, you will win if you can score more points. The game features three heroines who will oppose you throughout the game.</description></item><item><title>Seabed</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/seabed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/seabed/</guid><description>Game Description Seabed detective visual novel is revealed through the anime drawing and elements of Yuri, showing the relationship between two cute girls. Players will direct the development of the plot line with the adopted elections, observing the events. We’ll have to look at the world through the prism of the views of three characters that are faced with the problems of illusory dreams and the reality of adult life, which every mature person meets in one way or another.</description></item><item><title>STEINS;GATE</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/steinsgate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/steinsgate/</guid><description>Game Description STEINS;GATE is a visual novel made in an anime style, which is reflected in the appearance of the characters in the single-player campaign. The game received a lot of positive reviews due to its deep dramatic plot, which is not often found in the video game entertainment industry. The narrative is filled with sad moments that touch the soul and make you empathize with the main characters, who are trying to save all of humanity, while paying a terrible price.</description></item><item><title>VA-11 Hall-A: Cyberpunk Bartender Action</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/va-11-hall-a-cyberpunk-bartender-action/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/va-11-hall-a-cyberpunk-bartender-action/</guid><description>Game Description VA-11 Hall-A: Cyberpunk Bartender Action is an adventure simulator of a bartender in the setting of a dystopian future, where humanity finds itself under the control of huge corporations dictating the rules of life, and nanorobots controlling every area of ​​human activity and the implementation of laws and regulations adopted new world government. Stylistically, this project refers to Japanese games of the last century. The gameplay consists of communicating with bar visitors and providing them with high-quality service in order to build warm, friendly relationships with them.</description></item><item><title>The Wolf Among Us</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-wolf-among-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-wolf-among-us/</guid><description>Game Description The Wolf Among Us is an episodic graphic novel based on the Fable comics series created by Bill Willingham. The game&amp;rsquo;s plot acts as a prequel to the main story. The game is divided into 5 episodes, where every decision made by the player has a consequence and affects the overall one. history.
The gameplay is point-and-click, but some sections contain action and fights, which are QTE scenes. All the characters presented in the game are heroes of famous fairy tales, who, with the help of spells, can exist in the world of people or “Simps”, as they are called here.</description></item><item><title>CLANNAD</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/clannad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/clannad/</guid><description>Game Description CLANNAD is a visual novel in anime style. The story follows a second grade student who begins a new school year at Hikarizaka School. On his way to school, he meets a girl, Nagisa. It turns out that she is constantly alone and has no friends at all. Depending on the actions you take, the course of the story changes. By helping a girl make friends, you build good relationships with some characters, but at the same time spoil them with others.</description></item><item><title>Atomic OWL</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/atomic-owl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/atomic-owl/</guid><description>Game Description Atomic OWL puts the player in the role of Idalgo Bladywing, a bird who went to save his comrades. The main conflict is tied to the confrontation with the sorcerer-Voron Omega Vinc, who by force subjugated his entire troupe. The plot starts 2 years after this incident that happened during the return of the detachment to Ramennaya. Idalgo begins a campaign to correct the deed, and a daring speaking blade helps him in this.</description></item><item><title>GODSOUL</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/godsoul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/godsoul/</guid><description>Game Description Gamers in GODSOUL will be immersed in a cyberpunk atmosphere mixed with mythological creatures. The game is a card battler with elements of a role-playing visual novel, where the events taking place are demonstrated in the form of drawn anime art. Users will have to take control of rebel girls who have the power of the “Divine Soul,” which allows them to travel through different spaces. Players will be able to connect souls that resonate with each other to awaken God and deal with evil.</description></item><item><title>Killer Chat! - Expanded Edition</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/killer-chat-expanded-edition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/killer-chat-expanded-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Killer Chat! - Expanded Edition - a dating simulator that plunges you into a deadly adventure, where the price of a mistake is your own life. The main character, being a reporter and aspiring writer, is forced to pose as a maniac in a closed online chat for six months. This risky game has a dual goal: to collect exclusive material for a future crime novel and not to become another victim of your new acquaintances.</description></item><item><title>Zero Escape: The Nonary Games</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/zero-escape-the-nonary-games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/zero-escape-the-nonary-games/</guid><description>Game Description Zero Escape: The Nonary Games is a collection of high -resolution visual novels developed by Spike Chunsoft. The mysterious plot involves us in the role of one of the nine abducted people and play the game on the stake of which life is standing.
The game has undergone updates and is now equipped with high graphics, more modern intuitive controls, as well as many new functions, including Japanese and English voice acting!</description></item></channel></rss>