<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Racing on Game Vibe</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/tags/racing/</link><description>Recent content in Racing on Game Vibe</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://game-vibe.github.io/tags/racing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Street Racer Collection (QUByte Classics)</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/street-racer-collection-qubyte-classics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/street-racer-collection-qubyte-classics/</guid><description>Game Description Street Racer Collection (QUByte Classics) is a hybrid of arcade racing and combat competitions, where reaching the finish line is just one part of success. The main way to interact with opponents is not just overtaking, but direct physical elimination using special techniques. You can control a dozen colorful pilots, each of whom has a vehicle with unique attack capabilities. Competitions take place on routes full of dangers, running through both recognizable landmarks and completely fantastic areas.</description></item><item><title>Project Motor Racing</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/project-motor-racing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/project-motor-racing/</guid><description>Game Description Project Motor Racing is a full-time career in the world of professional motorsport where your path to glory involves managing budgets, negotiating sponsorship deals and taking responsibility for the consequences of accidents. Every decision made both on and off the track directly affects the path to the top of the racing Olympus. The project asks you to face the harsh reality of professional racing, where one incident can ruin both the car and your entire career.</description></item><item><title>Speed ​​Demons 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/speed-demons-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/speed-demons-2/</guid><description>Game Description Speed ​​Demons 2 is an arcade road racing game that focuses on explosive action and all-out destruction. The project offers hundreds of races, distributed across numerous chapters. A total of 10 modes are available, ranging from classic competitions with rivals to missions where the main goal is to destroy as many vehicles as possible within the allotted time. Moreover, each race is designed for quick sessions and is completed on average in 2-4 minutes, maintaining a high pace of what is happening.</description></item><item><title>Christmas Story</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/christmas-story/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/christmas-story/</guid><description>Game Description Christmas Story not only creates a deceptive feeling of festive warmth, but also immerses you in a chilling story where the line between fiction and reality is rapidly blurring. The narrative is transformed under the influence of the actions and choices of the gamer himself, turning a cozy Christmas night into a real nightmare. The symbols of the holiday familiar from childhood take on sinister features, and the crackling of wood in the fireplace gives way to oppressive silence.</description></item><item><title>Long Drive North: Co-Op RV Simulator</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/long-drive-north-co-op-rv-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/long-drive-north-co-op-rv-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Long Drive North: Co-Op RV Simulator is a brutal survival test where an old RV becomes the only refuge in the world after an unknown disaster. This vehicle requires constant attention, forcing gamers to personally repair it, search for spare parts in abandoned buildings and refuel the tank to continue driving. Every bolt found and engine fixed gives a temporary sense of security in the middle of the deserted American wilderness.</description></item><item><title>Driving Life</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/driving-life/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/driving-life/</guid><description>Game Description Driving Life is a detailed simulator that offers you to master more than 40 types of transport in the setting of rural America. Players will explore a vast open world of 16 km², where they can not only complete work tasks, but also buy and sell 16 unique houses. Of particular interest is the mechanics of restoring 6 project cars, parts for which are scattered throughout the island. In addition to managing finances, it is necessary to constantly monitor the basic needs of the character: hunger, thirst, sleep and even boredom, which significantly increases the level of immersion in what is happening.</description></item><item><title>SCHROTT</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/schrott/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/schrott/</guid><description>Game Description SCHROTT is a roguelike racing game where performing crazy stunts and collecting valuable loot provide the basis for deep vehicle customization. Instead of ordinary machines, there are absurd designs that lend themselves to all sorts of improvements to wreak even more chaos. Each race turns into a hunt for resources that allow you to turn your car into a unique weapon of destruction on the road. Arcade controls make the gameplay accessible and intuitive from the first minutes, and high-speed action does not let you relax.</description></item><item><title>Assetto Corsa Rally</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa-rally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa-rally/</guid><description>Game Description Assetto Corsa Rally is an uncompromising simulator that challenges drivers to push powerful cars to their limits. Each track, be it the gravel roads of Wales or the asphalt serpentines of Alsace, is recreated using laser scanning technology. This approach made it possible to transfer the real width of roads, the profile of roadsides and all surface irregularities into virtual space with the highest accuracy. Each race turns into a tense test, where the slightest mistake due to the treacherous terrain can become fatal, and success depends on instant decisions and filigree driving techniques.</description></item><item><title>NASCAR 25</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nascar-25/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nascar-25/</guid><description>Game Description NASCAR 25 takes you through the challenging journey from novice to motorsport legend. His career starts in a modest home garage, where he will prepare his first car for races in the ARCA Menards series. Gradually moving up the racing hierarchy, it will be possible to conquer the NASCAR Craftsman Truck Series, Xfinity Series championships and, finally, fight for the main cup. Success depends not only on skill on the track, but also on strategic decisions: hiring personnel, finding sponsors and developing new parts for the car, building its reputation through results and communication with the press.</description></item><item><title>Nitroglycerine!</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nitroglycerine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nitroglycerine/</guid><description>Game Description Nitroglycerine! is a test where the main task is to transport a deadly substance along difficult routes. The process of controlling a heavy tractor is subject to the laws of realistic physics, and the vehicle itself is completely unsuitable for overcoming obstacles along the way. Any mistake in piloting, sharp turn or collision can lead to the detonation of nitroglycerin and instant failure of the mission. Even climbing moderately steep slopes requires precise timing, and putting too much pressure on the engine via turbocharging risks stalling the engine.</description></item><item><title>THRASHER</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/thrasher/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/thrasher/</guid><description>Game Description THRASHER is a psychedelic arcade odyssey where music, visuals and the process itself are woven into a single transcendental stream that immerses you in a state of flow. The journey takes you from primeval darkness to the heights of celestial bliss, culminating in an intense showdown with a cosmic infant deity. Control the magnificent space eel to gracefully glide and dash across stunning alien worlds in a desperate race for survival.</description></item><item><title>Car Factory Empire</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/car-factory-empire/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/car-factory-empire/</guid><description>Game Description Car Factory Empire - testing the effectiveness of self-designed cars takes place on race tracks, where artificial intelligence acts as an opponent. However, success in the races is only part of the global struggle for market dominance. Competitors are actively fighting for control of resource-rich territories and key cities. Providing production capacity with raw materials by capturing mines and factories on the world map becomes a primary task for any aspiring industrialist.</description></item><item><title>Wreckreation</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/wreckreation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/wreckreation/</guid><description>Game Description Users in Wreckreation will enjoy dynamic rides in racing cars, moving across vast locations. You will go out for a ride on unique tracks where there are jumps, twisted road elements and other dangerous tests. The game has a plentiful number of cars to choose from, as well as many locked cars that should be gradually unlocked as you progress through the single-player campaign. Players will have to tune their cars, changing the appearance with paint and body kits, as well as improving driving characteristics with the engine, wheels and other components.</description></item><item><title>Zaccaria Pinball</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/zaccaria-pinball/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/zaccaria-pinball/</guid><description>Game Description Zaccaria Pinball is the digital incarnation of pinball machines, offering an extensive collection of tables divided into several categories. Enthusiasts have access to both classic electro-mechanical (EM) devices, like Nautilus or Universe, and more modern solid-state (SS) versions, including Time Machine and Devil Riders.
In addition to authentic recreations, the project includes completely redesigned tables such as Space Shuttle 2016 and Farfalla 2017, as well as unique themed designs presented in the Award category, where you can find The Mummy and Aliens.</description></item><item><title>Tokyo Xtreme Racer</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tokyo-xtreme-racer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tokyo-xtreme-racer/</guid><description>Game Description Tokyo Xtreme Racer is a racing game set against the backdrop of Tokyo&amp;rsquo;s vibrant underground street racing scene. The game immerses users in a world where speed and skill reign, and the ultimate goal is to defeat your opponents in intense one-on-one battles. Unlike traditional racing games, the title introduces a unique twist where the main goal is not to take first place, but to destroy the opponent&amp;rsquo;s Spirit Points (SP).</description></item><item><title>Formula Legends</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/formula-legends/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/formula-legends/</guid><description>Game Description Racers in Formula Legends have been competing in car races for several decades. The gameplay spans the period from the 1960s to the present day, offering 16 vehicle models based on historical prototypes. Races take place at 14 circuits based on famous racing locations. These tracks are not static, they change over the years and offer fresh challenges in each new era. This journey through time clearly shows the evolution of racing cars and track configurations.</description></item><item><title>FUMES</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/fumes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/fumes/</guid><description>Game Description FUMES plunges you into the heart of a chaotic wasteland world where vehicular combat reigns. Users take control of customizable vehicles, equipping them with weapons and armor to survive the unforgiving desert landscape. The title brings an old-school feel to car combat, drawing on the style of classic rally games with driving mechanics that reflect a time before flashy graphics and complex controls. It&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced, straightforward, and has genuine tension.</description></item><item><title>HOT ROD MAYHEM</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/hot-rod-mayhem/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/hot-rod-mayhem/</guid><description>Game Description Hot Rod Mayhem represents car competitions on many tracks. This racing arcade contains a campaign mode, where to obtain the title of world champion, it is necessary to win in 10 separate championships. Promotion requires special tests with unique tasks that open access to the main events. After unlocking the championship, you can participate in its races so that the player can take first place in the fight against opponents.</description></item><item><title>Assenizator</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/assenizator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/assenizator/</guid><description>Game Description Assenizator plunges into the harsh everyday life of sewage disposal service workers, whose already difficult work is complicated by constant challenges. Partners Petrovich and Mikhalych not only have to deal with their direct responsibilities, but also resist an annoying competitor who is trying to intercept all orders. The situation is aggravated after an incident involving waste dumping into the river, which attracted the attention of law enforcement officers. Now the heroes urgently need to earn money to pay a large fine in order to avoid serious consequences from the law, turning the routine into a struggle for survival.</description></item><item><title>JDM: Japanese Drift Master</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/jdm-japanese-drift-master/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/jdm-japanese-drift-master/</guid><description>Game Description JDM: Japanese Drift Master is a colorful car simulator that will take you into the exciting world of drifting on the streets of Japan. A huge open world with varied landscapes, from serene lakes to bustling city areas, offers endless opportunities for exploration, racing and, of course, the art of drifting itself. What sets the game apart is the freedom it gives players to customize their cars, allowing them to truly make it their own.</description></item><item><title>Bionic Bay</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bionic-bay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bionic-bay/</guid><description>Game Description Bionic Bay is a 2D side-scrolling platformer. The plot tells about the adventures of an ordinary person in an unusual world. The story is told without words or full cut scenes. The game has a dark and mysterious atmosphere. The project is divided into levels. Already completed maps can be replayed. Their selection is available through the main menu. The gameplay is built around unique physics and the hero&amp;rsquo;s ability to change places with certain objects.</description></item><item><title>Used Cars Simulator</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/used-cars-simulator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/used-cars-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description In Used Cars Simulator you will plunge headlong into the world of buying, selling and everything in between. You&amp;rsquo;ll search for cars, from shiny, barely used to salvaged, salvaged ones, trying to estimate their value before they land on your lot. Every decision you make matters - will you sell this car to make a quick buck, or restore it to its former glory to make a bigger profit?</description></item><item><title>STORROR Parkour Pro</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/storror-parkour-pro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/storror-parkour-pro/</guid><description>Game Description STORROR Parkour Pro is a parkour simulator set in the Isle of Dogs, London. Users navigate these urban environments using a set of motor abilities derived from the discipline of parkour. Available actions include jumping, climbing, overcoming obstacles, somersaulting, sliding, swinging and running across rooftops and streets. The character&amp;rsquo;s movement is provided by an animation system that combines motion capture data from parkour athletes with physics calculations to depict dynamics.</description></item><item><title>Drive Beyond Horizons</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/drive-beyond-horizons/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/drive-beyond-horizons/</guid><description>Game Description Drive Beyond Horizons abandons the linear path and throws gamers into a vast, ever-changing world. Buckle up and get ready to explore - procedurally generated landscapes make every game unique. Leave your comfort zone and choose your own route. Travel across vast deserts, lush forests, and any kind of road (or lack thereof). But this is not just a sightseeing trip. Drive Beyond Horizons is fraught with many secrets and difficulties that remain to be unraveled.</description></item><item><title>Sledders</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sledders/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sledders/</guid><description>Game Description Sledders is a snowmobile simulator designed to offer gamers a realistic snowmobiling experience across a variety of terrains. It&amp;rsquo;s clear from the start that the focus is on realism and the thrill of driving through snowy landscapes. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s deep powder or steep slopes, the title offers a range of conditions that simulate real-life snowmobiling. Each ride feels different thanks to the dynamic physics system that controls the sled&amp;rsquo;s movements.</description></item><item><title>Wreckfest 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/wreckfest-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/wreckfest-2/</guid><description>Game Description Wreckfest 2 is a title where there are no prisoners in the all-out destructive derby of high-speed racing without rules. Each collision changes the battlefield, and debris piles up as racers push their battered machines to the limit. Bugbear Entertainment uses its proprietary physics engine to make every crash more dynamic and every wing crush more satisfying. The vehicles are blown apart piece by piece until all that&amp;rsquo;s left is a smoking heap, limping toward the finish line—if it even gets there at all.</description></item><item><title>Motorcycle Night Ride</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/motorcycle-night-ride/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/motorcycle-night-ride/</guid><description>Game Description Motorcycle Night Ride invites gamers to a serene setting of night travel, where the open road becomes an escape from the chaos of everyday life. The title focuses on the pure thrill of driving a motorcycle on endless highways, bathed in the soft light of street lamps and the moon. Users zip through various environments without the pressure of competition or time limits, allowing them to immerse themselves in the atmosphere at their own pace.</description></item><item><title>Grand Theft Auto 5 Enhanced</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/grand-theft-auto-5-enhanced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/grand-theft-auto-5-enhanced/</guid><description>Game Description Grand Theft Auto 5 Enhanced is a significant update for players looking for a new experience from the already classic gameplay. Rockstar Games has turned the popular GTA 5 into a more powerful version aimed at new generation platforms. Gamers will experience improved performance across several technical parameters and significant updates to the core environment.
Los Santos in GTA 5 continues to serve as the backdrop for the narrative, with the three main characters navigating complex crime landscapes.</description></item><item><title>Speedboat Simulator</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/speedboat-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/speedboat-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Speedboat Simulator is a realistic racing simulator where gamers will take control of powerful high-speed boats to participate in water competitions. The main arena for the competition is the picturesque Hawaiian waters, offering many challenging routes. Each available vessel has individual handling and speed parameters, which requires the pilot to constantly adapt his driving style to the specific conditions of the race. Success in racing directly depends on the ability to feel the technique and effectively use its strengths on various sections of the route.</description></item><item><title>Turbo Dismount 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/turbo-dismount-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/turbo-dismount-2/</guid><description>Game Description Turbo Dismount 2 brings a fresh twist to the world of physics-based gaming, offering players a playground of chaos and humor. The game features a wide variety of levels where you can launch your character, Mr. Dismount, and his companions into increasingly wild scenarios. These levels are not limited to traditional racing, but also include stunt tracks and physics puzzles that add unexpected challenges. It&amp;rsquo;s a kind of freedom of action, but that&amp;rsquo;s the beauty of it.</description></item><item><title>Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lonely-mountains-snow-riders/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lonely-mountains-snow-riders/</guid><description>Game Description Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders offers gamers a new look at the snowy slopes. The title takes the core elements of its predecessor and adds new twists, offering users the opportunity to navigate the mountains in both relaxed and competitive modes. The fun begins when you start heading down the slopes, encountering everything from icy lakes to hairpin turns. It&amp;rsquo;s all about finding your rhythm while pushing the boundaries of your skill.</description></item><item><title>My Summer Car</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/my-summer-car/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/my-summer-car/</guid><description>Game Description My Summer Car is a life simulator of a Finnish, a 19-year-old boy who lives in a dacha in picturesque forests. His relatives on vacation in Tenerife, the whole house, and most importantly, garage, at his disposal. Created on Unity, thanks to the flexibility of this engine, and it became possible to add so much mechanic, which are below.
Your main occupation will be the restoration of the ancient Satsuma AMP car made on the basis of a real car - Datsun 100a.</description></item><item><title>4 Rush Together</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/4-rush-together/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/4-rush-together/</guid><description>Game Description 4 Rush Together puts teamwork to the test on a variety of levels designed to challenge and entertain. Here users are tied with a rope and must overcome obstacles, traps and difficult terrain. It is a game that combines competition with the need for cooperation, allowing gamers to either compete with each other or work as a team. The title supports up to four users, which means that you can gather a company for several hours of fun.</description></item><item><title>Winter Games Collection</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/winter-games-collection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/winter-games-collection/</guid><description>Game Description Winter Games Collection brings together a variety of winter-themed titles that will provide exciting entertainment for gamers of all ages. The project offers a variety of entertainment, from exciting snowball fights to exciting ice races, all in a festive winter setting. The combination of arcade style and family fun ensures that the game will be fun, whether you want to enjoy a solo adventure or gather a group of friends for competitive fun.</description></item><item><title>Tricky Madness</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tricky-madness/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tricky-madness/</guid><description>Game Description Tricky Madness is making its way onto the indie gaming scene, promising a wild ride for snowboarding enthusiasts. This adventure game is inspired by classic arcade snowboard games like SSX and 1080, so strap on your virtual board and get ready for some adrenaline-pumping action. The mountain is calling: Buckle up and get ready to fall down the treacherous slopes. This is not just the finish line, it is exploring and overcoming the boundaries of your capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Victory Heat Rally</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/victory-heat-rally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/victory-heat-rally/</guid><description>Game Description Victory Heat Rally is a retro racing game inspired by arcade games of the last century, such as Hang-On and OutRun. You have to take control of small cars to rush along various difficult tracks at high speed. The gameplay is hardcore and pays homage to the classic games of yesteryear.
To fully master the mechanics of Victory Heat Rally, you will need to learn how to glide around the track, take corners correctly, and feel the road.</description></item><item><title>Rally Arcade Classics</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rally-arcade-classics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rally-arcade-classics/</guid><description>Game Description Rally Arcade Classics takes gamers into the heart of rally racing history, bringing classic arcade gaming to the world of motorsports. With 44 cars from four different decades - the 70s, 80s, 90s and 00s - you&amp;rsquo;ll get a look at the cars that helped shape the rally scene. There&amp;rsquo;s a wide variety of iconic cars here, each offering its own set of challenges and driving features. In addition to the impressive list of cars, there are 48 tracks, each designed for a different type of racing.</description></item><item><title>Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/test-drive-unlimited-solar-crown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/test-drive-unlimited-solar-crown/</guid><description>Game Description Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown – restart of a series of arcade racing games. You can feel the vibration of hundreds of horses under the hood with modern graphics and physics. You can choose from top-notch hypercars from legendary manufacturers such as Koenigsegg, Porsche, Dodge, Ferrari, Lamborghini or Bugatti. It is worth understanding that luxury cars will require experience and skills, so you need to open them gradually. Each vehicle can be modified and customized to suit your preferences.</description></item><item><title>Turbo Sliders Unlimited</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/turbo-sliders-unlimited/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/turbo-sliders-unlimited/</guid><description>Game Description Turbo Sliders Unlimited is an opportunity to plunge into racing competitions in multiplayer or single player mode, where users can tune cars. The gameplay is made in the form of arcade races with a top view, where users will compete with racers on various professional tracks. The game has a special editor, which allows you to design your own levels, locations, vehicles and flexibly customize tournament modes.
In the multiplayer &amp;ldquo;Turbo Sliders Unlimited&amp;rdquo; up to 20 people (including observers) can participate simultaneously, which is suitable for creating e-sports tests.</description></item><item><title>LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild-</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lunaria-virtualized-moonchild/</guid><description>Game Description LUNARiA -Virtualized Moonchild- is a narrative-driven adventure game that explores the intersection of virtual reality and human connection. The story centers on T-BIT, a high school student and exceptional gamer who finds himself in a mysterious virtual space known as the Moon World. Here he encounters an AI avatar named LUNAR-Q, who is the mascot of the lunar exploration project. The adventure focuses on the developing relationship between T-BIT and LUNAR-Q as they overcome the difficulties of the Lunar World.</description></item><item><title>CarX Street</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/carx-street/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/carx-street/</guid><description>Game Description TheCarX Street car simulator allows you to build your own car and hit the streets to conquer the whole city. The metropolis is presented on a huge scale, including its surroundings: city streets, industrial area, picturesque highways, etc. CarX Streets features drifting, high-speed chases, heavy traffic and intense competition in online races.
The main feature of the game is the possibility of deep car customization and wide tuning possibilities.</description></item><item><title>Monster Jam Showdown</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/monster-jam-showdown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/monster-jam-showdown/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Jam Showdown is an adrenaline-pumping off-road racing experience that is sure to get your heart racing. Gamers can get behind the wheel of iconic monster trucks and compete in a variety of challenging environments. From dirt tracks to stadiums, the game offers a variety of racing arenas. The project has ten different modes and is designed for users of any level of training. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned veteran or just a new rider, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Supermoves</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/supermoves/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/supermoves/</guid><description>Game Description Supermoves - This parkour party promises wild fun. Users sprint, jump and grind the rails in intense challenges. Bomb Tag, Rising Tide and Royale modes offer different thrills. Up to forty gamers can race, pursue and compete. Makea Games' level editor allows users to create their own experiences. Makeaverse is waiting for you. Everyone can dive in, build and play.
Supermoves combines competition and creativity. Casual players and parkour professionals will find their place.</description></item><item><title>Rent A Car Simulator 24</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rent-a-car-simulator-24/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rent-a-car-simulator-24/</guid><description>Game Description Rent A Car Simulator 24 puts gamers in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat of a start-up car rental business. Starting small, with one car, users are faced with the difficulties of building a prosperous empire. It&amp;rsquo;s a balancing act between growth and maintenance. The basis is the purchase of cars. Users buy cars to expand their fleet. Variety is key: from compact city cars to spacious SUVs, each model attracts its own clientele.</description></item><item><title>Old School Rally</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/old-school-rally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/old-school-rally/</guid><description>Game Description In Old School Rally, users get behind the wheel of fire-breathing rally cars that spit dust and gravel as they make their way through unforgiving landscapes. Forget about fancy bells and whistles - the main thing here is pure, unadulterated driving skill. Racers must think, react quickly and tame their wild stallions in a variety of conditions. Each track throws a unique gauntlet at the gamer. One moment you might be struggling for control on a dusty desert highway, and the next you might be on treacherous snow and ice.</description></item><item><title>Expections: A Mudrunner Game</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/expeditions-a-mudrunner-game/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/expeditions-a-mudrunner-game/</guid><description>Game Description Expections: A Mudrunner Game throws you headlong into unknown territories, putting you at the head of research missions at insidious landscapes. Get ready for an off -road adventure based on physics, where every centimeter of progress requires the courage, strategy and masterful ownership of your strong all -terrain vehicle. Imagine how you will overcome the deserts sifted by the sun, thick forests clinging to your tires, and snowy peaks that experience you for strength.</description></item><item><title>LOLI RACING</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/loli-racing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/loli-racing/</guid><description>Game Description LOLI RACING is a dynamic arcade racing game in which anime characters compete for championship on a variety of tracks. The project invites gamers to plunge into the world of high-speed racing, where not only reflexes play a key role, but also the ability to enter a controlled skid. The competition takes place on 38 unique tracks, each with its own style, from Japanese temples and historical sites to futuristic metropolises and urban landmarks in Taiwan.</description></item><item><title>Pacific Drive</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/pacific-drive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/pacific-drive/</guid><description>Game Description Pacific Drive is an atmospheric car survival adventure in the Olympic Exclusion Zone. Here you will not find the usual racing tracks, but there will be supernatural dangers waiting for you that will make you very tense. The only chance of salvation is your car, which will have to be strengthened and improved throughout the game. You will have to look for resources in abandoned laboratories, set up a base in the garage, research new spare parts and construct new stations.</description></item><item><title>The Impossible Game 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-impossible-game-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-impossible-game-2/</guid><description>Game Description The Impossible Game 2 is a rhythm-platformer that offers not only single-player challenges, but also large-scale online competitions. For the first time in the series, a battle royale mode has been implemented, in which up to 60 people simultaneously compete in high-speed passage of tracks. In addition, for creative gamers, there is a built-in editor with an intuitive interface that allows you to design your own levels and share them with the community.</description></item><item><title>DriveCrazy</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/drivecrazy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/drivecrazy/</guid><description>Game Description DriveCrazy is an arcade madness that asks you to get behind the wheel of a miniature truck amid the total destruction of the apocalyptic landscapes of Japan. The main task is to survive in the face of constant pursuit by mysterious creatures. To avoid missiles and falling buildings, it is possible to move along vertical surfaces. The process of destroying environmental objects, such as pillars, trees and fences, is directly related to replenishing the supply of nitro acceleration.</description></item><item><title>Street Legal 1: REVision</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/street-legal-1-revision/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/street-legal-1-revision/</guid><description>Game Description Street Legal 1: REVision is a racing game that focuses on car customization and realistic damage simulation. This is a re-release of the 2002 game Street Legal with numerous improvements and fixes. The game allows you to start with a regular street car and turn it into a race car by purchasing, changing, repairing and tuning over 1,000 unique parts.
The game features 16 highly detailed cars based on real-life models, ranging from economy cars to muscle-bound V8s and exotic V10 supercars.</description></item><item><title>Brick Rigs</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/brick-rigs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/brick-rigs/</guid><description>Game Description Brick Rigs is a sandbox that allows you to create a variety of vehicles, and then enjoy realistic driving and destruction physics. You need to build cars using various blocks. The Brick Rings toolkit allows you to create a dragster, a fire truck, a forklift, a helicopter, an airplane or even a tank - it all depends on your imagination and skill.
Gameplay Brick Rigs is a full-fledged construction set with which you can create any type of transport.</description></item><item><title>First Racer</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/first-racer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/first-racer/</guid><description>Game Description First Racer is an arcade race where victory is achieved not only through quick reactions, but also through proper preparation of the car. The project offers a wide range of competitive disciplines, covering both city streets and specialized tracks. For fans of extreme driving, there are cross-country races that require a special approach to control. Drifting competitions, in turn, test your car control in a controlled drift, where points are awarded based on angle, speed and style of execution.</description></item><item><title>The Exorcist's Story</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-exorcists-story/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-exorcists-story/</guid><description>Game Description The Exorcist&amp;rsquo;s Story is an atmospheric 2D adventure game in which you will find yourself in the shoes of a young priest, Antonio, who had experience in performing exorcism rituals. But one day everything went wrong and a girl died during the ceremony. You escaped prison, but you promised yourself never to perform such rituals again. But a few years later, strange things begin to happen in your small town and Asmodeus, the demon you once encountered, challenges you again.</description></item><item><title>Mon Bazou</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mon-bazou/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mon-bazou/</guid><description>Game Description While repairing a car inMon Bazou, players have to deal with a variety of everyday problems that affect the life of the main character. The protagonist is a guy who dreams of turning his old car into a racing car that can compete with professional drivers and reach great speed. The game is made in the form of a simulator, where users have to take on the role of a novice racer who will live the everyday routine and do simple things, trying to earn a living.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 5</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 5 is a racing game that focuses on multiplayer racing and free-roaming in an open world. This project includes many aspects from Forza&amp;rsquo;s previous games. More than 200 original cars from real-life companies are presented, with realistic driving and clutch physics. There are high-quality graphics, effects and other elements that completely immerse users in a believable environment.
While riding around the world, the player is able to collide with other gamers or ordinary cars controlled by artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Surfing</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/virtual-surfing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/virtual-surfing/</guid><description>Game Description Virtual Surfing may be suitable for fans of sports games. The title offers to harness the sea and ocean waves. The project lives up to its name. This is an arcade surfing simulator. It boasts well-developed water physics. It has different weather conditions and several locations.
At the very beginning, the gamer is asked to enter a name. And then the user is offered to customize the appearance of his surfer (there is a choice of gender) and customize the board.</description></item><item><title>Skydrift Infinity</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/skydrift-infinity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/skydrift-infinity/</guid><description>Game Description Skydrift Infinity is an arcade game with simulator elements that allows you to take the controls of an airplane and rush through the picturesque expanses of an interactive world. You can fly in free mode or compete with other pilots. If it is impossible to catch up with the enemy, then you can shoot him down! Exotic islands are available for exploration, representing huge arenas for air racing.</description></item><item><title>F1 2021</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/f1-2021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/f1-2021/</guid><description>Game Description F1 2021 is a racing car simulator. The new part of the series provides an opportunity to take part in the 2021 season of the Formula 1 championship. Thanks to the official license, the product contains real teams, drivers and tracks. There is a choice of difficulty. Here you can configure the aggressiveness of artificial intelligence, the severity of the rules, and the driving assistance system. Casual users will be able to make the gameplay more arcade-like, and hardcore users will be able to add realism to the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Truck Driver</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/truck-driver/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/truck-driver/</guid><description>Game Description Truck Driver is a simulator in which you have to build a career as a truck driver. At the beginning of the game, select your character, be it a man or a woman, and get behind the wheel of a truck. Your task is to transport various goods and cargo. The better you cope with tasks, the higher the level of reputation you will have among employers.
Starting from the very bottom with a simple truck, you will gradually improve your transport by buying spare parts or buy a whole fleet of trucks.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 4</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 4 is a realistic racing simulator with an open game world, where the player is given the opportunity to explore many cities, participate in various races and interact with other players. Drive along the tracks of Great Britain, unlock new cars, and take part in tournaments and races.
The gameplay is focused on interaction between players. To participate in certain races, you will need to find a suitable area, as well as gather all participants in one lobby.</description></item><item><title>Under the Sand REDUX - a road trip game</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/under-the-sand-redux-a-road-trip-game/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/under-the-sand-redux-a-road-trip-game/</guid><description>Game Description Under the Sand REDUX - a road trip game is an adventure game in which the player is invited to travel around the world by car. The universe around the main character experienced a terrible apocalypse, turning into a desert. Graphically, the project is made using low-detail textures to create its own style. The locations where the gamer is present are created randomly thanks to the use of artificial intelligence in the process of generating territories, which is responsible for randomizing the environment.</description></item><item><title>Rival Stars Horse Racing: Desktop Edition</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rival-stars-horse-racing-desktop-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rival-stars-horse-racing-desktop-edition/</guid><description>Game Description With Rival Stars Horse Racing: Desktop Edition, the player will have at his disposal a stable of horses from which he must create winners in the race. Here you need to raise and choose a potential champion in order to lead him to victory in horse racing. The desktop version has updated graphics and different game styles. The user inherited a farm from his grandfather that had fallen into disrepair.</description></item><item><title>NFS Heat</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nfs-heat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nfs-heat/</guid><description>Game Description Need for Speed: Heat is an arcade racing simulator with an open game world and a large selection of cars of a wide variety of brands. The plot takes place in Palm City, a fictional city very similar to sunny Miami. You will be able to ride around the city, along the coast, and also take part in stunning races. The story begins with police captain Mercer catching one of the participants in night racing, which is prohibited by law.</description></item><item><title>MX Bikes</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mx-bikes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mx-bikes/</guid><description>Game Description MX Bikes is a motocross simulator that places a huge emphasis on transport physics. The engine accurately simulates the speed, weight, and dynamics of a motorcycle, while providing a wide window for individual settings and customization of vehicle parameters. Both single-player campaign and multiplayer mode are available. All completed races are collected into statistics and show your data, comparing results and personal achievements with players around the world. Support for virtual reality headsets is available, including HTC Vive and Valve Index.</description></item><item><title>Dude Simulator 3</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dude-simulator-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dude-simulator-3/</guid><description>Game Description Dude Simulator 3 is a dude simulator that is characterized by absurdity and black humor. You play the role of a “friend” who is preparing for his friend’s birthday. The day begins with you buying him a gift. Now we need to deliver it, but my friend lives in another city. You are about to go on an adventure that promises many funny and exciting moments.
Gameplay Dude Simulator 3 features an open world sandbox with a unique cubic visual style.</description></item><item><title>Assetto Corsa Competizione</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa-competizione/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa-competizione/</guid><description>Game Description The driving simulator at breakneck speeds - Assetto Corsa Competizione - will show you the real competition of racers in the Blancpain GT Series championship. In the cars that are used in the championships, we will compete against professional racers who will be controlled by artificial intelligence, but at the same time their actions were recorded from the actual behavior of the car on the road when it is driven by a professional.</description></item><item><title>Descenders</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/descenders/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/descenders/</guid><description>Game Description Descenders is a sports bike racing simulator. But as the creators themselves describe it: an extreme speed cycling downhill game. The developer was RageSquid studio, which developed the unusual indie racing game Action Henk.
The player chooses a bike and a team for which he will take part in extreme races across the hills and plains. There are three teams in total, each of which has its own unique characteristics:</description></item><item><title>Starlink: Battle for Atlas</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/starlink-battle-for-atlas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/starlink-battle-for-atlas/</guid><description>Game Description Starlink: Battle for Atlas is an adventure game in which you become a space pilot to rid the Atlas system of the villains Grax and the Forgotten Legion. You will lead your Starlink squad and take a stand against despotism to save the entire galaxy from powerful invaders. There are four ships to choose from to participate in the competition: Zenith, Neptune, Pulse, Lance.
The game provides a choice of six pilots, including Mason, Judge, Chase, Hunter, Levi, Razor, who have their own skills and characteristics.</description></item><item><title>Trials Rising</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/trials-rising/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/trials-rising/</guid><description>Game Description Trials Rising is a 2.5D racing simulator in which the player is invited to try his hand at the most difficult tracks on a loud, powerful bike. Also, the levels will be a serious test of the skills of quick response to the changing situation around and the ability to make unerring somersaults in the air, because if the racer crashes, he will have to start the stage again.</description></item><item><title>BallisticNG</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ballisticng/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ballisticng/</guid><description>Game Description BallisticNG is a dynamic racing simulator in the setting of a sci-fi distant future, in which all available technologies have made an unprecedented leap thanks to the painstaking work of the best minds of the human race. In 2159, battles on the tracks take place in vehicles equipped with an anti-gravity unit that allows them to hover above the earthen surface. The game supports earning achievements from a pre-prepared list of 26 awards, a built-in level editor, a leaderboard, as well as modern technology - a virtual reality helmet.</description></item><item><title>Liftoff: FPV Drone Racing</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/liftoff-fpv-drone-racing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/liftoff-fpv-drone-racing/</guid><description>Game Description Liftoff FPV Drone Racing is a training ground for quadcopter pilots. The game is a training ground for both beginners and an obstacle course for experienced gamers. Professionals can test their strength in a new environment, and people who have recently become interested in this sport can hone their skills before taking on real prototypes.
In Liftoff FPV Drone Racing, users can take their first steps towards the sport of quadcopter racing.</description></item><item><title>The Crew 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-crew-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-crew-2/</guid><description>Game Description In The Crew 2 you can ride anything, as long as you have money for this equipment. The game includes several game modes in the genre of a sports racing simulator from a third/first person: free, cooperative, career, multiplayer mode. A free race usually takes place on a separate map. We choose one unlocked vehicle element and try to win the race. In this simulator you can sail on a boat, drive a fast, high-speed car, or fly on an airplane.</description></item><item><title>CarX Drift Racing Online</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</guid><description>Game Description Arcade car simulatorCarX Drift Racing Online is a new word in the world of racing, where the main component is drifting! From the very beginning, you will have a huge number of opportunities that you can use in the world of real graphics and pumping up cars with modifications from famous manufacturers. From the first to the last minute in the game you will be able to upgrade your car so that it becomes a world prize-winner in the world of drifting!</description></item><item><title>Psebay</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/psebay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/psebay/</guid><description>Game Description The journey to Psebay will be made while driving a motorbike, moving through atmospheric locations. The user will have to overcome difficult landscape obstacles, cutting through hills and rocks on a powerful motorcycle. There is an opportunity to feel the surface of the earth, which constantly strives to move away from under the wheels. It is important to feel and control your balance so as not to fall when crossing difficult terrain and to correctly calculate the acceleration and weight of the vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Street Legal Racing: Redline</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/street-legal-racing-redline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/street-legal-racing-redline/</guid><description>Game Description Street Legal Racing: Redline is a car mechanic simulator that allows you to assemble a car completely from scratch. At the same time, street racing with assembled vehicles is available. New parts can affect the characteristics of the car, which are responsible for acceleration, handling and maximum speed. Street Legal Racing does not provide package upgrades. The rider must install each individual part himself.
The game has many features:</description></item><item><title>BeamNG drive</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/beamng-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/beamng-drive/</guid><description>Game Description BeamNG.drive is a car simulator that simulates the behavior of cars during collisions. Excellent physics, realistic controls and spectacular accidents are the main features of the game. The simulator allows you to find out what the consequences will be if, for example, the steering wheel of a Ferrari jams and the car flies into the oncoming lane, where it collides with a 40-ton truck. Or assess the damage to an army jeep whose brakes jammed when it was going down a hill at a speed of 90 km/h, flew off the road and crashed into a tree.</description></item><item><title>Grand Theft Auto 5</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/grand-theft-auto-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/grand-theft-auto-5/</guid><description>Game Description GTA 5 has received dozens of awards for its open world, and almost the most expensive multi-platform project in history isGrand Theft Auto V. The story opens before us in the same fictional state - San Andreas, made 1 to 1 as Southern California. We play as three robber friends who have spent their entire adult lives stealing cars, robbing small shops and people on the street. One day someone decides to get involved in organized crime, which they have been fighting for the last 5 years.</description></item><item><title>Assetto Corsa</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/assetto-corsa/</guid><description>Game Description Assetto Corsa is a car simulator developed based on test drives of cars using a model of real behavior. Includes both single player and multiplayer modes.
The developers presented a variety of licensed cars and tracks, which were specially digitized specifically for the race to convey maximum authenticity to their prototypes. The machines can be customized to your individual taste, because&amp;hellip; the creators have added an extensive set of settings and support for modifications.</description></item><item><title>BlazeRush</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/blazerush/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/blazerush/</guid><description>Game Description The creators of BlazeRush were clearly inspired by Blizzard&amp;rsquo;s ride-alongs that came out on consoles back in the 90s. Since that project ultimately did not reach the PC, its spiritual successor appeared a couple of decades later. The game also successfully played with the idea of ​​another racing hit of those years - &amp;ldquo;Micromachines&amp;rdquo; - in the form of a single screen for all participants in the race. The arcade action game features co-op for four people.</description></item><item><title>GRID Autosport</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/grid-autosport/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/grid-autosport/</guid><description>Game Description GRID Autosport develops a career mode and free driving in a huge number of cars, which can also be upgraded depending on your preferences. The new part of GRID is a car simulator with several game modes. Career passage is a single, story-based scenario part - this is about upgrading your driver, team of mechanics and building a reputation at the level of your driving. Here we upgrade the car and drive on 100 routes in 22 game locations, distributed according to difficulty and prestige.</description></item><item><title>Tick ​​Hop</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tick-hop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tick-hop/</guid><description>Game Description Tick ​​Hop is a 2D platformer that requires the accuracy of movements, where a gamer assumes the role of the keeper of time. The journey includes the passage of the stages, each of which consists of temporary fragments. The main goal is to solve riddles, opening the aspects of the past to restore the future. The reverse reference system in this project requires quick actions to move through chronological spaces.</description></item></channel></rss>