<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Arcade on Game Vibe</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/tags/arcade/</link><description>Recent content in Arcade on Game Vibe</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://game-vibe.github.io/tags/arcade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Realm Racer</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/realm-racer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/realm-racer/</guid><description>Game Description Realm Racer is an arcade racing project, the main goal of which is to find the ideal trajectory to achieve the maximum number of points. The process of passing is complicated by extraordinary routes that run through many eras and various biomes. The key element of the gameplay is a constantly running engine, which completely eliminates the possibility of stopping. Navigating through locations requires sharp reactions and skill to overcome all physical obstacles on the way to the finish line.</description></item><item><title>The Last Ninja Collection + Bonus Games</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-last-ninja-collection-bonus-games/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-last-ninja-collection-bonus-games/</guid><description>Game Description The Last Ninja Collection and Bonus Games - the final confrontation between the ninja Armakuni and the sinister shogun Kunitoki takes place within the walls of an ancient Tibetan temple. The path to the main enemy runs through five halls, each of which is subordinate to its own element. Overcoming these challenges requires not only combat skills, but also ingenuity to solve puzzles and find sacred scrolls. The combat system rewards skill through Bushido mechanics, increasing the effectiveness of a warrior fighting unarmed or using the same type of weapon as his opponent.</description></item><item><title>Terminator 2D: NO FATE</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/terminator-2d-no-fate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/terminator-2d-no-fate/</guid><description>Game Description Terminator 2D: NO FATE is an arcade action game, the plot of which is based on the events of the cult sci-fi action film, offering to relive iconic episodes in a 2D side-scroller format. Gamers take control of characters such as Sarah Connor and T-800, who will have to thwart the plans of Skynet&amp;rsquo;s artificial intelligence. The main enemy is the invulnerable T-1000, and the main task is to prevent the total destruction of humanity in the coming war.</description></item><item><title>I Sell Lemonade</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/i-sell-lemonade/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/i-sell-lemonade/</guid><description>Game Description I Sell Lemonade is a story about a 1980s summer spent on the sidewalk with a pitcher of soft drink. At the center of the story is a 10-year-old child who, after his father sells his gaming console, is forced to look for something to do on the street. An activity initially conceived as a way to pass the time gradually turns into an extended journey through childhood experiences, friendships and character formation.</description></item><item><title>Mutant Football League 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mutant-football-league-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mutant-football-league-2/</guid><description>Game Description Mutant Football League 2 is a brutal arcade reimagining of American football, where athletes are replaced by teams of orcs, skeletons and deadly robots. The project is an ideological continuation of the cult classic, relying not on realism, but on dark humor and spectacular matches in the 8 vs 8 format. Each arena is a high-danger zone filled with circular saws, mines and other deadly traps. Unpredictability is also introduced by sudden events that can radically change the balance of power during the competition.</description></item><item><title>NeverAwake FLASHBACK</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/neverawake-flashback/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/neverawake-flashback/</guid><description>Game Description Delving into the surreal world of subconscious nightmares, NeverAwake FLASHBACK offers a confrontation with distorted childhood memories. The project&amp;rsquo;s universe is filled with grotesque opponents, which are materialized phobias. The monsters are not demons, but hated vegetables, frightening dentists and other traumatic images from the past of the young heroine named Rem. On this dangerous journey through the recesses of consciousness, she is accompanied by her faithful plush companion Gabe-chan.</description></item><item><title>Simogo Legacy Collection</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/simogo-legacy-collection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/simogo-legacy-collection/</guid><description>Game Description Simogo Legacy Collection is an anthology of 7 classic projects, representing an eclectic collection of works from the past. In addition to the main works, the publication is supplemented by an extensive archive of rare materials. Among them you can find a digital book, an audio drama in podcast format, as well as previously unreleased musical compositions. Of particular interest are game prototypes and interactive storytelling, which allow you to look at the creative process from the inside.</description></item><item><title>MARVEL Cosmic Invasion</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/marvel-cosmic-invasion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/marvel-cosmic-invasion/</guid><description>Game Description MARVEL Cosmic Invasion is a side-scrolling beat &amp;lsquo;em up focused on interstellar conflict. The player will have to choose from 15 heroes to confront the Annihilation Wave, a force threatening the galaxy under the leadership of Annihilus. The story takes place in a variety of locations, starting on Earth, such as New York, and extending into space, including the Negative Zone. Figures like Nova, Spider-Man, Wolverine, Phyla-Vell and Captain America are among the available protagonists to join the efforts against this galactic menace.</description></item><item><title>Death In Abyss</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/death-in-abyss/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/death-in-abyss/</guid><description>Game Description Death In Abyss becomes a real test of strength for connoisseurs of intense shooters, because the project requires honed reflexes and virtuoso control of the combat apparatus. The flight system is designed for the fast maneuvers, including evasive maneuvers and sharp turns, needed to survive high-dynamic collision environments. Confrontation with hostile life forms is based on the use of a powerful arsenal. Each successful elimination of an enemy allows you to absorb his vital energy to restore your own reserve of strength, which forces you to constantly be on the move and conduct an aggressive battle.</description></item><item><title>Super Cabbage Kabumi</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/super-cabbage-kabumi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/super-cabbage-kabumi/</guid><description>Game Description Super Cabbage Kabumi is a roguelike game that focuses on creating unique builds of items and pets for maximum efficiency. The central element of the gameplay is the process of collecting artifacts, whose properties can be combined to produce unpredictable and powerful effects. Unlockable companions have a significant impact on the passage. These creatures have unique abilities that can, for example, modify the speed of a projectile or change the reaction of targets to interaction.</description></item><item><title>GLONK</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/glonk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/glonk/</guid><description>Game Description GLONK is an incremental project in which the entire gameplay is built around feeding the creature of the same name. The central task is to constantly provide the pet with food for its subsequent increase in size, which directly affects financial well-being. The viability and continuous growth of the ward is the only source of income, so maintaining his health becomes a paramount task for accumulating gold. Successfully nurturing one creature opens up the opportunity to have several more, thereby scaling up profits and accelerating advancement to new levels.</description></item><item><title>Social Soccer Champions</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sociable-soccer-champions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sociable-soccer-champions/</guid><description>Game Description Sociable Soccer Champions is a fast-paced take on competitive soccer with fast-paced arcade gameplay at its core. Controls are intuitive, but mastery will require some practice. The arsenal of techniques includes powerful shots with spin on the ball, as well as acceleration and energy consumption systems. The key element is to build your own roster from an extensive database of over 14,000 licensed FIFPRO professionals. Each player card has unique attributes, allowing you to create tactically flexible teams to achieve victories.</description></item><item><title>Bubble Bobble Sugar Dungeons</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bubble-bobble-sugar-dungeons/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bubble-bobble-sugar-dungeons/</guid><description>Game Description Bubble Bobble Sugar Dungeons is a colorful adventure with roguelike elements set in a whimsical world made entirely of sweets. The gameplay revolves around exploring ever-changing dungeons and castles filled with dessert-shaped enemies. From the treasures found, special ingredients are obtained that are necessary to enhance the abilities of the main character. Repeated completion of levels allows you to accumulate resources for learning new skills, opening access to previously inaccessible areas.</description></item><item><title>Street Racer Collection (QUByte Classics)</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/street-racer-collection-qubyte-classics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/street-racer-collection-qubyte-classics/</guid><description>Game Description Street Racer Collection (QUByte Classics) is a hybrid of arcade racing and combat competitions, where reaching the finish line is just one part of success. The main way to interact with opponents is not just overtaking, but direct physical elimination using special techniques. You can control a dozen colorful pilots, each of whom has a vehicle with unique attack capabilities. Competitions take place on routes full of dangers, running through both recognizable landmarks and completely fantastic areas.</description></item><item><title>AFTERBLAST</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/afterblast/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/afterblast/</guid><description>Game Description AFTERBLAST is a fast-paced first-person shooter with rogue-lite elements that takes you on an epic journey across a devastated planet. As you progress through randomly generated dungeons, you&amp;rsquo;ll encounter hordes of monsters and bosses, and you&amp;rsquo;ll need dozens of guns and other weapons to defeat them. In this world, chaos came without warning and wreaked havoc on the once beautiful planet of Aryasan. The skies dimmed, the vegetation withered, and animals began to attack each other as resources dried up.</description></item><item><title>Daisen</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/daisen/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/daisen/</guid><description>Game Description Daisen is a fast-paced first-person shooter that tells the story of the fate of a girl who finds herself at the center of a mysterious anomaly spreading. The protagonist is Emilia Svitanko, an ordinary girl who inevitably becomes a tool for containing chaos. She will have to figure out the reasons for the anomalous influence that has engulfed the surrounding lands. A key feature of the combat system is the complete absence of ammunition and reloading.</description></item><item><title>HoloCafe</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/holocafe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/holocafe/</guid><description>Game Description HoloCafe is a management simulator in which the player takes on the role of a manager and saves a small establishment from ruin. The plot takes place in an alternate universe, where instead of a VTuber agency, a cafe was opened, but the business quickly fell into disrepair. When the situation began to seem hopeless, virtual idols appear from a mysterious portal, ready to help restore business. The gamer has at his disposal a staff of 17 talents representing the Japanese, English and Indonesian divisions of Hololive.</description></item><item><title>Speed ​​Demons 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/speed-demons-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/speed-demons-2/</guid><description>Game Description Speed ​​Demons 2 is an arcade road racing game that focuses on explosive action and all-out destruction. The project offers hundreds of races, distributed across numerous chapters. A total of 10 modes are available, ranging from classic competitions with rivals to missions where the main goal is to destroy as many vehicles as possible within the allotted time. Moreover, each race is designed for quick sessions and is completed on average in 2-4 minutes, maintaining a high pace of what is happening.</description></item><item><title>ZAKO NO AHIRU</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/zako-no-ahiru/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/zako-no-ahiru/</guid><description>Game Description ZAKO NO AHIRU is a 2D platformer of increased difficulty, the main goal of which is to conquer an inaccessible peak to the accompaniment of caustic comments. Every action is tirelessly watched by a girl named Sugaki Mary, who lives next door. She&amp;rsquo;s ready to make a caustic remark or an inappropriate joke at any time, using an arsenal of more than 800 fully voiced lines. The reward for your patience and skill will be one of 7 endings, each of which represents a unique surreal situation, reminiscent of a dream.</description></item><item><title>Neon Inferno</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/neon-inferno/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/neon-inferno/</guid><description>Game Description Neon Inferno is a hybrid side-scroller whose gameplay is an explosive combination of 2D run-and-gun and gallery shooter. The basis of the combat system is the ability to fire at opponents who are simultaneously in the foreground and in the background. Tactical depth is provided by the Bullet Time mechanic, which allows you to deflect enemy projectiles, as well as the ability to hijack vehicles to pursue targets.</description></item><item><title>BIRDCAGE</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/birdcage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/birdcage/</guid><description>Game Description BIRDCAGE is a fast-paced bullet hell shooter where gameplay focuses on unique sword mechanics to fend off attacks and destroy enemies. The project takes inspiration from the arcade classics of the 90s, offering a polished combat system and stylized graphics. The pilot is required not only to dodge hundreds of projectiles, but also to actively use the blade to break through enemy squadrons. The title requires high concentration and sharp reflexes to survive in the chaos of battles.</description></item><item><title>Sektori</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sektori/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sektori/</guid><description>Game Description Sektori is an intense twin-stick shooter whose gameplay is inextricably linked to the aggressive rhythms of techno music and requires extreme concentration from the player. The project immerses you in a state of flow, where kaleidoscopic visuals, soundtrack and gameplay merge into one. The main task is to destroy a myriad of opponents in a constantly transforming arena. The battlefield dynamically changes its shape, expanding, contracting or even splitting into several parts, which forces you to constantly adapt battle tactics and does not allow you to rely on memorized patterns.</description></item><item><title>SpongeBob SquarePants: Titans of the Tide</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/spongebob-squarepants-titans-of-the-tide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/spongebob-squarepants-titans-of-the-tide/</guid><description>Game Description SpongeBob SquarePants: Titans of the Tide is a platformer that takes players on a new ghostly adventure through a beloved underwater world. The basis of the gameplay was the ability to instantly change the controlled character, choosing between SpongeBob and Patrick, in order to jointly use their unique acrobatic talents to deal with puzzles and obstacles. Special mention goes to Patrick, whose moveset has been expanded to include the ability to burrow into the ground or cling to ledges with a grappling hook.</description></item><item><title>Claire a la Mode</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/claire-a-la-mode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/claire-a-la-mode/</guid><description>Game Description Claire a la Mode is a global pastry tournament where not only the prestigious title of best baker, but also the fate of an entire city is at stake. This grand competition is marred by the presence of dishonest participants who seek to falsify the final results. At the head of the conspiracy is the insidious Queen Bee, whose numerous henchmen are actively trying to interfere with honest confectioners.</description></item><item><title>Shelldiver</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/shelldiver/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/shelldiver/</guid><description>Game Description Shelldiver immerses you in exploring a vast ocean filled with unique biomes, from volcanic waters to crystalline caves. Instead of linear development, a branched skill tree is offered, which allows you to customize expeditions in detail to suit your own style of passage, focusing on the speed of collection or the depth of research. All these improvements serve one purpose - the development of an unusual business founded by an elderly turtle.</description></item><item><title>Void Miner – Incremental Asteroids Roguelite</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/void-miner-incremental-asteroids-roguelite/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/void-miner-incremental-asteroids-roguelite/</guid><description>Game Description Void Miner – Incremental Asteroids Roguelite, a retro-stylized roguelike shooter that immerses you in the atmosphere of classic arcade games and invites you to take control of a spaceship to clear endless asteroid fields. The main task is to methodically destroy waves of space debris filling hostile space. Gamers will have to not only dodge countless threats, but also conduct targeted fire, turning chaotic clusters into valuable resources for further development.</description></item><item><title>CLAWPUNK</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/clawpunk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/clawpunk/</guid><description>Game Description CLAWPUNK, a 2D action-platformer with roglite elements, takes you to a dystopian city overrun by hostile factions and street gangs. The main goal is to recapture the metropolis from a tyrant named Mister Fluffy, a former ally who betrayed his relatives and expelled all the cats. The liberation mission falls on the shoulders of a squad of 9 unique cat heroes with a total of 9 lives per playthrough.</description></item><item><title>SCHROTT</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/schrott/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/schrott/</guid><description>Game Description SCHROTT is a roguelike racing game where performing crazy stunts and collecting valuable loot provide the basis for deep vehicle customization. Instead of ordinary machines, there are absurd designs that lend themselves to all sorts of improvements to wreak even more chaos. Each race turns into a hunt for resources that allow you to turn your car into a unique weapon of destruction on the road. Arcade controls make the gameplay accessible and intuitive from the first minutes, and high-speed action does not let you relax.</description></item><item><title>Soba's Gunpaw</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sobas-gunpaw/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sobas-gunpaw/</guid><description>Game Description Sobas Gunpaw is a dynamic action game in the style of Bullet Heaven, where survival directly depends on the constant and systematic strengthening of the protagonist. At the heart of it all is an extensive skill system that provides access to numerous character upgrades. The progression process is built on the cyclical destruction of everything on the screen, which allows you to accumulate valuable assets. It is these materials collected from defeated enemies that open new branches in the branched tree of talents.</description></item><item><title>DEFRAG</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/defrag/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/defrag/</guid><description>Game Description DEFRAG becomes a real optimization test for the gamer, since the project requires a careful approach to creating an effective system. The goal is to eliminate digital viruses that have infected system sectors. To achieve success, you will have to collect the resources necessary to strengthen the nodes. Combining these elements allows you to discover new fighting styles, which adds variety to the passage. The effectiveness of weapons is customized using special modules that form the basis for unique assemblies.</description></item><item><title>Duncrush</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/duncrush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/duncrush/</guid><description>Game Description Duncrush is a role-playing clicker game where the depth of character development is achieved through a well-developed skill tree and unique equipment. Creating your own strategy becomes possible thanks to powerful blades, shields and accessories found in battle. All this equipment is necessary to strengthen the hero, preparing to meet stronger opponents. Exploring numerous dungeons, each with unique challenges and rewards, forms the core of the gameplay. In these dangerous journeys, the protagonist is helped by mercenaries who fight shoulder to shoulder.</description></item><item><title>NASCAR 25</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nascar-25/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nascar-25/</guid><description>Game Description NASCAR 25 takes you through the challenging journey from novice to motorsport legend. His career starts in a modest home garage, where he will prepare his first car for races in the ARCA Menards series. Gradually moving up the racing hierarchy, it will be possible to conquer the NASCAR Craftsman Truck Series, Xfinity Series championships and, finally, fight for the main cup. Success depends not only on skill on the track, but also on strategic decisions: hiring personnel, finding sponsors and developing new parts for the car, building its reputation through results and communication with the press.</description></item><item><title>Cyber ​​Shard Clicker</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/cyber-shard-clicker/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/cyber-shard-clicker/</guid><description>Game Description Cyber ​​Shard Clicker is an incremental project that focuses on strategic development and constant enhancement of hacking capabilities. The central element of the entire progression system is a branched skill tree, offering tactical choices between immediate improvements and permanent bonuses. The latter guarantee a significant advantage in future hacking attempts. The resource for acquiring new skills are data fragments obtained in the process of destroying geometric defense systems. Each click turns into a pulse of digital destruction, aimed at destroying enemy polygonal shields, cubic guards and triangular drones.</description></item><item><title>Let Them Come: Onslaught</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/let-them-come-onslaught/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/let-them-come-onslaught/</guid><description>Game Description Let Them Come: Onslaught is the epitome of cinematic chaos as high-tech drones and deadly orbital lasers rain down on the enemy, accompanied by vibrant retro-pixelated visuals. The weapon fires automatically, allowing you to fully focus on tactical maneuvers and choosing upgrades in real time. Survival on a hostile planet infested with alien horrors becomes a real challenge. Endless waves of xenomorphs and giant bosses constantly test reflexes and the ability to adapt to the dangers of procedurally generated arenas inspired by 80s sci-fi action films.</description></item><item><title>Lumines Arise</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lumines-arise/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lumines-arise/</guid><description>Game Description Lumines Arise is a reimagining of the classic puzzle game from the studio Enhance, known for the Tetris Effect: Connected project. Temporarily stopping field clearing with the new Burst mechanic opens up tactical depth, allowing you to build huge formations for record-breaking scores. This approach turns each playthrough into a unique audiovisual experience, where actions directly affect the environment and soundtrack. The concept of synesthesia, laid down by the developers, is felt in every element, linking together light, sound and interaction.</description></item><item><title>Swords and Sandals 3 Redux</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/swords-and-sandals-3-redux/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/swords-and-sandals-3-redux/</guid><description>Game Description Swords and Sandals 3 Redux plunges fighters into a world of merciless combat, where cutting off limbs does not mean inevitable defeat, but only strengthens the will to win. Turn-based battles in the Gladiae Ultratus arena, taking place both one-on-one and in teams of two, set the goal for the gladiator to defeat 24 legendary champions of the Brandor universe. The path to glory runs through seven deadly locations, from the eerie depths of the Bone Pit to the dizzying heights of the Tower of Vertigo.</description></item><item><title>King of Bones</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/king-of-bones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/king-of-bones/</guid><description>Game Description In King of Bones, the main goal is to dominate prehistoric arenas in battles with realistic physics. The combat system conveys the weight and power of every encounter as all bites and strikes interact with physically simulated bodies in real time. Gamers dash, stomp and headbutt in fast-paced battles where creatures fight to the last. An attacking Triceratops can throw an enemy into the air, and small raptors can grab onto larger opponents right during a fight.</description></item><item><title>Nitroglycerine!</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nitroglycerine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nitroglycerine/</guid><description>Game Description Nitroglycerine! is a test where the main task is to transport a deadly substance along difficult routes. The process of controlling a heavy tractor is subject to the laws of realistic physics, and the vehicle itself is completely unsuitable for overcoming obstacles along the way. Any mistake in piloting, sharp turn or collision can lead to the detonation of nitroglycerin and instant failure of the mission. Even climbing moderately steep slopes requires precise timing, and putting too much pressure on the engine via turbocharging risks stalling the engine.</description></item><item><title>Dragon Blazers</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dragon-blazers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dragon-blazers/</guid><description>Game Description Adventures in Dragon Blazers take players into a fantasy setting where they have to take control of a mighty warrior. The hero masters mysterious combat techniques that will be useful in clashes against cyber ninjas. The game is made in the form of a classic arcade adventure game, drawn in retro pixel graphics. Users will wander through two-dimensional locations with a side view, encountering problems such as landscape obstacles (pits, hills, traps) and opponents.</description></item><item><title>Drill Bird</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/drill-bird/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/drill-bird/</guid><description>Game Description Drill Bird invites you to immerse yourself in a world where every foray underground is critical. As darkness falls, the depths become filled with danger, forcing you to rush back to the safety of your nest. This story of survival and care is told without a single word, creating a special atmosphere in which comfort is mixed with constant tension. Every decision made directly affects the outcome, because time is running out inexorably, and the creatures waiting in the darkness do not forgive mistakes, turning each expedition into a risky undertaking.</description></item><item><title>THRASHER</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/thrasher/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/thrasher/</guid><description>Game Description THRASHER is a psychedelic arcade odyssey where music, visuals and the process itself are woven into a single transcendental stream that immerses you in a state of flow. The journey takes you from primeval darkness to the heights of celestial bliss, culminating in an intense showdown with a cosmic infant deity. Control the magnificent space eel to gracefully glide and dash across stunning alien worlds in a desperate race for survival.</description></item><item><title>Click to Civ</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/click-to-civ/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/click-to-civ/</guid><description>Game Description Click to Civ is an incremental strategy game where the main goal is to help crashed aliens. The plot revolves around the emergency landing of their ship on prehistoric Earth, where the survivors find themselves surrounded by primitive tribes. The only way to return home is to accelerate the evolution of humanity, taking it from stone tools to interstellar technology. The basis of progress are special signs of civilization, obtained from the destruction of ancient monoliths.</description></item><item><title>Deep Space Exploitation</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/deep-space-exploitation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/deep-space-exploitation/</guid><description>Game Description Deep Space Exploitation is a space mining simulator in which pilots have to work for a dubious corporation in the distant future. The storyline, spanning a prologue and several epilogues, challenges gamers to survive under harsh corporate oppression. The main gameplay comes down to the exploration of asteroid fields, where not only courage is required, but also extreme caution to successfully extract resources. Every decision made directly affects the further development of events and the ability to secure a decent future for oneself.</description></item><item><title>Silly Survivors</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/silly-survivors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/silly-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Silly Survivors is a casual action game in which the protagonist will have to repel the attacks of hordes of funny ghosts. A brave fluffy fox falls under control, for which the only means of defense is an ordinary flashlight. Despite their comical appearance and ridiculous behavior, otherworldly entities pose a serious threat. They constantly try to get closer to the character in order to pull off some trick that turns out to be fatal.</description></item><item><title>Mortal Kombat: Legacy Collection</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mortal-kombat-legacy-kollection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mortal-kombat-legacy-kollection/</guid><description>Game Description Mortal Kombat: Legacy Kollection collects key games from the series' inception, presented as they appeared in arcades and on home consoles. This collection contains the original arcade releases and a carefully selected selection of home system adaptations from the 1990s. The gamer selects a character from a list of fighters, each of whom is based on digitized live actors - a technique that set the initial visual style of the project.</description></item><item><title>Nuclear Gladiators 3000</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nuclear-gladiators-3000/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nuclear-gladiators-3000/</guid><description>Game Description Nuclear Gladiators 3000 is an opportunity to become the star of a brutal TV show, quench the thirst for spectacle of the bloodthirsty crowd and write your name in history forever. The winners will receive not only recognition, but also a place of honor in the Hall of Fame, as well as a glossy cover of Gladiators Today Magazine. These are the goals that fighters pursue in a retrofuturistic world, where survival has become the highest-rated entertainment, broadcast live for the amusement of the audience.</description></item><item><title>Silver Bullet</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/silver-bullet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/silver-bullet/</guid><description>Game Description Silver Bullet is an arcade shooting gallery in which the protagonist will have to clear static screens from numerous waves of enemies. The famous monster hunter Van Helsing falls under the control of the gamer, who will have to go through 12 levels. The gameplay requires precise actions, since simultaneous movement and firing are not provided. To survive, you must constantly evade threats and choose the right position to attack.</description></item><item><title>Wreckreation</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/wreckreation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/wreckreation/</guid><description>Game Description Users in Wreckreation will enjoy dynamic rides in racing cars, moving across vast locations. You will go out for a ride on unique tracks where there are jumps, twisted road elements and other dangerous tests. The game has a plentiful number of cars to choose from, as well as many locked cars that should be gradually unlocked as you progress through the single-player campaign. Players will have to tune their cars, changing the appearance with paint and body kits, as well as improving driving characteristics with the engine, wheels and other components.</description></item><item><title>Flappy Bat 3</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/flappy-bat-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/flappy-bat-3/</guid><description>Game Description Flappy Bat 3 offers an endless arcade challenge where each playthrough is unique thanks to procedurally generated obstacles. Gamers must perform precise wing flaps using a simple mouse click or gamepad tap to guide the bat through an ever-changing maze of dangers. Intense competition for the highest score unfolds on the global leaderboard, motivating you to hone your skills. The difficulty increases steadily with each level, presenting new challenges and forcing you to constantly adapt your tactics to survive.</description></item><item><title>The Horde Wants You Dead</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-horde-wants-you-dead/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-horde-wants-you-dead/</guid><description>Game Description The Horde Wants You Dead is a fast-paced top-down shooter that plunges you into a desperate fight for survival against countless hordes of enemies. The main task is to confront thousands of ruthless opponents, using an extensive arsenal and tactical maneuvers. Survivors must collect coins from defeated enemies, which are exchanged for supply crates containing character upgrades, new weapons, or increased firepower.
The gameplay is based on constant movement and adaptation to different types of enemies.</description></item><item><title>OLAPU</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/olapu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/olapu/</guid><description>Game Description OLAPU is a test for a well-coordinated team, challenging raid bosses whose mechanics are reminiscent of large-scale battles in MMORPGs. Defeating opponents like Guardian Seraphina or Empress Elisera will require not only perfect knowledge of attack patterns, but also impeccable coordination. Each successful foray into the Valley of Elisera is rewarded, allowing you to unlock permanent upgrades, legendary gear with semi-random stats, and even new characters for future runs.</description></item><item><title>Roulette Hero</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/roulette-hero/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/roulette-hero/</guid><description>Game Description Roulette Hero is a project in which a squad of adorable animals confronts ruthless mechanical monsters, and the outcome of the battles is decided by the rotation of the roulette. Gamers will have to form a team of various animals, each of which has unique abilities. Some companions are distinguished by their attack speed, while others create impenetrable defense. The thoughtful placement of fighters on the cells of the roulette wheel and its subsequent launch activate their skills, creating powerful combinations and synergies that can turn the tide of even the most difficult fight.</description></item><item><title>Double Dragon Revive</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/double-dragon-revive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/double-dragon-revive/</guid><description>Game Description Double Dragon Revive is a revival of the classic series in modern 3D, where the combat system goes beyond just beating up your opponents. The outcome of the fight now depends on the ability to parry blows by performing the stunning technique Critical Assault, and on the competent use of the environment. The heroes will not only have to use their fists, but also use weapons scattered throughout the levels, from knives to hammers, and also use interactive elements of locations to gain a tactical advantage.</description></item><item><title>HYPERBEAT</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/hyperbeat/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/hyperbeat/</guid><description>Game Description HYPERBEAT is a rhythmic adventure in which the armored HYPERKNIGHT races through surreal interdimensional tunnels. Players must navigate their way through neon mazes, where every note of the original electronic soundtrack dictates the action. Instead of a static environment, the character plunges into an endless dream, reminiscent of a dynamic tube, dodging obstacles and tracking light paths.
Progressing through this world unlocks cosmetic items and a variety of palettes that allow you to fine-tune your turquoise knight&amp;rsquo;s appearance.</description></item><item><title>Hoop Land</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/hoop-land/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/hoop-land/</guid><description>Game Description Hoop Land is a detailed simulator that takes you from a young athlete to the greatest player of all time. The main task is to build your own basketball dynasty, where every decision affects your rise to glory. The path to greatness begins not in the professional arena, but in school. In Career Mode, your character develops as a young prospect who must choose a college, build relationships with teammates, and ultimately enter the draft to earn honors and recognition in the professional league.</description></item><item><title>Arcade Forever</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/arcade-forever/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/arcade-forever/</guid><description>Game Description Arcade Forever is a vertically scrolling 3D space shooter that immerses you in a sci-fi atmosphere of continuous battles. The project offers dynamic gameplay where you have to maneuver among numerous obstacles and enemy squadrons. The main task is to survive and destroy enemies throughout 25 different levels.
The gameplay is based on automatic shooting and a system of independent improvements, which allows you to concentrate on dodging enemy fire and tactical movement.</description></item><item><title>Pereelous</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/pereelous/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/pereelous/</guid><description>Game Description Pereelous is a role-playing adventure in which the fate of the character and all his actions are completely subordinated to the results of the rotation of the slot machine reels. The process of passing is not reduced to blind chance, since success largely depends on the ability to stop the rotation in time to form a profitable combination of symbols. Combinations of signs lead to both the activation of powerful effects and destructive consequences, which forces you to constantly adjust your tactics, based on current results and artifacts unlocked along the way.</description></item><item><title>BALL x PIT</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ball-x-pit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ball-x-pit/</guid><description>Game Description BALL x PIT is a dynamic roguelike, the events of which unfold in a world that has experienced the death of the great city of Ballbilon. After a mysterious cataclysm, a bottomless Pit was formed on the site of the metropolis, which attracted adventurers and treasure seekers from all over the world. The heroes will have to descend into its dark depths to fight hordes of enemies with the help of ricocheting balls and find the riches left over from the fallen civilization.</description></item><item><title>Zaccaria Pinball</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/zaccaria-pinball/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/zaccaria-pinball/</guid><description>Game Description Zaccaria Pinball is the digital incarnation of pinball machines, offering an extensive collection of tables divided into several categories. Enthusiasts have access to both classic electro-mechanical (EM) devices, like Nautilus or Universe, and more modern solid-state (SS) versions, including Time Machine and Devil Riders.
In addition to authentic recreations, the project includes completely redesigned tables such as Space Shuttle 2016 and Farfalla 2017, as well as unique themed designs presented in the Award category, where you can find The Mummy and Aliens.</description></item><item><title>Royal Revolt Survivors</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/royal-revolt-survivors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/royal-revolt-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Royal Revolt Survivors is a continuation of the famous franchise, taking gamers into a fantasy world that is being desecrated by hordes of dark forces. In the role of one of the Warriors from the star cast of heroes in the Royal Revolt universe, you will have to repel the invaders and cleanse your native lands of filth. This project combines elements of a slasher film and a simplified roguelike, where the main task is to survive under the onslaught of hundreds of enemies in a variety of dynamic arenas.</description></item><item><title>Vanquish The Eternal</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/vanquish-the-eternal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/vanquish-the-eternal/</guid><description>Game Description Vanquish The Eternal provides an arsenal of unique abilities, extensive talent trees, and a variety of empowering buffs to counter the forces of evil. Players will choose from eight fully voiced characters, including the mysterious Alchemist, to fight back against the nightmarish creatures. Advancement is built on a meta-progression system that allows you to gradually strengthen your heroes for subsequent battles. Deep customization of your fighting style is a key element in preparing for the battle with the main antagonist, whose power increases with each new challenge.</description></item><item><title>Absolum</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/absolum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/absolum/</guid><description>Game Description Absolum offers to take on the role of outcast heroes living in the world of Talam. These characters oppose the Sun King Azra, seeking to take away his power over magic. The experience combines the mechanics of a side-scrolling beat &amp;lsquo;em up with roguelite elements that influence the progression of each run. To complete the task, you need to move around Talam and fight Azra&amp;rsquo;s troops for the main goal.</description></item><item><title>Dicealot</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dicealot/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dicealot/</guid><description>Game Description Dicealot follows Queen Guinevere as she strives to save the cursed King Arthur by leading knights through chaos-ridden Camelot. Gamers will face more than 30 types of opponents, from commoners to mythical creatures, in this unpredictable medieval world. Each run is a solo journey with permanent death, forcing you to start a new adventure from scratch. The decisions made directly affect the outcome of the mission to remove the spell that threatens the domain.</description></item><item><title>Runeborn</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/runeborn/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/runeborn/</guid><description>Game Description Runeborn offers turn-based combat, similar to a slot machine. Spells are activated by rotating runic columns to match symbols along five different lines. Successful combinations initiate attacks against demonic opponents. For increased control, gamers can lock up to 8 individual symbols in place while the rest of the reels spin, allowing them to build powerful streaks. This mechanic underlies all tactical encounters with Malakar&amp;rsquo;s forces.
Strategy in Runeborn is based on direct customization of runic columns.</description></item><item><title>Vampire's Best Friend</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/vampires-best-friend/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/vampires-best-friend/</guid><description>Game Description Vampire&amp;rsquo;s Best Friend - a brave bat, controlled by the user, must make his way through deadly traps and treacherous obstacles to save his owner. The gameplay is based on unique flight mechanics, requiring refined and precise wing strokes to maneuver in confined spaces. The journey unfolds in gloomy but charming locations, among which there are foggy caves and ancient ruins. The visual design is stylized as retro classics, which is achieved through pixel graphics and a limited color palette, creating a nostalgic atmosphere.</description></item><item><title>Disaster Arms - Impact Project B.A.H.N.</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/disaster-arms-impact-project-bahn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/disaster-arms-impact-project-bahn/</guid><description>Game Description Disaster Arms Impact Project B.A.H.N. - The story of a lonely soldier named Gveral, whose vengeful chase unfolds on the threshold of the global apocalypse. The world stands on the edge of death due to an alien invasion provoked by the ruthless experiments of the Kaisercorps corporation. The past of the gover, known as the &amp;ldquo;empty soldier&amp;rdquo;, is revealed through the non -linear narration, presented in the form of stylized comics, immersing in the gloomy atmosphere of the coming anti -utopia.</description></item><item><title>LEGO Party!</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lego-party/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lego-party/</guid><description>Game Description At LEGO Party! Up to 4 opponents battle each other in themed Challenge Zones. The main task is to collect the maximum number of Golden Cubes, winning competitions and interfering with opponents. The competitions themselves take place in recognizable LEGO universes, including those based on the Pirates, Space and NINJAGO series. Gamers will have to navigate locations full of monsters, traps and other threats like flying fried turkeys. Power-ups provide temporary superiority, and well-placed traps can slow down opponents, which creates a spirit of competition.</description></item><item><title>Beatblock</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/beatblock/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/beatblock/</guid><description>Game Description In Beatblock, the player controls a platform located in the center of a circular arena. As the character Cranky, you need to intercept blocks that appear in time with the melody. This action requires constant rotation to meet targets that appear around the perimeter. Gameplay is complicated by the introduction of four different types of blocks, each requiring a different approach to eliminate. Each track is a self-contained level with a unique visual style, in which the main goal is to score points.</description></item><item><title>PAC-MAN WORLD 2 Re-PAC</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/pac-man-world-2-re-pac/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/pac-man-world-2-re-pac/</guid><description>Game Description PAC-MAN WORLD 2 Re-PAC takes the main character on a journey through the diverse regions of PAC-LAND. The adventure begins after the Ghosts steal the Golden Fruit from PAC-Village, inadvertently releasing a powerful ghost king named Spooky. The key task is to return the stolen artifacts and defeat the antagonist to restore order. The mission begins in an expanded village that serves as a central location from which gamers set out to explore the larger world.</description></item><item><title>Tokyo Xtreme Racer</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tokyo-xtreme-racer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tokyo-xtreme-racer/</guid><description>Game Description Tokyo Xtreme Racer is a racing game set against the backdrop of Tokyo&amp;rsquo;s vibrant underground street racing scene. The game immerses users in a world where speed and skill reign, and the ultimate goal is to defeat your opponents in intense one-on-one battles. Unlike traditional racing games, the title introduces a unique twist where the main goal is not to take first place, but to destroy the opponent&amp;rsquo;s Spirit Points (SP).</description></item><item><title>Explosive Odds</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/explosive-odds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/explosive-odds/</guid><description>Game Description Explosive Odds is a multiplayer competition where financial dominance is achieved through risky bets and the smart use of unique skills. The basis of the gameplay is the betting system, which allows you not only to increase bets in the general pot, but also to conclude side deals on the outcome of your opponents’ actions. To gain an advantage, there are tactical options such as canceling someone else&amp;rsquo;s skill, copying the last skill used, or completely upgrading your own set of abilities.</description></item><item><title>Mamorukun ReCurse!</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mamorukun-recurse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mamorukun-recurse/</guid><description>Game Description In Mamorukun ReCurse! the summoned souls, together with the main character, end up in the mysterious Underworld. A local priestess reports that the opening gates to the Dark Dimension are sending a curse on the inhabitants of this kingdom. The assembled characters are tasked with cleaning up the locals to prevent disaster. Joining forces is their only chance to return home, which sends the heroes on a journey through a strange land full of possessed enemies.</description></item><item><title>TORSO TENNIS</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/torso-tennis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/torso-tennis/</guid><description>Game Description TORSO TENNIS is about creating absurd but effective combinations of body parts and tattoos for total domination on the court. Players, controlling only one torso, will have to piece together a powerful tennis mechanism capable of independently generating chain reactions. The basis of everything is a synergy system inspired by auto-battlers, where some items act as triggers to activate the effects of others. This allows you to unleash spectacular combinations, turning each match into a unique event.</description></item><item><title>Formula Legends</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/formula-legends/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/formula-legends/</guid><description>Game Description Racers in Formula Legends have been competing in car races for several decades. The gameplay spans the period from the 1960s to the present day, offering 16 vehicle models based on historical prototypes. Races take place at 14 circuits based on famous racing locations. These tracks are not static, they change over the years and offer fresh challenges in each new era. This journey through time clearly shows the evolution of racing cars and track configurations.</description></item><item><title>Antivirus PROTOCOL</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/antivirus-protocol/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/antivirus-protocol/</guid><description>Game Description Antivirus PROTOCOL opens up a digital world captured by the ubiquitous Virus, and the gamer is given the role of counter-program. The main task is the methodical extermination of hostile elements that have filled the system. The first steps involve eliminating small pests to obtain their internal components, represented by code fragments and raw data. This process of gathering resources becomes the basis for achieving the main goal - complete cleanup of the infected network.</description></item><item><title>Professional Fishing 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/professional-fishing-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/professional-fishing-2/</guid><description>Game Description Players in Professional Fishing 2 begin their journey as novice anglers with simple equipment. The starter kit includes an old fishing rod, a reel from the 1980s, and bait bread. The landing net helps you catch prey, and the tent allows you to rest and create a save point anywhere. With the accumulation of experience and increasing levels comes progress. Selling the fish you catch earns you the currency you need to purchase upgraded equipment, which gives you access to various techniques such as float fishing, spinning and feeder methods, as well as special baits and sonar for tracking down large prey.</description></item><item><title>The Bleakest Keep</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-bleakest-keep/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-bleakest-keep/</guid><description>Game Description The Bleakest Keep sends Edward, captain of the guard, to a fortified tower to confront the dark sorcerer Cormac. The adventure begins in the cemetery outside the castle walls, and the final goal awaits at the very top of the structure. Progression involves passing through 4 different levels in the style of dark fantasy, teeming with hordes of zombies, vampires and other creatures. The main task of the player is to reach the peak, defeat the sorcerer and thereby save the kingdom from the nightmares he unleashed on these lands.</description></item><item><title>Funguys Swarm</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/funguys-swarm/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/funguys-swarm/</guid><description>Game Description Funguys Swarm places the fighter in a burning forest to confront the Fire King&amp;rsquo;s army using forest weapons and unusual abilities. There is a variety of heroes to choose from, each with unique skills for different combat approaches. The player&amp;rsquo;s main goal is to withstand continuous attacks from fiery minions and mutated vegetables, whose intensity increases over time. Survival in the top-down arena requires constant maneuvering and timely elimination of these threats.</description></item><item><title>Bendy: Lone Wolf</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bendy-lone-wolf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bendy-lone-wolf/</guid><description>Game Description Bendy: Lone Wolf sends gamers in the role of Boris deep into the endlessly generated corridors of Joey Drew&amp;rsquo;s studio in search of supplies. He will have to travel through the bizarre cartoon halls of the animation studio, filled with monsters and obstacles appearing from all sides. This foray becomes a constant test of survival in the face of increasing danger, forcing the hero to face the dark secrets hidden inside the building.</description></item><item><title>GRADIUS ORIGINS</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/gradius-origins/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/gradius-origins/</guid><description>Game Description GRADIUS ORIGINS is a collection of titles from the space shooter series. This collection includes 7 arcade titles from the history of the franchise, offering 18 different versions of them to play. The set includes the Salamander 3 title along with the original video game, including the Japanese, North American and European releases. Gamers also have access to numerous iterations of Salamander and Life Force, giving insight into the development of the arcade series.</description></item><item><title>Tower Networking Inc.</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tower-networking-inc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tower-networking-inc/</guid><description>Game Description Tower Networking Inc. puts the player at the head of an Internet provider operating in a single, constantly growing structure. The main task is to design and build network infrastructure for new clients as the tower randomly generates additional floors. Players physically connect equipment, connecting cables between switches, routers, and data risers to establish communications.
Each new level introduces unique residential or office spaces, introducing varied service requirements that require constant adaptation to the tower&amp;rsquo;s growth.</description></item><item><title>Achilles: Survivor</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/achilles-survivor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/achilles-survivor/</guid><description>Game Description Achilles: Survivor takes players into a world of intense, non-stop action where survival depends on smart decisions, quick reflexes and strong strategy. You are immersed in a scenario where thousands of enemies are trying to stop you. Your character develops, gaining more strength and capabilities after each attempt. This cycle of death and rebirth becomes the basis of your survival story. As you progress through each wave, your goal is clear: survive and become stronger for the battles ahead.</description></item><item><title>FUMES</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/fumes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/fumes/</guid><description>Game Description FUMES plunges you into the heart of a chaotic wasteland world where vehicular combat reigns. Users take control of customizable vehicles, equipping them with weapons and armor to survive the unforgiving desert landscape. The title brings an old-school feel to car combat, drawing on the style of classic rally games with driving mechanics that reflect a time before flashy graphics and complex controls. It&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced, straightforward, and has genuine tension.</description></item><item><title>Gold Miner: Classic Edition</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/gold-minerclassic-edition/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/gold-minerclassic-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Gold Miner: Classic Edition puts the player in control of a miner operating an underground winch with a 2D side-scroller perspective. The main task is to launch the swinging gripper in a timely manner to intercept and retrieve gold nuggets, precious stones and other valuables from the ground. Each level offers a new arrangement of resources under a strict time limit, requiring efficient mining of items to complete a financial goal.</description></item><item><title>Little Fighter 2 Remastered</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/little-fighter-2-remastered/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/little-fighter-2-remastered/</guid><description>Game Description Little Fighter 2 Remastered introduces an updated version of the multiplayer fighting game. This version introduces completely redrawn graphics, replacing the original assets. It enables local network gaming with up to eight computers connected, expanding multiplayer options for users on the same network. Characters' move sets have been adjusted, which affects how fighters perform actions during combat scenes. Operational improvements have been made by fixing various minor technical issues that existed previously.</description></item><item><title>Bridge Constructor Studio</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bridge-constructor-studio/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bridge-constructor-studio/</guid><description>Game Description Bridge Constructor Studio is a series of physics-based construction puzzles. The player&amp;rsquo;s task is to design structures in animated 3D mini-dioramas. The goal is to apply engineering principles to construct functional span crossings. Once the work is completed, a simulation is run to test the structural integrity of the creation under the influence of physical forces.
This process determines the stability and success of the building under the load of passing traffic, summing up the test of the architect&amp;rsquo;s intent.</description></item><item><title>The Legend of Dark Witch Episode 4</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-legend-of-dark-witch-episode-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-legend-of-dark-witch-episode-4/</guid><description>Game Description The Legend of Dark Witch Episode 4 is a continuation of a series of two-dimensional action games, the gameplay of which is based on clearing locations and strengthening the character. The visual style of the project is made in pixel graphics format. The basis for the heroine’s development is a resource called Tres, received for eliminating opponents at the level. Each location contains hidden special enemies known as Jammers.</description></item><item><title>Hopeless Sea</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/hopeless-sea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/hopeless-sea/</guid><description>Game Description Hopeless Sea imagines a world submerged after climate catastrophe melts the polar ice caps. A sea level rise of more than 50 meters has rendered 90 of the planet&amp;rsquo;s coastal cities uninhabitable, forcing survivors to move inland to escape powerful storms. Soon, a new threat emerged from the ocean depths - mutated aggressive sea creatures that began to attack the last strongholds of people.
To save civilization, a final mission is sent to the sea to find the source of the creatures and eliminate the root cause of the disaster.</description></item><item><title>Dragon Is Dead</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dragon-is-dead/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dragon-is-dead/</guid><description>Game Description Dragon Is Dead throws you headlong into a world remade by a fallen dragon. Gone are the days of majestic flight and fire, replaced by a shadowy kingdom infested with vile creatures. This is not your grandfather&amp;rsquo;s platformer - here you need not just jump and press buttons, but build a strategy for passing. Each enemy you encounter is a puzzle to solve, a challenge that requires you to adapt your tactics on the fly.</description></item><item><title>Two Strikes</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/two-strikes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/two-strikes/</guid><description>Game Description Battles in Two Strikes take users into casual duels set in the bloody period of ancient Japan. The game is made in the genre of a two-dimensional fighting game, where you have to face opponents and fight to the death, using edged weapons and martial arts skills that allow you to push your opponent away or jump over him in the arena. In battle you have to use strikes, blocks and special techniques that help open up the enemy&amp;rsquo;s vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title>Deliver At All Costs</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/deliver-at-all-costs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/deliver-at-all-costs/</guid><description>Game Description Deliver At All Costs is a courier simulator that allows you to experience the real madness and bustle of this profession. Trying to deliver a package, you will end up in constant traffic jams, ridiculous situations, etc. You need to move around the city in your used pickup truck. However, it has one feature: the ability to accelerate using nitro. Deliver At All Costs is a project that places a huge emphasis on humor and madness.</description></item><item><title>JDM: Japanese Drift Master</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/jdm-japanese-drift-master/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/jdm-japanese-drift-master/</guid><description>Game Description JDM: Japanese Drift Master is a colorful car simulator that will take you into the exciting world of drifting on the streets of Japan. A huge open world with varied landscapes, from serene lakes to bustling city areas, offers endless opportunities for exploration, racing and, of course, the art of drifting itself. What sets the game apart is the freedom it gives players to customize their cars, allowing them to truly make it their own.</description></item><item><title>Capcom Fighting Collection 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/capcom-fighting-collection-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/capcom-fighting-collection-2/</guid><description>Game Description Capcom Fighting Collection 2 brings together eight fighting games from the company&amp;rsquo;s archives. This set contains projects such as Capcom vs. SNK 2: Mark of the Millennium 2001 and Project Justice. In addition, the selection includes 3D action games such as Power Stone and Power Stone 2, representing a range of titles covering different time periods. Players have access to this set of experiences in one single edition.</description></item><item><title>Vellum</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/vellum/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/vellum/</guid><description>Game Description Vellum throws gamers into a world filled with strategic combat and decision-making. Go it alone or team up with others to overcome challenges and gain control of your journey. The main highlight of Vellum is the innovative mechanics of influencing the enemy’s development. This gives the strategy an extra layer that goes beyond simply winning the next fight.
The heart beats with collaboration. Team up with friends to overcome obstacles together.</description></item><item><title>Galactic Plague 2000</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/galactic-plague-2000/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/galactic-plague-2000/</guid><description>Game Description Galactic Plague 2000 is a large-scale space war against ruthless Martian invaders who have threatened the existence of the entire galaxy. Survival in this chaos directly depends on the constant improvement of the manned starship and unlocking legendary weapons. Each encounter with enemy squadrons becomes a real test of strength, forcing you to adapt tactics and make the most efficient use of the ship&amp;rsquo;s resources to repel the alien plague.</description></item><item><title>FATAL FURY: City of the Wolves</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/fatal-fury-city-of-the-wolves/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/fatal-fury-city-of-the-wolves/</guid><description>Game Description FATAL FURY: City of the Wolves is released as a new chapter in the fighting game series, 26 years after the release of the previous main part. This project includes mechanics that provide special offensive capabilities from the very beginning of the fight. It covers the moves REV Arts, REV Accel and REV Blows (with S.P.G. active), and its use is limited by the REV Meter, which overheats from intensive use.</description></item><item><title>Viscerafest</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/viscerafest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/viscerafest/</guid><description>Game Description Viscerafest is a dynamic shooter made in retro style. The game takes you into a sci-fi world where you have to fight alien invaders and various creepy monsters. The arsenal of weapons consists of various futuristic guns. Allows you to take the barrel in your hand to destroy enemies, shooting Macedonian style. Events take place in 3796.
The main character of Viscerafest is named Caroline. She is a mercenary and a psychopath rolled into one.</description></item><item><title>Monaco 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/monaco-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/monaco-2/</guid><description>Game Description Monaco 2 invites the player to assemble a specialized squad to carry out cunning heist operations. The main setting is the city of Monaco, presented as a location with many valuable targets due to the wealth concentrated there. Gamers embody members of an international group of criminal specialists seeking to exploit these conditions for material gain. Success requires careful movement through locations, bypassing security and retrieving intended valuables in a tense environment.</description></item><item><title>Driveloop: Survivors</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/driveloop-survivors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/driveloop-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Driveloop: Survivors puts the player behind the wheel of a rigged car as it navigates a dangerous urban landscape following an unspecified disaster. Gamers will use driving techniques, including skidding and ramming, along with shooting to destroy opponents in a steampunk style. You need to withstand the onslaught of enemy waves in destroyed cities. Success depends on maneuvering the vehicle, choosing an attack position and avoiding threats on the battlefield.</description></item><item><title>Slime Squisher</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/slime-squisher/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/slime-squisher/</guid><description>Game Description Slime Squisher is an arcade project that combines roguelike and clicker mechanics, where the main task is to protect a defenseless berry. The basis for successful completion is the creation of unique assemblies from many improvements, which are unlocked after repelling each enemy wave. The gamer has an extensive arsenal at his disposal, allowing him to customize tactics to suit his style of combat. Progression is implemented through a system of permanent upgrades acquired between runs, which adds strategic depth to the process.</description></item><item><title>Vaporwave Pinball</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/vaporwave-pinball/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/vaporwave-pinball/</guid><description>Game Description Vaporwave Pinball is about immersing yourself in the relaxing atmosphere of liminal spaces, presented in the form of a tiny fantasy operating system. The process unfolds on several tables, each of which immerses you in a unique environment. The locations include both indoor pools and outdoor areas with black and white checkered floors. As you progress, new, more complex arenas open up, requiring honing your skills. Some of them are made in an unexpected horror style, adding a touch of tension to the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>cheapskate</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/cheapskate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/cheapskate/</guid><description>Game Description cheapskate is an arcade skateboarding simulator where the gameplay philosophy is based on complete freedom of action and self-expression. The mechanics are based on predictable and responsive arcade physics, completely eliminating any elements of uncontrolled realism. Precise digital controls provide complete control over every movement, allowing you to perform tricks with great stability. The project is aimed at both veterans of the genre and newcomers, offering a low barrier to entry, but at the same time motivating them to hone their skills.</description></item><item><title>STORROR Parkour Pro</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/storror-parkour-pro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/storror-parkour-pro/</guid><description>Game Description STORROR Parkour Pro is a parkour simulator set in the Isle of Dogs, London. Users navigate these urban environments using a set of motor abilities derived from the discipline of parkour. Available actions include jumping, climbing, overcoming obstacles, somersaulting, sliding, swinging and running across rooftops and streets. The character&amp;rsquo;s movement is provided by an animation system that combines motion capture data from parkour athletes with physics calculations to depict dynamics.</description></item><item><title>Warm Monkey</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/warm-monkey/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/warm-monkey/</guid><description>Game Description Warm Monkey is about a desperate struggle for survival in the heart of a concrete jungle, where a troop of small monkeys multiplies under the scorching sun. Instead of the traditional health scale, there is an inexorably decreasing thirst indicator, forcing you to constantly look for saving moisture. The behavior of their relatives, appearing every 10 seconds, is unpredictable: they can fall from a height or run out onto the roadway under the wheels of scooters.</description></item><item><title>Speedboat Simulator</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/speedboat-simulator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/speedboat-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Speedboat Simulator is a realistic racing simulator where gamers will take control of powerful high-speed boats to participate in water competitions. The main arena for the competition is the picturesque Hawaiian waters, offering many challenging routes. Each available vessel has individual handling and speed parameters, which requires the pilot to constantly adapt his driving style to the specific conditions of the race. Success in racing directly depends on the ability to feel the technique and effectively use its strengths on various sections of the route.</description></item><item><title>Reality Break</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/reality-break/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/reality-break/</guid><description>Game Description Reality Break takes a unique approach to the ARPG genre, combining fast-paced action with roguelite elements for fresh and unpredictable gameplay. At its core, this is a management game. You play as a mercenary who suddenly gains the ability to distort reality, throwing you into a whirlwind of constant change and danger. As you progress, you will face challenges that require more than just combat skills - it is your mastery of reality control that will determine the outcome.</description></item><item><title>Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lonely-mountains-snow-riders/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lonely-mountains-snow-riders/</guid><description>Game Description Lonely Mountains: Snow Riders offers gamers a new look at the snowy slopes. The title takes the core elements of its predecessor and adds new twists, offering users the opportunity to navigate the mountains in both relaxed and competitive modes. The fun begins when you start heading down the slopes, encountering everything from icy lakes to hairpin turns. It&amp;rsquo;s all about finding your rhythm while pushing the boundaries of your skill.</description></item><item><title>Dragon Ruins 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dragon-ruins-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dragon-ruins-2/</guid><description>Game Description In Dragon Ruins 2, ancient dragons and forgotten treasures are central to the journey. At the beginning, users assemble a squad of four adventurers, each of whom has their own abilities and goals. As you progress through various quests, battles happen automatically, allowing gamers to focus on strategy and planning rather than constant action. In this world, treasure hunting is not just about collecting items, but about uncovering a long-forgotten history full of secrets.</description></item><item><title>Talented</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/talented/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/talented/</guid><description>Game Description Talented is an arcade roguelite shoot &amp;lsquo;em up that throws gamers into a chaotic world where survival is key. The project revolves around the character Ed, who will spend 20 nights on the infamous Demon Conveyor Belt (D.C.B). Each night presents him with new challenges as waves of enemies come inexorably, and Ed can only adapt and use a combination of abilities and upgrades to stay alive.
The randomness-focused structure makes each session feel different, as no two playthroughs are the same.</description></item><item><title>Winter Games Collection</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/winter-games-collection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/winter-games-collection/</guid><description>Game Description Winter Games Collection brings together a variety of winter-themed titles that will provide exciting entertainment for gamers of all ages. The project offers a variety of entertainment, from exciting snowball fights to exciting ice races, all in a festive winter setting. The combination of arcade style and family fun ensures that the game will be fun, whether you want to enjoy a solo adventure or gather a group of friends for competitive fun.</description></item><item><title>Entropy Survivors</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/entropy-survivors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/entropy-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Entropy Survivors is a fast-paced bullet hell roguelike that combines frantic action with unique mechanics. Here, gamers control both a massive mech and a pointy-eared space frog, creating an unusual pair of characters with different abilities. In single or co-op play, gamers must control both units as they fight their way through waves of enemies, each offering their own set of challenges. Gameplay is designed to test reflexes, strategy and timing, requiring quick decision making as users dodge bullets and land their own blows.</description></item><item><title>Relic Dudes</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/relic-dudes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/relic-dudes/</guid><description>Game Description Relic Dudes is an online multiplayer game that can be played alone or with up to four friends. It&amp;rsquo;s a survivor-style action RPG where you work together or fight against each other to defeat hordes of different types of enemies. Gamers can collect relics, become stronger, and create unique kits that can change the fate of their team.
Both single-player and multiplayer online modes are implemented, which makes it possible to choose a specific gaming style.</description></item><item><title>Dungeon Clawler</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dungeon-clawler/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dungeon-clawler/</guid><description>Game Description Dungeon Clawler is a deep dive into the dark and unpredictable world of dungeons, where every step could be the beginning of a new legend. The interweaving of mysterious corridors leading to halls shrouded in twilight creates a feeling of continuous discovery of secrets. There are no easy solutions here—treacherous traps, ancient puzzles, and creatures whose origins are shrouded in speculation and fear await the player.
Each encounter is a test of character: you can rush into a frontal attack, try to hide in the shadows, or try to find a workaround so as not to get involved in an unnecessary conflict.</description></item><item><title>Tricky Madness</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tricky-madness/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tricky-madness/</guid><description>Game Description Tricky Madness is making its way onto the indie gaming scene, promising a wild ride for snowboarding enthusiasts. This adventure game is inspired by classic arcade snowboard games like SSX and 1080, so strap on your virtual board and get ready for some adrenaline-pumping action. The mountain is calling: Buckle up and get ready to fall down the treacherous slopes. This is not just the finish line, it is exploring and overcoming the boundaries of your capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Bullet Runner</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bullet-runner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bullet-runner/</guid><description>Game Description The dynamic shootouts inBullet Runner show the adventures of a pixelated man who is forced to resist against a crowd of evil opponents. The game is a top-down action shooter where you have to fight with various opponents. The project is filled with fast and active gameplay, where users can test the speed of their reaction to current events. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to move around the map and shoot enemies using a wide arsenal of weapons.</description></item><item><title>Social Soccer 25</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sociable-soccer-25/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sociable-soccer-25/</guid><description>Game Description Sociable Soccer 25 brings a new level of excitement to the world of soccer video games. It&amp;rsquo;s an adventure game that stands out in a crowded market by offering fast-paced, arcade-style gameplay that keeps users on their toes. Gone are the days of overly complex management; The title allows gamers to immerse themselves in the action without requiring a complex learning curve. Once you start, you&amp;rsquo;re ready to hit the field, and whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned gamer or just picking up a controller for the first time, you&amp;rsquo;ll quickly get hooked.</description></item><item><title>Shave and Stuff</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/shave-and-stuff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/shave-and-stuff/</guid><description>Game Description InShave and Stuff, gamers find themselves in a lively and practical simulator, where two roles come to the fore - a hairdresser and a tattoo artist. The title combines hairdressing and paint work, which promotes creativity and experimentation. Whether performing precision cutting tasks or plunging into the complex world of body art, users are immersed in a world of tools, techniques and client preferences. A constant flow of tasks and light humor provide the basis for an original approach to customization and self-expression.</description></item><item><title>Tetris Forever</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tetris-forever/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tetris-forever/</guid><description>Game Description Tetris Forever marks a milestone in the history of one of the most famous puzzle games, celebrating the 40th anniversary of Tetris. The collection contains more than 15 different versions, from early versions for Electronika 60 in 1984 to more recent ones, such as Hatris and Super Bombliss DX1, which many users may not have encountered before. The inclusion of these lesser-known games is a treat for those who are passionate about the evolution of Tetris and want to explore its varied history.</description></item><item><title>XENOTILT: HOSTILE PINBALL ACTION</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/xenotilt-hostile-pinball-action/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/xenotilt-hostile-pinball-action/</guid><description>Game Description XENOTILT: HOSTILE PINBALL ACTION transports gamers to a high-octane world where the classic game of pinball meets hostile forces for an intense blend of arcade action. The adventure follows the path of its predecessor, Demon&amp;rsquo;s Tilt, and brings familiar gameplay mechanics while adding many new challenges. Each new table offers a new set of obstacles, targets and bonuses that force users to be on their guard. Pinball here is not just about throwing a ball, it is a battle against time, enemies and your own reflexes.</description></item><item><title>Locuras en el Banverso</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/locuras-en-el-banaverso/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/locuras-en-el-banaverso/</guid><description>Game Description Locuras en el Banaverso is a single-player platformer that takes gamers on a chaotic adventure through a bizarre multiverse. The game follows the eccentric YouTuber El Bananero, who not only plays the role of the main character, but also voices him. From the very beginning, El Bananero finds himself in an unexpected situation - he is kidnapped by none other than Santa Claus and his gang of henchmen. As fate would have it, the kidnapping turns into an escape through a portal that leads him into the depths of the multiverse.</description></item><item><title>Taiko no Tatsujin: Rhythm Festival</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/taiko-no-tatsujin-rhythm-festival/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/taiko-no-tatsujin-rhythm-festival/</guid><description>Game Description Taiko no Tatsujin: Rhythm Festival is a delightful rhythm game in which users go on an exciting adventure with Don-chan, a cute drummer, and his new friend Kumo-kyun, an adorable cloud-like creature. The rhythmic escapade takes place in the city of Omiko, where the duo strives to rise to the level of taiko masters. The game offers gamers two modes: an interesting story mode with Don-chan and Kumo-kyun, and a rhythm-rich Taiko, which features 76 songs of various genres - from anime anthems to pop hits, classical compositions and original tracks.</description></item><item><title>Outbreak: Shades of Horror Chromatic Split</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/outbreak-shades-of-horror-chromatic-split/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/outbreak-shades-of-horror-chromatic-split/</guid><description>Game Description Outbreak: Shades of Horror Chromatic Split takes users into the disturbing environment of Cypress Ridge, where chaos reigns amid a zombie outbreak. Set in the early moments of this disaster, gamers are given the choice of one of two different characters: Lydia, a seasoned police officer, or Hank, a figure shrouded in mystery whose goals differ sharply from Lydia&amp;rsquo;s. These choices affect how users interact with the narrative, resulting in different experiences as they navigate a city filled with danger.</description></item><item><title>Vengeance Hunters</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/vengeance-hunters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/vengeance-hunters/</guid><description>Game Description Vengeance Hunters is a side-scrolling beat-&amp;lsquo;em-up that captures the essence of classic arcade action. Here users can choose one of several characters, each of which has different abilities and fighting styles. These choices play an important role in how gamers approach gaming challenges. Going through various stages, users encounter many enemies, each of which has unique behavior and attack style. With a variety of characters, gamers will be able to find the fighting style that suits their preferences.</description></item><item><title>Speedollama</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/speedollama/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/speedollama/</guid><description>Game Description Speedollama is a fast-paced platform shooter that takes gamers into a world where llamas battle an army of alpacas. The unusual premise draws users into a chaotic world where humor and action collide in the most unexpected ways. The goal is simple: control a llama equipped with a mining machine and destroy waves of alpaca enemies. The title features a vibrant environment filled with quirky characters and varied challenges, making every moment exciting.</description></item><item><title>Up to Par</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/up-to-par/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/up-to-par/</guid><description>Game Description Up to Par is more than just minigolf! Take on procedurally generated levels with up to 16 friends or alone, but remember that every hit counts. Stay below par to avoid being eliminated from the game! You will have to show your skills and planning to progress as far as possible and unlock the next course. Can you beat your record? Will you be able to defeat your friends?</description></item><item><title>Tech Store Simulator</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tech-store-simulator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tech-store-simulator/</guid><description>Game Description Tech Store Simulator immerses gamers in the fast-paced world of tech retail, giving them hands-on experience in running their own electronics store. The title&amp;rsquo;s focus is on strategic decision-making, requiring users to balance inventory management with customer satisfaction. Gamers will have to navigate the ins and outs of running a successful tech business, from stocking shelves with the latest gadgets to setting competitive prices.
Hiring and managing staff is another key aspect of the game to keep the store running smoothly and efficiently.</description></item><item><title>Victory Heat Rally</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/victory-heat-rally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/victory-heat-rally/</guid><description>Game Description Victory Heat Rally is a retro racing game inspired by arcade games of the last century, such as Hang-On and OutRun. You have to take control of small cars to rush along various difficult tracks at high speed. The gameplay is hardcore and pays homage to the classic games of yesteryear.
To fully master the mechanics of Victory Heat Rally, you will need to learn how to glide around the track, take corners correctly, and feel the road.</description></item><item><title>Dwarven Realms</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dwarven-realms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dwarven-realms/</guid><description>Game Description Dwarven Realms is an action-oriented 3D ARPG that invites gamers to immerse themselves in a realm filled with intense combat and deep character customization. Users will have to explore vast underground kingdoms and navigate treacherous caves, facing insurmountable waves of enemies. The gameplay emphasizes a variety of combat techniques, allowing you to choose your preferred style, be it using a bow or spells. The design encourages players to create a unique character, unlocking different abilities suited to different combat strategies.</description></item><item><title>Iron Meat</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/iron-meat/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/iron-meat/</guid><description>Game Description Iron Meat is a dynamic platformer made in the style of arcade shooters of the last century. The game takes place on Mars, when a group of scientists disappeared from radar without a trace. The case is entrusted to a member of an elite squad who goes in search of missing people. He must find out what really happened and who is behind this mysterious event.
The gameplay takes inspiration from classic action games such as Contra.</description></item><item><title>Halls of Torment</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/halls-of-torment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/halls-of-torment/</guid><description>Game Description Halls of Torment invites you into the world of terrifying monsters in this unique action game with roguelite elements, where you will face new challenges and dangers in each game. Dive into the dark and ruthless dungeons where the lords of the underworld await you. Find treasures and magical artifacts, and assemble a team of heroes who will help you defeat the horrors emanating from the depths of the earth.</description></item><item><title>Rally Arcade Classics</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rally-arcade-classics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rally-arcade-classics/</guid><description>Game Description Rally Arcade Classics takes gamers into the heart of rally racing history, bringing classic arcade gaming to the world of motorsports. With 44 cars from four different decades - the 70s, 80s, 90s and 00s - you&amp;rsquo;ll get a look at the cars that helped shape the rally scene. There&amp;rsquo;s a wide variety of iconic cars here, each offering its own set of challenges and driving features. In addition to the impressive list of cars, there are 48 tracks, each designed for a different type of racing.</description></item><item><title>The Karate Kid: Street Rumble</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-karate-kid-street-rumble/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-karate-kid-street-rumble/</guid><description>Game Description The Karate Kid: Street Rumble is a beat &amp;lsquo;em up title that immerses you in the world of the cult trilogy. Users step into the shoes of characters such as Daniel LaRusso, Mr. Miyagi, Ali Mills and Kumiko as they battle through various levels inspired by the films. The game has a side-scrolling format in which players face waves of enemies, including famous antagonists such as Johnny Lawrence, John Croesus and Terry Silver.</description></item><item><title>Slackers - Carts of Glory</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/slackers-carts-of-glory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/slackers-carts-of-glory/</guid><description>Game Description Slackers - Carts of Glory is a racing adventure game that is something out of the ordinary. Instead of racing along the highway in luxury cars, you&amp;rsquo;re pushing a shopping cart. Yes, you heard right. It&amp;rsquo;s like playing supermarket, but with more fun and chaos. The basic idea is simple: you are part of a group of friends and try to get to the store before it closes. But what is the difficulty?</description></item><item><title>UFO 50</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ufo-50/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ufo-50/</guid><description>Game Description The UFO 50 project is a collection of single and multiplayer games made in different genres, such as platformers, shooters, puzzles, roguelike or role-playing adventures. The style is made in old school retro graphics, which creates an 8-bit aesthetic in the design of locations. Each of the fifty video games gives you the opportunity to try out full-fledged gameplay with different levels, where there is a beginning and an end to the single-player campaign.</description></item><item><title>Judero</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/judero/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/judero/</guid><description>Game Description Judero immerses you in the world of strategic decisions and tactical battles. The title combines elements of role-playing and strategy, requiring gamers to go through various challenges and opponents. Users must manage resources, create alliances and make important decisions that will affect the outcome of their journey. In Judero, users encounter a variety of characters, each with unique abilities and history. These characters can be recruited into the player&amp;rsquo;s team, giving them various tactical advantages in battle.</description></item><item><title>Grapple Dogs: Cosmic Canines</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/grapple-dogs-cosmic-canines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/grapple-dogs-cosmic-canines/</guid><description>Game Description Grapple Dogs: Cosmic Canines is a 2D action platformer that follows the adventures of Pablo and Luna. Users move through different dimensions, using unique abilities to overcome obstacles and enemies. It combines swinging, jumping and explosions to provide dynamic gameplay. In the title, gamers alternate between the characters Pablo and Luna. Pablo uses a grappling hook to progress through levels, while Luna brings her own set of skills to the table.</description></item><item><title>Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/test-drive-unlimited-solar-crown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/test-drive-unlimited-solar-crown/</guid><description>Game Description Test Drive Unlimited Solar Crown – restart of a series of arcade racing games. You can feel the vibration of hundreds of horses under the hood with modern graphics and physics. You can choose from top-notch hypercars from legendary manufacturers such as Koenigsegg, Porsche, Dodge, Ferrari, Lamborghini or Bugatti. It is worth understanding that luxury cars will require experience and skills, so you need to open them gradually. Each vehicle can be modified and customized to suit your preferences.</description></item><item><title>Turbo Sliders Unlimited</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/turbo-sliders-unlimited/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/turbo-sliders-unlimited/</guid><description>Game Description Turbo Sliders Unlimited is an opportunity to plunge into racing competitions in multiplayer or single player mode, where users can tune cars. The gameplay is made in the form of arcade races with a top view, where users will compete with racers on various professional tracks. The game has a special editor, which allows you to design your own levels, locations, vehicles and flexibly customize tournament modes.
In the multiplayer &amp;ldquo;Turbo Sliders Unlimited&amp;rdquo; up to 20 people (including observers) can participate simultaneously, which is suitable for creating e-sports tests.</description></item><item><title>I Am Your Beast</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/i-am-your-beast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/i-am-your-beast/</guid><description>Game Description I Am Your Beast is not your average shooter. This narrative-driven game throws you headlong into a brutal conflict with the shadowy organization you once worked for. You play as Alphonse Harding, a former operative who has been lured back into the world of underground warfare. Survival and thinking quickly are key. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to navigate treacherous terrain, dodging and fighting enemies in a high-stakes chase.
Forget about going with guns at the ready.</description></item><item><title>Rugrats: Adventures in Gameland</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rugrats-adventures-in-gameland/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rugrats-adventures-in-gameland/</guid><description>Game Description Rugrats: Adventures in Gameland is a new action-platformer that brings beloved characters from the 1990s Nickelodeon series into a vibrant, imaginative world. Together with Tommy, Chucky, Phil and Lil, users will go on an adventure inspired by their favorite video game character, Reptar. The title features a unique co-op design that allows gamers to form teams and complete various levels located in the Pickles' home. The gameplay of Rugrats: Adventures in Gameland revolves around exploration and teamwork.</description></item><item><title>Utopia Must Fall</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/utopia-must-fall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/utopia-must-fall/</guid><description>Game Description Utopia Must Fall is a basic defense arcade shooter where gamers take on the role of humanity&amp;rsquo;s last line of defense against an alien invasion. The action takes place in a post-apocalyptic metropolis, and players will have to defend the city from relentless waves of alien aggressors. The gameplay of Utopia Must Fall is based on strategic resource management and quick decision making. Gamers must carefully manage their resources to upgrade their defenses and purchase new weapons, ensuring they are properly prepared for the challenges ahead.</description></item><item><title>Guns And Draguns</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/guns-and-draguns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/guns-and-draguns/</guid><description>Game Description Guns And Draguns is a top-down co-op shooter that plunges gamers into a dangerous fantasy dungeon. Here users will have to go through various levels, destroying fantasy monsters with weapons. The main goal is to defeat the final boss, but along the way there are enemies and obstacles that require strategic teamwork and cooperation. Gamers can choose one of seven unique characters, each of which has its own abilities.</description></item><item><title>Smells Like a Mushroom</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/smells-like-a-mushroom/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/smells-like-a-mushroom/</guid><description>Game Description Smells Like a Mushroom is a sci-fi third-person shooter that takes gamers on a journey through the Milky Way. At the center is an invasion of creatures known as Magic Mushrooms. Users take on the role of Carrotado, a brave character tasked with preventing disaster. The gameplay includes platformer and shooter mechanics, and missions take place on various planets in the solar system.
Smells Like a Mushroom&amp;rsquo;s narrative is driven by an absurd story and features both single-player and co-op modes.</description></item><item><title>Call of Sentinels</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/call-of-sentinels/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/call-of-sentinels/</guid><description>Game Description Call of Sentinels plunges you headlong into an epic struggle against the forces of darkness. Choose your champion from a growing list, each with unique skills and fighting styles. Hone your combat skills against the relentless hordes in the Arena, or take on dangerous journeys across varied landscapes in Campaign. Unleash devastating combos and master tactical maneuvers to defeat treacherous enemies and colossal bosses. Each victory unlocks valuable upgrades, expanding the hero&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and shaping his legend.</description></item><item><title>CarX Street</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/carx-street/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/carx-street/</guid><description>Game Description TheCarX Street car simulator allows you to build your own car and hit the streets to conquer the whole city. The metropolis is presented on a huge scale, including its surroundings: city streets, industrial area, picturesque highways, etc. CarX Streets features drifting, high-speed chases, heavy traffic and intense competition in online races.
The main feature of the game is the possibility of deep car customization and wide tuning possibilities.</description></item><item><title>Monster Jam Showdown</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/monster-jam-showdown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/monster-jam-showdown/</guid><description>Game Description Monster Jam Showdown is an adrenaline-pumping off-road racing experience that is sure to get your heart racing. Gamers can get behind the wheel of iconic monster trucks and compete in a variety of challenging environments. From dirt tracks to stadiums, the game offers a variety of racing arenas. The project has ten different modes and is designed for users of any level of training. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned veteran or just a new rider, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Supermoves</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/supermoves/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/supermoves/</guid><description>Game Description Supermoves - This parkour party promises wild fun. Users sprint, jump and grind the rails in intense challenges. Bomb Tag, Rising Tide and Royale modes offer different thrills. Up to forty gamers can race, pursue and compete. Makea Games' level editor allows users to create their own experiences. Makeaverse is waiting for you. Everyone can dive in, build and play.
Supermoves combines competition and creativity. Casual players and parkour professionals will find their place.</description></item><item><title>MT Force Aliens Uprising</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mt-force-aliens-uprising/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mt-force-aliens-uprising/</guid><description>Game Description MT Force Aliens Uprising is a fast-paced action game that combines sci-fi elements with old-school gameplay. The setting, in which a government team known as MT Force must confront the chaos caused by a scientist&amp;rsquo;s contact with alien forces, offers a title with a plot that keeps gamers on the edge of their seats. The world leans into the retro vibes of the 1980s and 1990s, combining both side-scrolling platformer and shooter action.</description></item><item><title>Nova Drift</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nova-drift/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nova-drift/</guid><description>Game Description Nova Drift is a top-down action RPG adventure. The gamer has the opportunity to test his strength in piloting a space fighter, forced to fight enemies that are superior in numbers and firepower. The spaceship uses unusual technologies; it is created using biomechanics, which means that it seems to be alive and is constantly changing both in appearance and in terms of available weapons. Thanks to the addition of artificial intelligence trained in procedural random generation, the developers from a small indie formation were able to achieve almost endless replayability.</description></item><item><title>Old School Rally</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/old-school-rally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/old-school-rally/</guid><description>Game Description In Old School Rally, users get behind the wheel of fire-breathing rally cars that spit dust and gravel as they make their way through unforgiving landscapes. Forget about fancy bells and whistles - the main thing here is pure, unadulterated driving skill. Racers must think, react quickly and tame their wild stallions in a variety of conditions. Each track throws a unique gauntlet at the gamer. One moment you might be struggling for control on a dusty desert highway, and the next you might be on treacherous snow and ice.</description></item><item><title>Be My Horde</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/be-my-horde/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/be-my-horde/</guid><description>Game Description In Be My Horde, users play the role of Moriana, a necromancer. The world is dangerous, but Moriana has a unique ability: turning fallen enemies into an army. Death is not the end, it is a resource. The gameplay revolves around resurrection. Every enemy defeated becomes a soldier in Moriana&amp;rsquo;s horde. Their souls fuel her growth, giving her new abilities. Her base, Dominion, serves as a hub for ability upgrades.</description></item><item><title>Bloody Knuckles Street Boxing</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bloody-knuckles-street-boxing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bloody-knuckles-street-boxing/</guid><description>Game Description Bloody Knuckles Street Boxing challenges those looking for shallow arcade-style fights, focusing solely on skill. The project deliberately creates a deep gap in the level of training of fighters, abandoning any auxiliary systems. There is no room for easy victories here, because every aspect of the battle is under complete control. Thanks to pressure-sensitive controls, the fighter becomes an accurate reflection of the gamer&amp;rsquo;s actions, requiring tactical understanding and lightning-fast reactions.</description></item><item><title>JustAxe</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/justaxe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/justaxe/</guid><description>Game Description JustAxe is the adventure of a young girl named Marta, who must save her sister from the clutches of mysterious creatures that have invaded her hometown of Novy Sovetsk. Having received a mysterious letter indicating the path to salvation, the heroine arms herself with her grandfather’s ax and sets off on a dangerous journey. Her path runs through picturesque but dangerous locations: from forests and mountains to a gloomy other dimension from where the invaders came.</description></item><item><title>Bang Average Football</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bang-average-football/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bang-average-football/</guid><description>Game Description Bang Average Football brings new energy to the world of sports games. Here, gamers are immersed in fast-paced matches with an intuitive setup that makes it accessible to anyone who wants to kick a virtual ball around. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re playing with friends in a multiplayer match or challenging yourself in Story mode, there&amp;rsquo;s always something to keep you busy. The title is not about perfection, but about enjoying an imperfect but compelling approach to football.</description></item><item><title>Footgun: Underground</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/footgun-underground/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/footgun-underground/</guid><description>Game Description Footgun: Underground throws you into a chaotic mix of football and roguelike action. You emerge from cryogenic sleep into a strange post-apocalyptic future, equipped with a cybernetic leg, a ball and amnesia. This underground world is infested with mutants, and your trusty ball is your only defense. Footgun: Underground offers a unique twist. Instead of swords, guns or magic, you rely solely on your ball skills. Think classic roguelike: explore procedurally generated rooms, fight a variety of creatures, and upgrade your gear.</description></item><item><title>Moorhuhn - Crazy Chicken Traps and Treasures</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/moorhuhn-crazy-chicken-traps-and-treasures/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/moorhuhn-crazy-chicken-traps-and-treasures/</guid><description>Game Description Moorhuhn - Crazy Chicken Traps and Treasures is a fast-paced arcade adventure full of danger and ancient secrets, set in an impenetrable jungle. On the way to his cherished goal, the main character is confronted not only by ingenious traps, but also by a whole string of colorful opponents. The path is blocked by evil gorillas, ferocious crocodiles, mysterious shamans and even forest spirits, along with aliens stuck in the thicket.</description></item><item><title>Contra: Operation Galuga</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/contra-operation-galuga/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/contra-operation-galuga/</guid><description>Game Description Contra: Operation Galuga, the latest installment in the legendary Contra series, delivers a nostalgic adrenaline rush for fans and newcomers alike. This run-and-gun reimagining of the classic &amp;rsquo;80s action film offers a new take on the iconic franchise. Players embark on a high-octane adventure as elite Contra commandos Bill Riser and Lance Bean. Their task is to prevent the Red Falcon terrorist group from seizing the Galuga Islands near New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Balatro</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/balatro/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/balatro/</guid><description>Game Description Balatro - the word &amp;ldquo;poker&amp;rdquo; crackles with energy, whispering promises of high stakes and cunning deals. This poker roguelike beckons players into a deck-building odyssey where bluffing becomes the spell and chips become your lifeblood. Forget about limping into pots with low pairs. Here you create powerful synergies by weaving intricate combinations that unleash explosive power. Valid poker hands dance with unique wild cards, their abilities changing the course of the game like a magician.</description></item><item><title>Cash Cow DX</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/cash-cow-dx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/cash-cow-dx/</guid><description>Game Description Cash Cow DX immerses users in an exciting arcade adventure reminiscent of 80s vibes. Gamers take on the role of a character who has to win wealth from the notorious Pig Pockets. As gamers progress through five multi-screen levels, they are faced with various obstacles and challenges that test their skills. The title is characterized by a high level of difficulty that does not allow continuations, which increases the stakes for each move.</description></item><item><title>Deep Rock Galactic: Survivor</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/deep-rock-galactic-survivor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/deep-rock-galactic-survivor/</guid><description>Game Description Deep Rock Galactic: Survivor is not your average survival game, but a single-player, addictive auto-shooting game that is sure to keep you on your toes. As a lone dwarf, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to use every weapon in your arsenal to fight off waves of deadly aliens while earning riches and unlocking powerful upgrades.
But don&amp;rsquo;t think this will be an easy task. You will have to face the harsh and unforgiving landscape of the planet Hoxes, and only your wits and weapons can protect you.</description></item><item><title>Skibidi Toilets: Invasion</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/skibidi-toilets-invasion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/skibidi-toilets-invasion/</guid><description>Game Description Skibidi Toilets: Invasion throws you into a whirlwind of cyborg toilet chaos. Play as a secret agent armed with an arsenal of weapons tasked with quelling a toilet rebellion. Unleash your fury in seven diverse environments, from desolate cityscapes to chilling graveyards, each presenting unique strategic challenges. Welcome to a world where porcelain turns into brawl. This exciting FPS will pit you against rebel toilets, each of which has more firepower than a regular toilet plunger.</description></item><item><title>Tekken 8</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tekken-8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tekken-8/</guid><description>Game Description Tekken 8 is a continuation of the cult fighting game, directly continuing the story of the previous part. In the sequel, many beloved heroes return, and new fighters are introduced. A full-fledged story campaign is presented, telling the dramatic story of Jin Kazama&amp;rsquo;s family. In addition, you will find many different modes, including multiplayer battles, various tests, local co-op, the ability to customize fighters, etc.
The gameplay of Tekken 8 is based on a complex combat system based on memorizing combinations and timings of opponents.</description></item><item><title>Just Click The Button</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/just-click-the-button/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/just-click-the-button/</guid><description>Game Description Just Click The Button is an unusual project where the central element is a single button, and pressing it multiple times launches a whole chain of gameplay transformations. The whole process comes down to a choice between endless development and the desire to achieve one of the four available endings. The path to each of the finals directly depends on the chosen strategy. The combination of acquired abilities determines the ease of passing and achieving a specific outcome, which encourages the deliberate formation of your style.</description></item><item><title>SUPER CRAZY RHYTHM CASTLE</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/super-crazy-rhythm-castle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/super-crazy-rhythm-castle/</guid><description>Game Description SUPER CRAZY RHYTHM CASTLE will take you to a bizarre world filled with absurdity and frivolity. The mission is clear: defeat the eccentric King Ferdinand and restore rhythmic order to the kingdom. The game features a motley crew of unlikely heroes who must overcome bizarre challenges. From launching beans in an ancient summoning ritual to drowning out a colossal eggplant DJ and smearing gravy on tiny meat people - all while keeping the beat - the journey is a surreal mixture of music and adventure.</description></item><item><title>The Elephant Collection</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-elephant-collection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-elephant-collection/</guid><description>Game Description The Elephant Collection is a collection that features the blue elephant in ten different games. These adventure games span a variety of genres, including puzzle platformers and fast-paced arcade games. Gamers are faced with various mechanics, each of which offers its own set of obstacles and challenges. An overarching narrative runs throughout the collection, tying the individual adventures together and creating a cohesive experience for those who immerse themselves in the game.</description></item><item><title>Mostroscopy</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mostroscopy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mostroscopy/</guid><description>Game Description Mostroscope is a title that draws heavily on the traditions of classic arcade combat, combining elements of the horror genre and Mexican luchador films of the 1950s. Set against a backdrop of monsters and masked wrestlers, this adventure game has a distinctive atmosphere reminiscent of old movies, while offering simple but fun combat mechanics. Most of the time, fighting games tend to be cluttered with overly complex systems. However, the gameplay here is accessible, and the control scheme, inspired by classics like Smash Bros and Street Fighter x Tekken, allows users to quickly jump into the action without requiring a steep learning curve.</description></item><item><title>Cavalry Girls</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/cavalry-girls/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/cavalry-girls/</guid><description>Game Description Cavalry Girls is an exciting top-down shooter that immerses you in a futuristic world where brave and fearless girl soldiers fight unforgiving enemies. This addicting game seamlessly combines action, strategy and customization to deliver an immersive gaming experience. In a world where the versatile mineral &amp;ldquo;jade&amp;rdquo; fuels a bionic revolution and sparks conflict, players take on the role of commander of a team that directs mechanized armor-piercing girls to defend a besieged city from enemy forces.</description></item><item><title>Ray'z Arcade Chronology</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rayz-arcade-chronology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rayz-arcade-chronology/</guid><description>Game Description Rayz Arcade Chronology is a collection that invites you to immerse yourself in the digital space, where the Waverider manned fighter is presented as a virus, whose main task is to penetrate deep into the system. The mission, known as Operation RayCrisis, is to fight against the self-aware neurocomputer Con-Human who has rebelled against humanity.
Advancement through levels is associated with a unique Encroachment mechanic: if you do not destroy enemies quickly enough, a special meter is filled, and when 100% is reached, you are forced to move to the final clash, which directly affects the outcome of the entire operation.</description></item><item><title>DriveCrazy</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/drivecrazy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/drivecrazy/</guid><description>Game Description DriveCrazy is an arcade madness that asks you to get behind the wheel of a miniature truck amid the total destruction of the apocalyptic landscapes of Japan. The main task is to survive in the face of constant pursuit by mysterious creatures. To avoid missiles and falling buildings, it is possible to move along vertical surfaces. The process of destroying environmental objects, such as pillars, trees and fences, is directly related to replenishing the supply of nitro acceleration.</description></item><item><title>Super Raft Boat Together</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/super-raft-boat-together/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/super-raft-boat-together/</guid><description>Game Description Super Raft Boat Together is an adventure for those who love danger and teamwork! In a world inundated by a mysterious flood, you and your trusty boat are all that&amp;rsquo;s left. But don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid! Along with three friends, you&amp;rsquo;ll battle ruthless sea creatures as you build and expand your raft to reach the final island, where the truth about the flood will finally be revealed. This multiplayer roguelike shooter offers endless excitement as you navigate a variety of breathtaking biomes, strategically choosing trinkets to create the ultimate, super-powered structure.</description></item><item><title>Punch Club 2: Fast Forward</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/punch-club-2-fast-forward/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/punch-club-2-fast-forward/</guid><description>Game Description Punch Club 2: Fast Forward is a 2D action fighting game for real fighters who are not afraid of difficulties and are ready to fight their way through life&amp;rsquo;s challenges. You, as the main character, have spent 20 long years patiently waiting for your moment in your mother&amp;rsquo;s cramped garage, dreaming of a better life and searching for your missing father. But life doesn’t give you anything for nothing, and there will be many obstacles and troubles on your way.</description></item><item><title>Brotato</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/brotato/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/brotato/</guid><description>Game Description In the shooterBratato you have to take control of a potato using a variety of guns while fighting alien creatures. The gameplay includes roguelite genre elements. Locations are procedurally generated, and each run can take up to 30 minutes of real time. There are dozens of types of weapons and additional items of equipment to choose from, allowing you to progress at your own pace and combine the effects of items.</description></item><item><title>Pixel Ripped 1978: An Atari Adventure</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/pixel-ripped-1978-an-atari-adventure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/pixel-ripped-1978-an-atari-adventure/</guid><description>Game Description Pixel Ripped 1978: An Atari Adventure is a virtual adventure, the plot of which is built around the confrontation between two heroines and the villain Cyblin Lord. The narrative is split between two realities. In one of them, the protagonist is Dot, a character in the in-game world, and in the other, her creator named Bug, an Atari employee. The antagonist interferes with Bug&amp;rsquo;s past, trying to change her creative plans and prevent the creation of a happy universe for Dot.</description></item><item><title>Elypse</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/elypse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/elypse/</guid><description>Game Description Elypse is an atmospheric metroidvania, which is a mixture of classic platformer and 2D action. The action takes place in the very depths of hell. The plot tells how every 10 years it is necessary to sacrifice people to the Abyss in order to protect oneself from the mystical Abyss - an otherworldly force with destructive power. Unfortunately, the main character was chosen to become a victim.
There is always a chance of salvation: if you manage to pass all the tests that the Abyss has prepared, then you can continue your life.</description></item><item><title>Keeper's Toll</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/keepers-toll/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/keepers-toll/</guid><description>Game Description Keeper&amp;rsquo;s Toll is a fun and challenging game that will test the skills of any gamer who enjoys the classic retro time survival genre. Featuring unique dark fantasy elements, the game boasts a carefully crafted blend of skill-based gameplay, roguelike elements, and unique mechanics that set it apart from others in the genre.
Gamers will be able to choose from six different heroes, each with their own defining mechanics, abilities, and meta progression.</description></item><item><title>Tape to Tape</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tape-to-tape/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tape-to-tape/</guid><description>Game Description Tape to Tape is a sports simulation that offers gamers an original roguelite approach. Every decision you make has a huge impact on your journey to creating the best hockey team. Choose your path, recruit unique players, find synergies between them, choose special abilities, bribe the judges or visit the Blademaster to restore the former glory of hockey. Explore the beautiful world of hockey in a roguelike style, where every decision you make matters as you rebuild hockey in all its glory.</description></item><item><title>Magical Drop 6</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/magical-drop-6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/magical-drop-6/</guid><description>Game Description Magical Drop VI, the next installment in the popular Japanese arcade game series, combines a captivating storyline, colorful characters, various modes and difficulty levels, and the ability to play with other people online or offline. In this game, you can choose your favorite character from 15, each with their own personality, backstory, and soundtrack. You can then choose from a variety of available modes, depending on your mood and preferences.</description></item><item><title>First Racer</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/first-racer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/first-racer/</guid><description>Game Description First Racer is an arcade race where victory is achieved not only through quick reactions, but also through proper preparation of the car. The project offers a wide range of competitive disciplines, covering both city streets and specialized tracks. For fans of extreme driving, there are cross-country races that require a special approach to control. Drifting competitions, in turn, test your car control in a controlled drift, where points are awarded based on angle, speed and style of execution.</description></item><item><title>Crab Champions</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/crab-champions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/crab-champions/</guid><description>Game Description Crab Champions is one of those projects where the gamer is given control of an extraordinary hero. As you can guess from the name, the characters of the game are crabs. The setting is tropical islands - the player will be surrounded by palm trees, sand, ocean, stones and exotic animals. And also other crabs, armed to the teeth. Crab Champions can be played in three different modes: Co-op.</description></item><item><title>Saga of Sins</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/saga-of-sins/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/saga-of-sins/</guid><description>Game Description Saga of Sins is an atmospheric action role-playing game in a dark setting in which you take on the role of demonic creatures to fight the deadly sins and free the village of Sinwell from the infection. In this action-packed adventure, you play as Cecil the priest, who can enter people&amp;rsquo;s minds and transform into unique demons, each with their own individual skills and abilities.
Fight enemies, collect gold and upgrade your demons to become even stronger and face new challenges.</description></item><item><title>Boneraiser Minions</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/boneraiser-minions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/boneraiser-minions/</guid><description>Game Description Boneraiser Minions plunges you into a very dark fantasy universe, where powerful creatures once lived, whom people called boneraisers. They were none other than necromancers - wizards who delved into the study of the dark arts and, with their help, learned to raise the dead from their graves, then making their slaves out of them. The main character is one of these magicians, who was caught red-handed and decided to resort to the only method practiced in those days - burning at the stake and then burial in a sacred temple.</description></item><item><title>Spectator</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/spectator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/spectator/</guid><description>Game Description Spectator can please fans of Internet folklore. This game is inspired by popular urban legends. Here you can go Backstage, visit Slenderman’s habitat and visit other locations. It&amp;rsquo;s full of all kinds of references. The video game is a representative of the point-and-click survival horror genre. The indie title uses a first-person perspective. Before you start, you can choose one of 3 difficulty types: normal, hard and nightmare. There are 6 levels (days) in total.</description></item><item><title>Risky Woods</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/risky-woods/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/risky-woods/</guid><description>Game Description Risky Woods invites gamers to a breathtaking, adrenaline-filled arcade adventure! Are you ready to take on the biggest test yet? As the fearless warrior Rohan, you must fight your way through treacherous forests and dark caves. But beware - the path is full of dangers, from stomping Skeletons to insidious traps and face-snatching flying devils! Arms in hand, you must navigate treacherous terrain, free petrified monks, and defeat the evil Draxos once and for all.</description></item><item><title>Scott Pilgrim vs. The World: The Game – Complete Edition</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/scott-pilgrim-vs-the-world-the-game-complete-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/scott-pilgrim-vs-the-world-the-game-complete-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Scott Pilgrim vs. The World: The Game - Complete Edition is a whirlwind arcade action-adventure game based on the plot of the famous series of graphic novels and the movie of the same name. In addition to the original game, equally exciting add-ons Knives Chau and Wallace are also available. Players can choose to play through many of their favorite characters, such as Scott Pilgrim himself, Ramona, Knives, Stephen Stills and others.</description></item><item><title>Military Conflict: Vietnam</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/military-conflict-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/military-conflict-vietnam/</guid><description>Game Description Military Conflict: Vietnam is a fast-paced multiplayer first-person shooter that combines fast-paced arcade action with the realism of intense battles. The game invites you to plunge into the fierce confrontation between the American army and the Viet Cong guerrillas, concentrating on close combat. The gameplay mechanics and controls are familiar to fans of the genre, which allows you to quickly immerse yourself in the process, and for beginners there is a training ground where you can hone your skills.</description></item><item><title>SokoFrog</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sokofrog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/sokofrog/</guid><description>Game Description SokoFrog is a Sokoban-style puzzle game where the main goal is to move blocks to open a passage to the next stage. The little frog is under control and needs help in solving spatial problems. The entire gameplay is built around one central mechanic: you need to place a box with a symbol printed on it on a tile with a similar image. Successfully completing this action will unlock the door leading further.</description></item><item><title>Atari 50: The Anniversary Celebration</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/atari-50-the-anniversary-celebration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/atari-50-the-anniversary-celebration/</guid><description>Game Description Atari 50: The Anniversary Celebration takes gamers on an interactive adventure that follows the development of the video game industry over fifty years. Users will watch a variety of arcade projects in which they will take part. You will be able to enjoy a variety of gameplay mechanics that underlie the following projects: Swordquest, VCTR-SCTR, Neo Breakout, Quadtank, Yars' Revenge Reimagined, Haunted Houses, etc.
Users of Atari 50: The Anniversary Celebration will have a wide variety of opportunities to immerse themselves in pixelated arcade games made in the spirit of old-school retro games from the 90s.</description></item><item><title>The Exorcist's Story</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-exorcists-story/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-exorcists-story/</guid><description>Game Description The Exorcist&amp;rsquo;s Story is an atmospheric 2D adventure game in which you will find yourself in the shoes of a young priest, Antonio, who had experience in performing exorcism rituals. But one day everything went wrong and a girl died during the ceremony. You escaped prison, but you promised yourself never to perform such rituals again. But a few years later, strange things begin to happen in your small town and Asmodeus, the demon you once encountered, challenges you again.</description></item><item><title>Lunistic</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lunistice/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/lunistice/</guid><description>Game Description Lunistice may be of interest to those nostalgic for early 3D platformers. The graphics in this project are specially made in a low-poly style and in low resolution. This retro platformer imitates the console hits that came out on fifth-generation consoles in the 90s. He suggests exploring the memories of the main character named Hana. In the story, she is trying to get to the Moon. Her adventures consist of linear levels.</description></item><item><title>Last Command</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/last-command/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/last-command/</guid><description>Game Description Last Command is deceptively easy to learn. To control, the player will only need the arrows on the keyboard and the mouse, but this does not make the task easier at all. A huge number of obstacles on the way, bosses with a large area of ​​​​AoE damage and many additional small attacks will definitely not let you relax. The game is perfect for those who love hardcore challenges mixed with a puzzle.</description></item><item><title>Vampire Survivors</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/vampire-survivors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/vampire-survivors/</guid><description>Game Description Survival in theVampire Survivors universe is based on minimalist gameplay, where you have to move around the map and knock out as much gold as possible. The main task for the protagonist is to advance through the levels generated in roguelight style. You need to try to survive the night, fighting off monsters and higher undead. Vampires will hunt for the protagonist, not giving him the opportunity to rest at a rest or come up with a future plan of action.</description></item><item><title>NeverAwake</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/neverawake/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/neverawake/</guid><description>Game Description NeverAwake is a 2D side-scrolling action platformer with beautiful hand-drawn graphics about a girl named Rem. She is still a child of 10 years old and suffers from regular nightmares in which she strives to conquer everything that brought her resentment and pain in real life. Her opponents are not the classic monsters from banal dreams, but those who were somehow able to damage her psyche. These are school friends and just classmates, dentists who hurt when they pulled out teeth and even yard dogs that try to bite her every morning when she goes to school.</description></item><item><title>HYPER DEMON</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/hyper-demon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/hyper-demon/</guid><description>Game Description HYPER DEMON is a minimalist and experimental first-person shooter. It stands out for its visual style. It has very fast and dynamic gameplay. Here you can make jerks, slide, perform regular jumps and something like rocket jumps. There are more than a dozen techniques in total. You can master all these mechanics through training. The protagonist shoots daggers at demonic creatures from his outstretched hand. He is also capable of using consumable gems.</description></item><item><title>Rollerdrome</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rollerdrome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rollerdrome/</guid><description>Game Description The Rollerdrome shooter combines dynamic and vibrant battles, smooth graphics, third-person view and tactical mechanics that allow you to influence the outcome of the battle even with lower chances of winning. The player will have to participate in fierce battles with a variety of opponents. By killing opponents, the main character restores health and replenishes ammunition. During the fight, you can perform spectacular tricks, dodges, or use various tactical movements to eliminate opponents.</description></item><item><title>GigaBash</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/gigabash/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/gigabash/</guid><description>Game Description GigaBash is an adventure game about huge kaiju monsters capable of destroying entire cities. One day, humanity was faced with a global threat: huge monsters appeared on Earth and began to wage a protracted battle among themselves, destroying human settlements and killing each other. Gigabash talks about how complete chaos reigned on the planet: people fight against unknown creatures, monsters fight with themselves and confront people. Absolute madness and destruction reign.</description></item><item><title>Shotgun King: The Final Checkmate</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/shotgun-king-the-final-checkmate/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/shotgun-king-the-final-checkmate/</guid><description>Game Description Shotgun King: The Final Checkmate is an alternate version of chess with elements of classic roguelikes. Users will have to go on action missions, controlling a selected figure with a royal shotgun. The main task for the protagonist will be the destruction of enemy objects on a field designed in the form of a standard chessboard. Players have to destroy the white pieces on behalf of the Black King, who has prepared firearms.</description></item><item><title>Shredders</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/shredders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/shredders/</guid><description>Game Description Shredders is a snowboarding simulator. The indie project contains a large number of references for fans of this sport and related media products. You can play it alone or with other users online. For single-player fans, there is a single-player story mode. The plot begins with the protagonist and best friend Scotty trying to make entertaining videos about winter extreme sports. A representative of one of the brands named Lisa contacts them and offers sponsorship along with participation in the championship.</description></item><item><title>Dawn of the Monsters</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dawn-of-the-monsters/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dawn-of-the-monsters/</guid><description>Game Description Dawn of the Monsters takes place in the distant future. According to it, humanity has achieved a certain technological progress. But everything turned out to be not so rosy. Evil and cruel invaders have arrived on Earth and are ready to do anything to enslave humanity. They are called Nephilim. True, the little people also have aces up their sleeves. The global network of the defense alliance decides to engage them in battle, and is even ready to sacrifice lives.</description></item><item><title>Pets at Work</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/pets-at-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/pets-at-work/</guid><description>Game Description Pets at Work is a colorful arcade puzzle adventure game designed for local multiplayer that revolves around a group of funny animals who have lost their owners in an office building. To find people, pets must interact as a team using boxes, mats, buttons and climbing on shelves and tables. Dozens of levels have been implemented, each of which has more than six different mechanics, which provides players with exciting and dynamic gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 5</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-5/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 5 is a racing game that focuses on multiplayer racing and free-roaming in an open world. This project includes many aspects from Forza&amp;rsquo;s previous games. More than 200 original cars from real-life companies are presented, with realistic driving and clutch physics. There are high-quality graphics, effects and other elements that completely immerse users in a believable environment.
While riding around the world, the player is able to collide with other gamers or ordinary cars controlled by artificial intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Bubble Bobble 4 Friends: The Baron's Workshop</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bubble-bobble-4-friends-the-barons-workshop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/bubble-bobble-4-friends-the-barons-workshop/</guid><description>Game Description Bubble Bobble 4 Friends: The Baron&amp;rsquo;s Workshop is an atmospheric adventure where you have to control small bubbles. The user will have to solve puzzles and various tasks that require a logical approach. You have to take control of Bub, Bob, Peb or Pub, who are capable of exploding interactive objects in the environment, in order to cope with offenders and opponents living in the locations. Players need to visit a large number of locations made in a colorful style.</description></item><item><title>Skydrift Infinity</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/skydrift-infinity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/skydrift-infinity/</guid><description>Game Description Skydrift Infinity is an arcade game with simulator elements that allows you to take the controls of an airplane and rush through the picturesque expanses of an interactive world. You can fly in free mode or compete with other pilots. If it is impossible to catch up with the enemy, then you can shoot him down! Exotic islands are available for exploration, representing huge arenas for air racing.</description></item><item><title>F1 2021</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/f1-2021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/f1-2021/</guid><description>Game Description F1 2021 is a racing car simulator. The new part of the series provides an opportunity to take part in the 2021 season of the Formula 1 championship. Thanks to the official license, the product contains real teams, drivers and tracks. There is a choice of difficulty. Here you can configure the aggressiveness of artificial intelligence, the severity of the rules, and the driving assistance system. Casual users will be able to make the gameplay more arcade-like, and hardcore users will be able to add realism to the gameplay.</description></item><item><title>Agent Intercept</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/agent-intercept/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/agent-intercept/</guid><description>Game Description Agent Intercept is a dynamic arcade game full of exciting chases, intrigue, explosions and destruction. As the main character, you need to stop the crime syndicate CLAWS. They are developing a powerful transforming machine that is capable of destroying the entire world. You need to drive a car called Scepter. Transport is equipped with the latest gadgets and spy technologies. Racing along the tracks, you need to drift, jump on springboards, cut through air and water, and also try to elude death.</description></item><item><title>DOOMBRINGER</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/doombringer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/doombringer/</guid><description>Game Description DOOMBRINGER is an uncompromising arena shooter, the gameplay formula of which is built on rapid movement, merciless destruction of enemies and masterful use of the arsenal. Confrontation with opponents is devoid of an element of chance, since each attack is predictable and can be prevented, which transfers all responsibility for survival to the skill of the gamer himself. The visual style refers to the classics of the genre, and the movement system with an emphasis on expressive jumping and jumping allows you to navigate the well-designed maps as efficiently as possible.</description></item><item><title>Astrodogs</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/astrodogs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/astrodogs/</guid><description>Game Description Astrodogs is an arcade action game where space dogs take part in battles. The main characters will have to save the galaxy from the WOOFER company, which controls all territories and planets. Enemy dogs attack civilians, deceive ordinary workers and commit other wrong acts, because of which the ruin of the entire civilization is on the verge.
The usual antics of the suspicious organization weren&amp;rsquo;t too bad until they started attacking every planet in the solar system.</description></item><item><title>ROUNDS</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rounds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rounds/</guid><description>Game Description ROUNDS is a competitive game with several modes and numerous locations for competition. Each match takes place in a 1v1 style, where participants try to score more points or kill their opponent. In a 2D side-scrolling world, you control round characters with arms and legs. They use the elements around them or firearms to win battles.
As soon as the round ends, the next, more dynamic level immediately begins.</description></item><item><title>Metal Heads</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/metal-heads/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/metal-heads/</guid><description>Game Description Metal Heads is a multiplayer adventure with 1 to 8 participants simultaneously in each match. Users will compete in a variety of modes, team or single matches. The gameplay features over 15 original mini-games with multiple elements, easy process and difficult to master. The project allows you to participate via a local network, on one monitor or online.
Mini-games in Metal Heads:
Pipemare - takes participants to a small area where they will try to survive among a dozen dangers.</description></item><item><title>pureya</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/pureya/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/pureya/</guid><description>Game Description pureya is a collection of pixel mini-games lasting 10 seconds. The user will go through hundreds of modes with original obstacles and goals. The location, missions and traps will change constantly. Somewhere you have to travel on a spaceship and fly around objects, or fight enemies as a powerful knight.
Each arcade is controlled using two buttons. The gameplay features 2 main modes: complete passage and change every 10 seconds.</description></item><item><title>Forza Horizon 4</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/forza-horizon-4/</guid><description>Game Description Forza Horizon 4 is a realistic racing simulator with an open game world, where the player is given the opportunity to explore many cities, participate in various races and interact with other players. Drive along the tracks of Great Britain, unlock new cars, and take part in tournaments and races.
The gameplay is focused on interaction between players. To participate in certain races, you will need to find a suitable area, as well as gather all participants in one lobby.</description></item><item><title>Rhythm Doctor</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rhythm-doctor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/rhythm-doctor/</guid><description>Game Description Rhythm Doctor is an indie game in which you need to treat patients to the rhythm of music. The music in the game has healing properties. Each patient has unusual problems based on music theory: polyrhythms, hemiols, atonality, syncopation, etc. Rhythm Doctor helps you learn music theory through gameplay. The game contains: more than 20 levels with their own stories; each chapter is a rhythmic concept; many doctors and unique patients; single and cooperative mode; about 50 different visual effects and backgrounds.</description></item><item><title>Flipon</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/flipon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/flipon/</guid><description>Game Description Flipon invites gamers to immerse themselves in a fast-paced adventure across the solar system as they join Kat and her team on a planet-spanning quest. The adventure consists of 75 levels, each of which is set against the backdrop of five unique planets, representing challenges guarded by formidable creatures. Users will have to show strategic thinking, building combinations of flip blocks and solving various puzzles. The cute opponents you meet along the way add an extra layer of challenge that makes the game lively and fun.</description></item><item><title>Maiden and Spell</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/maiden-and-spell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/maiden-and-spell/</guid><description>Game Description Maiden and Spell is a scrolling shooter in which the main characters are girls. The user is given a choice of 8 female characters, which differ from each other not only in appearance, but also in their ability sets. The fictional universe created by indie developers is filled with magic and unusual creatures. The setting is the Kingdom of Stars, which is represented by many locations in the background, because the game has a top-down camera.</description></item><item><title>NFS Heat</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nfs-heat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nfs-heat/</guid><description>Game Description Need for Speed: Heat is an arcade racing simulator with an open game world and a large selection of cars of a wide variety of brands. The plot takes place in Palm City, a fictional city very similar to sunny Miami. You will be able to ride around the city, along the coast, and also take part in stunning races. The story begins with police captain Mercer catching one of the participants in night racing, which is prohibited by law.</description></item><item><title>Singled Out</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/singled-out/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/singled-out/</guid><description>Game Description Singled Out is a test of reaction speed and observation, where the task is to accurately identify a target in a crowd. The player is presented with a kaleidoscope of eccentric creatures, but only one of them matches the three descriptive characteristics provided. An inexorable ten-second timer forces you to act as quickly as possible, because any mistake or delay leads to failure. The search process turns into an intense visual puzzle, where every second counts and extreme concentration on the smallest details of appearance is required.</description></item><item><title>Dude Simulator 3</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dude-simulator-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dude-simulator-3/</guid><description>Game Description Dude Simulator 3 is a dude simulator that is characterized by absurdity and black humor. You play the role of a “friend” who is preparing for his friend’s birthday. The day begins with you buying him a gift. Now we need to deliver it, but my friend lives in another city. You are about to go on an adventure that promises many funny and exciting moments.
Gameplay Dude Simulator 3 features an open world sandbox with a unique cubic visual style.</description></item><item><title>Muse Dash</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/muse-dash/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/muse-dash/</guid><description>Game Description Muse Dash is a dynamic rhythm game in anime style, where you will visit many colorful locations, dance to the rhythm of fiery songs and send enemies into outer space. At the center of the story are three charismatic beauties. Having chosen one of the heroines, you need to fight with various creatures in the rhythm of the dance. The action will take place on a colorful background accompanied by dynamic dance music.</description></item><item><title>Mortal Kombat 11: Ultimate Edition</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mortal-kombat-11-ultimate-edition/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mortal-kombat-11-ultimate-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Despite the average ratings for the 10th part of the franchise,Mortal Kombat 11 became a continuation of the story, and the developers tried to improve and add a lot of new things to players. The eleventh fighting game in the Mortal Kombat universe has new gameplay, plot, graphics, and character relationships that reveal the story as it progresses. We arrive in the world after the defeat of Shinnok, who was defeated by Cassie Cage.</description></item><item><title>BallisticNG</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ballisticng/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/ballisticng/</guid><description>Game Description BallisticNG is a dynamic racing simulator in the setting of a sci-fi distant future, in which all available technologies have made an unprecedented leap thanks to the painstaking work of the best minds of the human race. In 2159, battles on the tracks take place in vehicles equipped with an anti-gravity unit that allows them to hover above the earthen surface. The game supports earning achievements from a pre-prepared list of 26 awards, a built-in level editor, a leaderboard, as well as modern technology - a virtual reality helmet.</description></item><item><title>Katamari Damacy REROLL</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/katamari-damacy-reroll/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/katamari-damacy-reroll/</guid><description>Game Description Katamari Damacy REROLL takes users to a bizarre alternative reality. The King of All Space destroys all the stars. The ruler did this not on purpose, but by accident. He instructs the Prince to correct his own mistake to see how the heir copes with the task. He flies to Earth with his father&amp;rsquo;s crazy plan. You have to play for your little son.
Katamari Damacy REROLL is an improved version of the game that was released back in 2004.</description></item><item><title>FIGHTING EX LAYER</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/fighting-ex-layer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/fighting-ex-layer/</guid><description>Game Description FIGHTING EX LAYER, as the name suggests, is a fighting game. The game has two types of controls - classic and progressive. The first is designed for fans of fighting, and the second is suitable for beginners. Battles take place in 2.5D in closed arenas.
The gameplay of the project is reminiscent of the second or third part of SF and other virtual battles of the 90s. The super canceling mechanic allows you to abruptly cancel a combo during the attack animation in order to quickly carry out another series of attacks.</description></item><item><title>NBA 2K Playgrounds 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nba-2k-playgrounds-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/nba-2k-playgrounds-2/</guid><description>Game Description NBA 2K Playgrounds 2 is a continuation of the famous basketball sports simulator. This release will feature mind-blowing modes, a considerable number of tricks and tricks, as well as more popular athletes!
Speaking of them, you can choose your character from more than 400 wards. Half of them are still playing professionally in real life, the other half are world-class stars who have retired, including Kobe Bryant, Karl-Anthony Towns, Michael Jordan and others.</description></item><item><title>The Crew 2</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-crew-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/the-crew-2/</guid><description>Game Description In The Crew 2 you can ride anything, as long as you have money for this equipment. The game includes several game modes in the genre of a sports racing simulator from a third/first person: free, cooperative, career, multiplayer mode. A free race usually takes place on a separate map. We choose one unlocked vehicle element and try to win the race. In this simulator you can sail on a boat, drive a fast, high-speed car, or fly on an airplane.</description></item><item><title>DRAGON BALL FighterZ</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dragon-ball-fighterz/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/dragon-ball-fighterz/</guid><description>Game Description A good, juicy anime fighting game with the Tag Team system - DRAGON BALL FighterZ - takes us on a fascinating journey through the beautiful animation of the fight itself, where “press all the buttons at once” and “use according to your abilities” are practically the same thing. The gameplay of the fighting game is, on the one hand, incredibly simple, but on the other hand, difficult and interesting if you play by the rules.</description></item><item><title>CarX Drift Racing Online</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/carx-drift-racing-online/</guid><description>Game Description Arcade car simulatorCarX Drift Racing Online is a new word in the world of racing, where the main component is drifting! From the very beginning, you will have a huge number of opportunities that you can use in the world of real graphics and pumping up cars with modifications from famous manufacturers. From the first to the last minute in the game you will be able to upgrade your car so that it becomes a world prize-winner in the world of drifting!</description></item><item><title>Mutant Football League</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mutant-football-league/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mutant-football-league/</guid><description>Game Description Mutant Football League is a sports action simulator in which monsters and a wide variety of creatures will take to the field for sports games. You can create your own team of the most unique creatures that will be able to compete with other squads in various games. You will fight monsters, huge worms, or take part in sports games to the death.
Each mission offers you a new challenge, as well as stronger enemy teams.</description></item><item><title>TEKKEN 7</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tekken-7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/tekken-7/</guid><description>Game Description TEKKEN 7 is a side-scrolling 3D fighting game that tells the true story of the Mishima clan&amp;rsquo;s feud. In the storyline we learn why Heitachi killed his wife, for what reasons Kazuya Mishima survived. The basis of the game&amp;rsquo;s action is a fighting game based on love, family relationships with friendly fights.
Each battle in Tekken 7 is a separate branch in the plot, so after the end of the battle (victory in it), we see a small interactive video of the creation of the entire universe, Kazuya growing up, and the formation of the Mishima clan.</description></item><item><title>N++ (NPLUSPLUS)</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/n-nplusplus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/n-nplusplus/</guid><description>Game Description N++ (NPLUSPLUS) is a dynamic indie platformer, each level of which is built using the simplest graphics possible, using many shades to create a memorable picture. The gamer is given a side view of a two-dimensional space, through which it is necessary to move a small man, shown schematically. The project uses the player’s skills to correctly and quickly assess the environment to make the most correct decisions. To perform precise and complex jumps, gamers will need skill and experience in this genre of video game entertainment.</description></item><item><title>Raiden Legacy - Steam Edition</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/raiden-legacy-steam-edition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/raiden-legacy-steam-edition/</guid><description>Game Description Raiden Legacy is a collection of four arcade action games by Japanese game designer Kaihatsu Seibu. The games take place in 2090. Our planet was attacked by alien forces. The World Alliance decides to fight back and creates a special project called Raiden.
You play as an experienced pilot who is the only hope for saving humanity. Arm yourself with powerful guns, board a battle shuttle and destroy a huge number of enemies.</description></item><item><title>Mushihimesama</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mushihimesama/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/mushihimesama/</guid><description>Game Description Mushihimesama is set in a wild and unspoiled world with vast desert areas gradually turning into dense forests. Kozuyu&amp;rsquo;s arthropods, insect beasts, live here. Once they die, vegetation grows around the area where they die, creating a natural cycle of life and death. This race has the vital force of Levi-Sense, which turned out to be incredibly poisonous for people and was called miasma.
Only a few inhabited areas were allowed to live, but in exchange for a little 15-year-old girl every 200 years.</description></item><item><title>Broforce</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/broforce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/broforce/</guid><description>Game Description Broforce is a powerful paramilitary organization that is called upon when the world is in danger due to an excessive number of evil forces. Take control of dozens of different brothers to counter terrorist attacks and save civilians. Destroy your opponents with napalm, shooting, lightning and other various character skills.
Broforce is a 2D shooter platformer with pixel graphics. You will move around locations, destroying opponents in every possible way.</description></item><item><title>Geometry Dash</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/geometry-dash/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/geometry-dash/</guid><description>Game Description Geometry Dash is a 2D arcade game aimed at hardcore level completion. You will take control of a unique character, which can be in the form of a geometric figure, to pass the most difficult levels and open up new opportunities in the gameplay. Here you will find more than 100 original and challenging missions, as well as the opportunity to create your own main character and share your results on the leaderboard.</description></item><item><title>BlazeRush</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/blazerush/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/blazerush/</guid><description>Game Description The creators of BlazeRush were clearly inspired by Blizzard&amp;rsquo;s ride-alongs that came out on consoles back in the 90s. Since that project ultimately did not reach the PC, its spiritual successor appeared a couple of decades later. The game also successfully played with the idea of ​​another racing hit of those years - &amp;ldquo;Micromachines&amp;rdquo; - in the form of a single screen for all participants in the race. The arcade action game features co-op for four people.</description></item><item><title>GRID Autosport</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/grid-autosport/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/grid-autosport/</guid><description>Game Description GRID Autosport develops a career mode and free driving in a huge number of cars, which can also be upgraded depending on your preferences. The new part of GRID is a car simulator with several game modes. Career passage is a single, story-based scenario part - this is about upgrading your driver, team of mechanics and building a reputation at the level of your driving. Here we upgrade the car and drive on 100 routes in 22 game locations, distributed according to difficulty and prestige.</description></item><item><title>One Finger Death Punch</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/one-finger-death-punch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/one-finger-death-punch/</guid><description>Game Description One finger death punch is an arcade fighting game in the style of beat&amp;rsquo;em up, in which you can feel like a real martial arts master. In this game we have to fight off crowds of enemies that have surrounded the main character and are advancing from opposite sides. The game design is made in 2D, and all the characters are drawn people, which adds simplicity to the game, but at the same time makes it unusual.</description></item><item><title>Super Hexagon</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/super-hexagon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/super-hexagon/</guid><description>Game Description Super Hexagon does not contain any plot. This is a dynamic arcade game with a top view. From the outside it looks like an endless game. But in fact, it can be passed. It will not be easy to reach the end, since the title is very hardcore. The project uses a minimalistic visual style.
The gameplay is about survival in the arena. In Super Hexagon it is hexagonal in shape.</description></item><item><title>Castle Crashers</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/castle-crashers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/castle-crashers/</guid><description>Game Description Castle Crashers is an arcade action game in which players will take control of powerful characters and fight monsters. Create a squad by choosing from 25 characters to fight your way through castles against your enemies. Compete with other users or monsters living throughout the continent. The plot will unfold at a ball in the king&amp;rsquo;s castle. During the fun, an evil sorcerer stole a precious magic stone and four princesses, who must be rescued by the knights and fight the enemy.</description></item><item><title>Coven</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/coven/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:44 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/coven/</guid><description>Game Description Going to the gloomy world ofCoven, you have to deal with a large number of enemy creatures and deal with their elimination. The universe takes you into an atmospheric medieval fantasy world, where witches and other mythical creatures live alongside people. The first episode is available in the game, where you will take on the role of a young girl. The heroine is burned at the stake during the 1600s, mistaken for a witch and a fiend.</description></item><item><title>Follow me</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/follow-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/follow-me/</guid><description>Game Description Follow Me is a charming 2D platformer that takes you on an exciting adventure through a huge and colorful world. The plot revolves around a curious little white rabbit who goes on a journey to discover what lies behind a mysterious door. Game mechanics focus on exploration and interaction with other characters. The world is full of both friendly and hostile creatures, and you need to use your wits and skills to navigate various locations and solve puzzles.</description></item><item><title>Half-Life 2D: Block Mesa</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/half-life-2d-block-mesa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/half-life-2d-block-mesa/</guid><description>Game Description Half-Life 2D: Block Mesa is a two-dimensional remake of the original Half-Life. The story also begins with a laboratory where another experiment was to take place. There were no signs of trouble until a powerful explosion occurred right before your eyes. Alien entities have infiltrated from the world of Zen, a military detachment is trying to rectify the situation, but it is becoming more and more difficult every minute.</description></item><item><title>Wanderburg</title><link>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/wanderburg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://game-vibe.github.io/posts/wanderburg/</guid><description>Game Description Wanderburg is an open-world roguelike that places gamers at the center of a brutal ecosystem where entire castles on wheels move across procedurally generated lands. Each such stronghold is a predator, preying on weaker competitors and absorbing everything in its path for its own strengthening. The setting is filled with anachronistic technology, such as knights on motorcycles and steam-powered siege engines, which creates a unique atmosphere of the absurd Middle Ages.</description></item></channel></rss>